English 简体中文 繁體中文 Français Deutsch Italiano 日本語 한국어 Português русский Español Türkçe Print This Page  

KIXEYE Inc. Privacy Policy
==========================

Last Updated: June 23, 2023

I. Introduction to Our Privacy Policy
-------------------------------------

KIXEYE Inc. ("we" or "KIXEYE") is serious about games. And we are serious about your privacy and data rights. We are committed to maintaining a relationship of trust and transparency with you. This Privacy Policy is written in plain language to make it easy to understand how we collect, use, store, and share information that is identifiable to you ("Personal Data" – “Personal Data” may, when the context indicates, also mean “Personal Information” as set forth in the California Consumer Privacy Protection Act of 2018 and / or the EU General Data Protection Regulation) when you access our websites, mobile applications, games, forums, or other services (collectively the "Services"). When you use a Service, you consent to each of the collections, uses and disclosures of information (including recording and tracking) described in this Privacy Policy. Please read it carefully. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE ANY SERVICE.

II. What Information/Personal Data Do We Collect?
-------------------------------------------------

### A. Information You Provide to Us Directly.

When you interact with a KIXEYE owned website, or download the Service from a third-party app store, we will collect and store information from you directly as described below, to the extent it is available to us. We collect the information that you give us, and the information may include your:

* Name
* E-mail address
* KIXEYE account information, such as unique user-name, ID or avatar
* Your ID from various “Social Networks” (including Facebook, Apple iTunes, Google Play, Steam, etc.)
* We may also offer you the option to complete a user profile that is visible to other Service users. Your user profile may include: a profile image; one or more Service username(s); and a KIXEYE user ID number that is created by KIXEYE and used to identify your profile.
* Payment or billing information
* Your messages to us or the Services (chat logs, customer support requests)
* Information that helps us verify it’s actually you, prevent fraud, develop and improve our Services

### B. Automatically Collected Information.

We collect other information automatically from your device through cookies and other means (SDKs, tracking pixels etc.) when you use our Services, including, to the extent it is available, and when required, subject to your consent:

* IP Address
* General Location Data Device information (such as device type, model, operating system, browser version, or unique device identifiers for checking device compatibility and IDFA or GAID)
* IDFA means Identifier for Advertisers on Apple and GAID means Google Advertising Identity. These unique identifiers are non-permanent and non-personal, meaning they do not contain sensitive information about you but do allow for consistency across all apps and cross-app tracking. You can opt-out of sharing your device identifier by updating the settings on your device.
* Service communications (in-game messages, chat logs)
* Connection type

### C. Information Given to Us by Third Parties.

We may be given access to certain information collected from you by third parties, including Social Networks, through your use of such third party’s services, websites, applications, or other services.

### D. Information we Collect Regarding Your Account.

We will create and assign to your device an identifier that is similar to an account number. We will also collect the following information about you, to the extent it is available, and if required, based on your consent:

* Game username;
* Device type; model; operating system; memory; storage;
* Telephone number;
* Country, region, city;
* User name, character name;
* Language;
* E-mail address; and
* Your contacts to enable you to invite friends to join you in the Service.

When you use our Services, we will collect information about the ways in which you use and interact with our Services, such as when and for how long your device is logged into our games, game features you access and other players you interact with, in-app purchases you make, progress or levels you achieve, and other gameplay activities.

We also collect pseudonymous usage statistics about your interactions with the Service. This information is typically collected through the use of server log files or web log files, mobile device software development kits and tracking technologies like browser cookies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information. Some of the cookies the Service places on your computer are linked to your user ID number(s). 

### E. Information Gathered Through your participation in Communities

When you use the Service, you will get access to the online gaming community within the Service which gives you the opportunity to communicate or share information not just with us, but also with other users of our Service through:

* Participating in player forums and message boards;
* Posting public comments to other users’ profiles or game boards;
* Sending private messages or invitations to other users, either directly on our websites or to their e-mail accounts;
* Chat with other users; and
* Posting web links.

When you participate in online gaming communities, we access and store information / Personal Data about you. The information we store varies by game / application and is affected by the privacy settings you and your friends establish in that game / application. You can control and find out more about these settings within the application. We will collect the following information:

* Your in-Service username;
* Your device advertiser ID;
* Depending on how you log into the Services, Facebook User ID;
* The IP address of your access devices;
* Your in-game chats and messages; and
* If provided by you, your e-mail address and phone number.
* Submitted Avatars

### F. Payment information

We will also collect some purchase information (which consists of transaction history, including what you have purchased, the price, and the date). Note that your in-game and/or in-app purchase transactions are processed by third-party payment processors, such as Apple (for purchases on iOS devices), Google (for purchases on Android devices). These third-party payment processors are the “merchant of record” for your purchases and do not share your financial information, like credit card numbers, with us.

### G. Customer Support correspondence

When you ask for assistance from our Customer Support team, we will collect and store:

* Your name and e-mail address;
* Information about your activity on the Service;
* Your user name or ID number; and
* Any correspondence connected to the assistance provided to you

### H. Information we Never Collect.

We do not collect any "special categories” of information from or about you. That is racial data or information regarding ethnic origin, sexual practices or orientation, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, union membership, or health data etc.

III. How and Why Do We Use this Information / Personal Data?
------------------------------------------------------------

We use your Personal Data and non-personal information to:

### A. Provide you with our Services.

* Communicate with you according to your preferences, and our Terms of Service.
* Operate, develop, maintain, and improve our Services.
* Provide customer support for the Services.
* Resolve disputes and enforce our Terms of Service.
* Make special/promotional in-game offers available to you
* Collect fees, payments, and other amounts due in connection with the Services.
* Enable you to connect with other players.
* Create a user account to use the Services.
* Provide you with the appropriate version of the Services, including in your preferred language.
* Identify, fix, and troubleshoot bugs and service errors.
* Develop new services.

### B. Secure our Services.

* Identify and/or prevent fraud.
* Identify and/or prevent Terms of Service violations, illegal activities or cheating.
* Verify user identities for customer support communications.
* Monitor, ensure and enhance the security of our network and information systems.

### C. Personalize our Services or Offer Promotions.

* Provide you with notices, personalized game experience and other offers.
* Communicate with you regarding your areas of interest and respond to your requests.
* Serve, optimize and measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.
* Perform analytics for internal marketing and demographic studies to develop, improve or personalize the Services.
* Save, track your game attributes, progress and stats.

### D. Legal/Other.

We also use your Personal Data and non-personal information to:

* Comply with legal obligations.
* Exercise, establish, or defend our Terms of Service and other legal rights.
* Instances in which we have a good faith belief of a need to protect the safety, financial or important interest of you, us or any other person.

IV. Who Do We Share this Information / Personal Data With?
----------------------------------------------------------

Except as described below, we will not share your Personal Data with unaffiliated third parties without your consent. However, we may share non-personal data, including anonymized, aggregated, or pseudonymized data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may share your information, including Personal Data to third parties in the following instances:

### A. Third Party Service Providers.

We may contract with third parties to collect or process your information or Personal Data on our behalf to provide the Services such as hosting providers to store the personal data you provide and for disaster recovery services, as well as for the performance of any contract we enter into with you, email delivery services, and analytics companies (credit card processing, sending customer service e-mails). Our agreements with such third parties require them to protect the confidentiality and security of your Personal Data and information in line with this Privacy Policy. We do not share Personal Data with any third parties so they can market to you, without your consent.

### B. KIXEYE Affiliated Companies.

We are a part of the StillFront AB group of companies. We may share your information amongst our subsidiaries, parents, or affiliated companies to deliver and/or improve our Services and extend you personalized experience and offers.

### C. A Successor or Acquiring Third Party.

If KIXEYE is merged with a third party, acquired, purchased (in full or in part), experiences a divestiture, reorganization, bankruptcy, or similar event, information collected under this Privacy Policy may be shared with such third party. We will notify you if this happens.

### D. As Required by Law.

We may disclose Personal Data if we have a good faith belief we are obliged to do so to:

* Comply with a legal obligation.
* Protect and defend the rights or property of KIXEYE, users of the Services, or others.
* Protect the personal safety, financial or important interest of users of the Services or the public.
* Protect against legal liability.
* Monitor compliance with & enforce our Terms of Service, policies, or forum/community rules.
* Respond to lawful requests by public authorities, including national security or law enforcement agencies.

V. How do we Store and Protect Your Personal Data?
--------------------------------------------------

### A. Protecting your Personal Data.

We implement reasonable security measures to protect the security of your information both online and offline, and we are committed to the protection of customer/user information. While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches of our Services and our customer databases and records, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the Internet is never completely secure. Although we strive to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted to our site; so any transmission is at your own risk. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe (including your account password), and to log out of your account after use. If your account is hacked, this may lead to unauthorized access to your account, so please keep your account information secure.

### B. Storing your Personal Data.

Personal Data we collect, is shared with us, or is processed under this Privacy Policy may be stored in the United States or any other country in which we, our subsidiaries/affiliates, or third-party service providers operate, including through the use of cloud storage. By using the Services, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Data and non-personal data to the United States and other countries which may not offer the same level of privacy protections as the laws in your country of residence or citizenship. As a result, your information could be accessed by foreign governmental authorities, or otherwise, in accordance with applicable local laws.

VI. Your Privacy Controls
-------------------------

You have control over the collection and use of your Personal Data. You may at any time access or correct your Personal Data, restrict collection or processing of your Personal Data, and in some cases, request the deactivation or permanent deletion of your Personal Data. To request access, correction, restriction, deactivation, or deletion of your Personal Data, contact us at [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Before we process any request, we may ask that you verify your identity to protect your privacy. This may include communication via the Services platform or other methods of identity verification.

Requests that are unverified, unreasonable or impractical may be rejected. To protect your account, requests for deactivation or deletion of Personal Data require additional verification, which may include a temporary suspension of your account and the Services. Once requests for deactivation or deletion are processed, they are permanent, and the Personal Data and account cannot be restored.

VII. Children Under Age 13
--------------------------

Our Services are not directed, or intended to be attractive, to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect Personal Data, personal information, photos, videos, audio files, or location data of or from children under the age of 13 or knowingly use persistent identifiers to recognize children under the age of 13 over time and across different websites or online services. If you are under the age of 13, do not use our Services and do not submit any information to us. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce this Privacy Policy by instructing their children under the age of 13 never to use our Services. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data or personal information to KIXEYE through our Services, please contact us at [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com), and we will take steps to delete that information from our databases as soon as possible.

VIII. Third Party Privacy Policies & Practices / Social Networks
----------------------------------------------------------------

This Privacy Policy applies only to Personal Data and information collected by KIXEYE through your use of our Services. Third-party websites may be accessible through links when using our Services, or you may have reached, accessed, downloaded our Services through third-party websites. These third-party websites are governed by their own privacy policies and we are not liable or responsible for any content appearing on those websites or any privacy or security practices for those websites. To manage the information KIXEYE receives about you from Social Networks where you use our Services, you will need to follow the instructions at that site for updating your information and changing your privacy settings. The privacy management tools for applications on Apple can be found at [http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/). The privacy management tools for Google can be found at [https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/). You can manage certain aspects of information collection and use by going to the settings of your (mobile) device and reviewing the permissions of each application.

Once KIXEYE receives your information from Social Networks, that information is stored and used by KIXEYE in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and you may access and update that information as described below. Accounts created with KIXEYE are considered active until we receive a user request to delete or deactivate them.

IX. Data Retention / Effect of Deletion Requests
------------------------------------------------

We strive to retain only as much Personal Data as is necessary. When Personal Data is no longer required under this Privacy Policy, we will periodically delete it or de-identify it. When it is not commercially reasonable to delete or de-identify your Personal Data, we will remove your Personal Data from processing and securely store it until we are able to permanently delete it. Please note that we may retain information needed for legal and accounting purposes, to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreements, protect our legal rights, and comply with technical and legal requirements and constraints. For example, we may retain records pertaining to payments or customer service matters. If you have sent or posted content on the Service, we may not be able to delete it. Effective deletion may require actions on your part such as deleting apps and/or content related to the Service from your device and/or de-linking the Service from your Social Network(s) account(s). Please note that if you ask us to delete your account all your progress in the game and any unused virtual items will be permanently lost to you. Note that results and artifacts from your in-game play, e.g. bases, characters, ships, supplies etc. may remain live in the game (and subject to game-play, i.e. destruction or exploitation by active players) even after your account and/or Personal Data has been deleted or dissociated from the game.

X. Legal Bases for European Countries’ Users
--------------------------------------------

If you are located in a country in the European Union, the European Economic Area, or Switzerland, the following are the legal bases which we rely upon in processing your information.

* Contractual Necessity. This covers data used by us in order to provide you with Services that you have requested - and that we have agreed - to provide to you, such as our games, customer services, and chat functionality;
* Legal Obligation. This covers data used by us to comply with legal obligations, such as to maintain records relating to tax or to respond to valid legal requests for certain data;
* Legitimate Interests. This covers data used by us for purposes that can be reasonably expected with your use of our Services and that we do not believe are harmful to your privacy, such as analytics to understand how our users navigate our websites and apps, to keep our websites and apps safe and secure, research and optimization of our Service, to provide a more personalized experience, marketing and advertising; and

Consent. In cases where we process data based on your consent, we will ask for your explicit consent. You may withdraw consent at any time, but that will not affect the lawfulness of the processing of your personal data prior to such withdrawal.

While you can withdraw your consent or object to certain types of processing at any time in the ways described in this Privacy Policy, please note that if you continue to use the Services after such request(s) we will resume collecting personal data about you and process it as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not want us to collect any personal data about you at all, you should cease all game play and use of our Services.

XI. European Countries Users’ Rights
------------------------------------

If you are located in a country in the European Union, the European Economic Area, or Switzerland, you have certain rights in relation to the personal data we hold about you, which we detail below, and which are subject to exemptions under applicable data privacy laws. Some of these only apply in certain circumstances as set out in more detail below. We also set out how to exercise those rights. Please note that we may require you to verify your identity before responding to any requests to exercise your rights. We will respond to a request by you to exercise those rights without undue delay and at least within one month (although this may be extended by a further two months in certain circumstances). To exercise any of your rights, please send an email to [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

We may decline to process requests in certain circumstances, such as where requests are manifestly unfounded or excessive or requests that jeopardize the privacy of others.

### A. Deletion of your personal data

In some circumstances, you may request that we erase some of the personal data we hold about you. Should you wish to have your Personal Data deleted, please contact us at [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Please note that in order to process your request and ensure deletion you must delete our apps/games from your mobile devices and clear our cookies from any device where you have played our games. You must also remove all Service functionality links within your Social Network accounts. When we delete any information, it will be deleted from our active databases but may remain in our archives. Please note, however, we may still retain some or all of that information for other purposes such as maintaining financial records, protecting or enforcing legal rights, maintaining marketing suppression lists or for technical reasons such as maintaining technical security or our database integrity. We may also retain your information in an anonymized form. See “Data Retention Impact of Deletion” above for more information about requests for deletion.

### B Access and portability

You have a right to know what information we hold about you and, in some cases, to have the information communicated to you. If you wish to exercise this right, please contact us at [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) and let us know that you wish to exercise your right of access and precisely what information you are requesting. Please note that we may not be able to provide all the information you ask for, for instance if the information includes personal information about another person.

In some circumstances, you may request the data we process based on consent or to perform our contract with you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format or to request we transfer such personal data to another party. Your rights are subject to exemptions under applicable data privacy laws.

If you wish for us to transfer the personal data to another party, please ensure you detail that party and note that we can only do so where it is technically feasible. We are not responsible for the security of the personal data or its processing once received by the third party.

We also may not provide you with certain data if providing it would interfere with another’s rights (e.g. where providing the personal data we hold about you would reveal information about another person or our trade secrets or intellectual property) as permitted under applicable data protection rights.

### C. Correction

You have the right to correct any Personal Data we have that is inaccurate. Where you request correction, please explain in detail why you believe the Personal Data we hold about you to be inaccurate or incomplete so that we can assess whether a correction is required.

### D. Restriction of processing to storage only

You have a right to require us to stop processing the Personal Data we hold about you other than for storage purposes in certain circumstances, e.g. while we are considering whether it should be corrected or deleted or, based on your objection, whether we should permanently stop processing. Please note, however, that if we stop processing the Personal Data, we may use it again if there are valid grounds for us to do so (e.g. for the defense of legal claims or for another’s protection).

### E. Objection

You have the right to object to our processing of data about you other than where required to perform under our Terms of Service.

You also have the right to object to our processing of data about you by emailing us at [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) if we are processing the data we hold about you on the basis of our legitimate interest and you object to such processing. Please provide us with detail as to your reasoning so that we can assess whether there is a compelling overriding interest in us continuing to process such data or we need to process it in relation to legal claims.

### F. Complaints

If you wish to make a complaint about how we process your Personal Data, please contact us at [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) and we will endeavor to respond to your concerns. This is without prejudice to your right to launch a claim with the data protection supervisory authority in the EU country in which you live or work where you think we have infringed data protection laws.

XII. Your California privacy rights.
------------------------------------

Effective January 1, 2020, if you are a California resident, and upon your verifiable consumer request, you have the rights listed below (however, these rights are subject to certain exceptions permitted by law):

* Information. You can request the following information about how we have collected and used your Personal Information during the past 12 months: the categories of “Personal Information” (as contemplated by the CCPA) that we have collected; the categories of sources from which we collected Personal Information; the business or commercial purpose for collecting and/or selling Personal Information; the categories of third parties with whom we share Personal of information so that we can provide our Services to you. If you ask us to delete some or all of your information, you may no longer be able to access or use the Services.
* Nondiscrimination. You are entitled to exercise the rights described above free from discriminatory practices prohibited by California law.

Exercising your rights. You may exercise your California privacy rights described above by emailing us at [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com), or the in-game contact methods from time to time. We will need to confirm your identity and California residency to process your requests to exercise your information, access or deletion rights. We cannot process your request if you do not provide us with reasonably sufficient detail to allow us to understand and respond to it.

Response Timing. We aim to respond to a consumer request for access or deletion within 45 days of receiving that request. If we require more time, we will inform you of the reason and extension in writing.

Personal Information that we collect, use and share. We describe the sources from which we collect Personal Information and the business and commercial purposes for which we collect this information in this Privacy Policy above.

We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties. We do share Personal Information with third parties for the business and commercial purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including without limitation advertising and marketing of our Services.

XIII. Updates to Our Privacy Policy
-----------------------------------

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy to maintain our commitment to privacy. Updates apply going forward, and never retroactively. When we make changes, we will update the date at the top of this page and make reasonable efforts to notify you if the changes are material. We encourage you to visit this page frequently to keep current with any changes.

We will provide an individual opt-out or opt-in choice before we share your data with third parties other than our agents, or before we use it for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized. To request to limit the use and disclosure of your Personal Data, please submit a written request to [privacy@kixeye.com.](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)

[](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)XIV. Contact Us
--------------------------------------------

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may email us at [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). If you wish to contact our Data Protection Officer, you may email us at [dpo@kixeye.com](mailto:dpo@kixeye.com)

KIXEYE公司隐私政策
============

上次更新时间：2023年6月23日

I. 介绍我们的隐私政策
------------

KIXEYE公司（以下称“我们”或“KIXEYE”）热衷于游戏。而且我们非常重视您的隐私和数据权。我们致力于与您保持信任和透明的关系。本隐私政策以通俗易懂的语言编写，以便于理解在您访问我们的网站、移动应用程序、游戏、论坛或其它服务（统称为“服务”）时，我们如何收集、使用、存储和共享可识别您的身份的信息（“个人数据”在上下文中也可指2018年《加利福尼亚州消费者隐私保护法》和/或《欧盟一般数据保护条例》中规定的“个人信息”）。在使用服务时，您同意本隐私政策中描述的信息的收集、使用和披露（包括记录和追踪）。请仔细阅读。如果您不同意本隐私政策，请不要使用任何服务。

II. 我们收集什么信息/个人数据？
------------------

### A. 您直接提供给我们的信息。

在您与KIXEYE拥有的网站交互，或从第三方应用商店下载服务时，我们会按如下所述直接从您那里收集和存储信息（在我们能获得的范围内）。我们收集您提供给我们的信息，这些信息可能包括您的：

* 姓名
* 电子邮件地址
* KIXEYE帐户信息，如唯一用户名、ID或头像
* 您来自各种“社交网络”的ID（包括Facebook、Apple iTunes、Google Play、Steam等）
* 我们还可能让您可以完成其他服务用户可见的用户个人资料。您的用户个人资料可能包括：个人资料图像；一个或多个服务用户名；以及由KIXEYE创建用来识别您的个人资料的KIXEYE用户ID号。
* 付款或帐单信息
* 您给我们或本服务发送的消息（聊天记录、客户支持请求）
* 有助于我们确认您的身份、防止欺诈，开发并改进服务的信息

### B. 自动收集的信息。

在您使用我们的服务时，我们会通过cookie和其它方式（SDK、追踪像素等）自动从您的设备收集其它信息，（在可用范围内，以及在需要时，经您同意）这包括：

* IP地址
* 常规位置数据 设备信息（如设备类型、型号、操作系统、浏览器版本或用于检查设备兼容性的设备唯一标识符，以及IDFA或GAID）
* IDFA是指苹果上的广告商标识符，GAID是指谷歌广告标识。这些唯一标识符是非永久、非个人的，这意味着它们不包含有关您的敏感信息，但有助于所有应用之间的一致性和跨应用追踪。您可以通过更新设备上的设置来选择不共享设备标识符。
* 服务通信（游戏内消息、聊天记录）
* 连接类型

### C. 第三方提供给我们的信息。

通过您使用第三方的服务、网站、应用程序或其它服务，我们可能会获得第三方（包括社交网络）从您那里收集的某些信息的访问权限。

### D. 我们收集的有关您的帐户的信息。

我们会创建类似于帐号的标识符并将其分配给您的设备。我们还会在可用的范围内基于您的同意（如果需要）收集有关您的以下信息：

* 游戏用户名；
* 设备类型；型号；操作系统；内存；存储；
* 电话号码；
* 国家，地区，城市；
* 用户名，角色名称；
* 语言；
* 电子邮件地址；以及
* 您的联系人，使您可以邀请好友跟您一起享用服务。

在您使用我们的服务时，我们会收集有关您使用服务以及与之交互的方式的信息，例如您的设备登录我们的游戏的时间和时长，您访问的游戏功能以及与您互动的其他玩家，您进行的应用内购买，进度或达到的等级，以及其它游戏活动。

我们还收集有关您与服务交互的匿名使用统计数据。通常通过使用服务器日志文件或Web日志文件来收集该信息，用移动设备软件开发包和追踪技术（例如浏览器cookie）来收集和分析某些类型的技术信息。服务置于您的计算机上的一些cookie与您的用户ID号关联。

### E. 通过您参与社区活动收集的信息

在使用服务时，您将可以访问服务内的在线游戏社区，这使您不仅能与我们也能与服务的其他用户交流或共享信息，方法如下：

* 参与玩家论坛和留言板；
* 向其他用户的个人资料或游戏板发表公开评论；
* 向其他用户发送私信或邀请，直接在我们的网站上或向其电子邮件帐号发送；
* 与其他用户聊天；以及
* 发布网页链接。

在您参与在线游戏社区时，我们会访问和存储有关您的信息/个人数据。我们存储的信息因游戏/应用程序而异，并受您和您的好友在该游戏/应用程序中进行的隐私设置影响。您可以在应用程序中控制和了解有关这些设置的更多信息。我们会收集以下信息：

* 您的服务内用户名；
* 您的设备广告商ID；
* 取决于您登录服务的方式，Facebook用户ID；
* 接入设备的IP地址；
* 您在游戏中的聊天和消息；以及
* 您的电子邮件地址和电话号码（如果您提供了）。
* 提交的头像

### F. 付款信息

我们还会收集一些购买信息（包括交易历史记录、您购买的商品、价格和日期）。请注意，您的游戏内和/或应用内购买交易由第三方支付平台处理，例如Apple（在iOS设备上的购买）、Google（在Android设备上的购买）。这些第三方支付平台是您购买的商品的“记录商家”，不与我们共享您的财务信息，例如信用卡号码。

### G. 客户支持通信

在您向我们的客户支持团队寻求帮助时，我们会收集和存储：

* 您的姓名和电子邮件地址；
* 有关您在服务中的活动的信息；
* 您的用户名或ID号；以及
* 与向您提供的帮助有关的任何通信

### H. 我们从不收集的信息。

我们不向您收集或收集关于您的任何“特殊类别”的信息。即关于族裔、性行为或性取向、政治观点、宗教或哲学信仰、工会成员资格或健康数据等的种族数据或信息。

III. 我们如何以及为什么使用这些信息/个人数据？
--------------------------

我们使用您的个人数据和非个人信息，以便：

### A. 为您提供服务。

* 根据您的喜好和我们的服务条款与您沟通。
* 运营、开发、维护和改进我们的服务。
* 为服务提供客户支持。
* 解决纠纷并执行我们的服务条款。
* 向您提供特别/促销性游戏内优惠
* 收取与服务相关的费用、付款和其它应付款项。
* 使您能与其他玩家联系。
* 创建用户帐户以使用服务。
* 为您提供适当版本的服务，包括以您的首选语言。
* 确定、修复并解决漏洞和服务错误。
* 开发新的服务。

### B. 确保我们的服务安全。

* 确定和/或防止欺诈。
* 确定和/或防止违反服务条款、非法活动或欺骗。
* 验证用户身份，以进行客户支持通信。
* 监控、确保和增强我们网络和信息系统的安全性。

### C. 个性化我们的服务或提供促销活动。

* 为您提供通知、个性化的游戏体验，以及其它产品和服务。
* 就您感兴趣的领域与您沟通，并回应您的要求。
* 服务、优化并衡量我们的营销活动的有效性。
* 对内部营销和人口统计研究进行分析，以开发、改进或个性化服务。
* 保存、追踪您的游戏属性、进度和统计资料。

### D. 法律/其它。

我们还使用您的个人数据和非个人信息，以便：

* 遵守法律义务。
* 行使、确立或捍卫我们的服务条款和其它合法权利。
* 在我们有足够理由相信有必要保护您、我们或任何其他人的安全、财务或重要利益的情况下。

IV. 我们与谁共享这些信息/个人数据？
--------------------

除以下所述外，未经您的同意，我们不会与无从属关系的第三方共享您的个人数据。但根据本隐私政策，我们可能会共享非个人数据，包括匿名、聚合或化名数据。在以下情况下，我们可能会与第三方共享您的信息（包括个人数据）：

### A. 第三方服务提供商。

我们可能会与第三方签订合同，代表我们收集或处理您的信息或个人数据，以提供服务，例如托管提供商，以存储您提供的个人数据、提供灾难恢复服务，以及履行我们与您、电子邮件发送服务和分析公司（信用卡交易处理、发送客户服务电子邮件）签订的任何合同。我们与此类第三方的协议要求他们根据本隐私政策保护您的个人数据和信息的保密性和安全性。我们不会与任何第三方共享个人数据，以便他们可以未经您的同意向您营销。

### B. KIXEYE附属公司。

我们隶属于StillFront AB集团公司。我们可能会在我们的子公司、母公司或附属公司之间共享您的信息，以提供和/或改进我们的服务，并为您提供个性化体验以及产品和服务。

### C. 继任者或收购第三方。

如果KIXEYE与第三方合并、被收购、购买（全部或部分）、发生剥离、重组、破产或类似事件，则根据本隐私政策收集的信息可与此类第三方共享。如果发生这种情况，我们会通知您。

### D. 根据法律规定。

如果有足够理由相信我们有义务这样做，我们可能会披露个人数据，以便：

* 遵守法律义务。
* 保护和捍卫KIXEYE、服务用户或他人的权利或财产。
* 保护服务用户或公众的人身安全、财务或重要利益。
* 避免法律责任。
* 监控对我们的服务条款、政策或论坛/社区规则的遵守和执行情况。
* 响应政府当局的合法要求，包括国家安全或执法机构。

V. 我们如何存储和保护您的个人数据？
-------------------

### A. 保护您的个人数据。

我们采取合理的安全措施来保护您的在线和离线信息的安全，并致力于保护客户/用户信息。尽管我们采取合理的预防措施来防范我们的服务以及客户数据库和记录的潜在安全入侵，但我们不能保证绝对不会发生未经授权的访问、黑客攻击、数据丢失或其它入侵。不幸的是，通过互联网传输信息从来都不是绝对安全的。尽管我们努力保护您的个人数据，但我们无法保证您的数据在传输到我们网站时的安全性；因此，任何传输均由您自担风险。我们敦促您采取措施以确保个人信息（包括帐户密码）的安全，并在使用后注销帐户。如果您的帐户被黑客入侵，可能会导致未经授权访问您的帐户，因此请确保您的帐户信息安全。

### B. 存储您的个人数据。

我们收集、与我们共享或根据本隐私政策处理的个人数据可能会存储在美国，或我们、我们的子公司/附属机构或第三方服务提供商运营的任何其它国家，包括通过使用云存储。使用本服务，则您同意将您的个人数据和非个人数据传输到美国和其它国家，这些国家可能无法提供与您的居住国或国籍国法律同等程度的隐私保护。因此，根据适用的当地法律，外国政府机构或其它机构可能会访问您的信息。

VI. 您的隐私控制
----------

您可以控制个人数据的收集和使用。您可以随时访问或更正您的个人数据，限制收集或处理您的个人数据，并在某些情况下，要求停用或永久删除您的个人数据。若要求访问、更正、限制、停用或删除您的个人数据，请通过[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)与我们联系。在处理任何要求之前，我们可能会要求您验证身份以保护您的隐私。这可能包括通过服务平台或其它身份验证方法通信。

未经核实、不合理或不切实际的要求可能会被拒绝。为了保护您的帐户，要求停用或删除个人数据需要进一步的验证，这可能包括暂时中止您的帐户和本服务。处理停用或删除请求后，这些操作是永久性的，个人数据和帐户将无法恢复。

VII. 13岁以下儿童
------------

我们的服务不针对或旨在吸引13岁以下儿童。我们不会有意收集13岁以下儿童的个人数据、个人信息、照片、视频、音频文件或位置数据，也不有意使用持久标识符识别不同时间、跨不同网站或在线服务的13岁以下儿童。如果您未满13岁，请不要使用我们的服务，也不要向我们提交任何信息。我们建议家长和法定监护人监控孩子的互联网使用情况，并指示13岁以下的孩子不要使用我们的服务，以帮助执行本隐私政策。如果您有理由相信13岁以下的儿童通过我们的服务向KIXEYE提供了个人数据或个人信息，请通过[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)联系我们，我们会尽快采取措施从数据库中删除该信息。

VIII. 第三方隐私政策和实践/社交网络
---------------------

本隐私政策仅适用于KIXEYE通过您使用我们的服务收集的个人数据和信息。在使用我们的服务时，可通过链接访问第三方网站，或者您可能通过第三方网站接触到、访问、下载我们的服务。这些第三方网站受其各自的隐私政策规范，对于出现在这些网站上的任何内容或这些网站的任何隐私或安全实践，我们概不负责。要管理KIXEYE从您使用我们服务的社交网络收到的有关您的信息，您需要按照该网站上的说明更新信息并更改隐私设置。Apple应用程序的隐私管理工具在[http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/)可见。Google的隐私管理工具在[https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/)可见。您可以通过前往（移动）设备的设置并查看每个应用程序的权限来管理信息收集和使用的某些方面。

在KIXEYE从社交网络收到您的信息后，KIXEYE会根据本隐私政策存储和使用该信息，您可以按如下所述访问和更新该信息。在用户要求删除或停用信息之前，在KIXEYE创建的帐户视为有效。

IX. 数据保留/删除要求的影响
----------------

我们尽量只保留必要的个人数据。在本隐私政策下，当不再需要个人数据时我们会定期将其删除或去识别化。如果删除或去识别化个人数据在商业上不合理，我们会不处理并安全存储您的个人数据，直到能将其永久删除。请注意，我们可能会保留法律和会计目的所需的信息，以解决纠纷，执行我们的用户协议，保护我们的合法权利，并遵守技术和法律要求和限制。例如，我们可能会保留有关付款或客户服务事项的记录。如果您在服务上发送或发布了内容，我们可能无法将其删除。有效删除可能需要您采取措施，例如从您的设备中删除与服务相关的应用和/或内容，以及/或从您的社交网络帐户取消与服务的关联。请注意，如果您要求我们删除您的帐户，您在游戏中的所有进度和任何未使用的虚拟物品会永远丢失。请注意，即使您的帐户和/或个人数据已从游戏中删除或取消关联，游戏中的结果和构件（例如基地、角色、舰船、补给等）可能仍在游戏中有效（并受游戏影响，即被活跃玩家破坏或利用）。

X. 欧洲国家用户的法律依据
--------------

如果您位于欧盟、欧洲经济区或瑞士的某个国家，以下是我们处理您的信息时所依照的法律依据。

* 合同必要性。这包括我们为了向您提供您要求（并且我们同意）向您提供的服务而使用的数据，例如我们的游戏、客户服务和聊天功能；
* 法律义务。这包括我们为遵守法律义务而使用的数据，例如保留与税务有关的记录或对索要某些数据的合理法律要求作出回应；
* 合法权益。这包括我们为您使用服务时可以合理预期（并且我们认为不会对您的隐私造成伤害）的目的而使用的数据，例如用来了解用户如何浏览我们的网站和应用，确保我们的网站和应用安全，研究和优化我们的服务，提供更加个性化的体验、营销和广告的分析；以及

同意。在我们基于您的同意处理数据的情况下，我们会征求您的明确同意。您可以随时撤回同意，但这不会影响在撤回之前处理您的个人数据的合法性。

尽管您可以随时按照本隐私政策中所述的方式撤回同意或反对某些类型的处理，但请注意，如果您在提出此类要求之后继续使用服务，我们会重新开始收集有关您的个人数据，并按照本隐私政策的其它说明处理数据。如果您不希望我们收集有关您的任何个人数据，则应停止所有游戏活动并停止使用我们的服务。

XI. 欧洲国家用户的权利
-------------

如果您位于欧盟、欧洲经济区或瑞士的某个国家，则您对我们持有的关于您的个人数据享有某些权利，我们会在以下对此进行详细说明，并且根据适用的数据隐私法，这些权利可免除。其中一些仅在某些情况下适用，详见下文。我们还阐明了如何行使这些权利。请注意，我们可能会在回应任何行使权利的要求之前请您验证身份。我们会对您提出的行使这些权利的要求作出回应，不会无故拖延，并会在至少一个月内回应（尽管在某些情况下可能会再延长两个月）。要行使您的任何权利，请发送电子邮件至[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)。

在某些情况下，我们可能会拒绝处理要求，例如明显无根据或过分的要求，或危害他人隐私的要求。

### A. 删除您的个人数据

在某些情况下，您可能会要求我们删除所持有的有关您的一些个人数据。如果您希望删除个人数据，请通过[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)联系我们。

请注意，要处理您的要求并确保删除，您必须从移动设备上删除我们的应用/游戏，并从玩过我们游戏的任何设备上清除我们的cookie。您还必须删除社交网络帐户中的所有服务功能链接。在我们删除任何信息时，该信息会从我们的活动数据库中删除，但可能会保留在我们的存档中。但请注意，我们仍可能出于其它目的保留部分或全部信息，例如用于保留财务记录，保护或行使合法权利，维护营销限制清单或出于技术原因，例如维护技术安全性或我们的数据库完整性。我们也可能以匿名形式保留您的信息。有关删除要求的更多信息，请参阅以上“删除对数据保留的影响”。

### B 访问和可移植性

您有权知道我们掌握有关您的哪些信息，并且在某些情况下，有权让我们将信息发送给您。如果您希望行使该权利，请通过[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)联系我们，并告知我们您希望行使访问权以及您所要求的具体信息。请注意，我们可能无法提供您要求的所有信息，例如，如果该信息包含有关他人的个人信息。

在某些情况下，您可能会索要我们基于同意处理的数据，或以结构化、常用且机器可读的格式履行与您的合同，或要求我们将此类个人数据传输给另一方。根据适用的数据隐私法，您的权利可免除。

如果您希望我们将个人数据传输给另一方，请确保详细说明该方，并请注意，我们只能在技术上可行的情况下这样做。我们对第三方收到的个人数据或其处理的安全性概不负责。

如果提供某些数据会妨碍适用数据保护权允许的其它权利（例如，提供我们持有的关于您的个人数据会泄露有关他人或我们的商业秘密或知识产权的信息），我们也可能不会向您提供。

### C. 更正

您有权更正我们掌握的任何不准确的个人数据。如果您要求更正，请详细说明为什么您认为我们持有的关于您的个人数据不正确或不完整，以便我们评估是否需要更正。

### D. 仅限于存储处理

在某些情况下，您有权要求我们停止出于存储之外的目的处理我们持有的有关您的个人数据，例如在我们考虑是否应更正或删除数据时，或根据您的异议，我们是否应永久停止处理这些数据。但请注意，如果我们停止处理个人数据，在有正当理由的情况下，我们可能会再次使用这些数据（例如，为索赔辩护或其它保护）。

### E. 异议

除根据服务条款要求处理的情况之外，您有权反对我们处理有关您的数据。

如果我们基于合法利益处理我们持有的有关您的数据，但您反对此类处理，那么您也有权通过发送电子邮件至[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)对我们处理有关您的数据提出异议。请向我们提供有关您的理由的详细信息，以便我们评估继续处理此类数据是否有令人信服的压倒性权益，或我们是否需要就索赔处理该数据。

### F. 投诉

如果您希望对我们处理您的个人数据的方式提出投诉，请通过[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)联系我们，我们会尽力回应您的关切。如果您认为我们违反了数据保护法，这不影响您向居住或工作所在地的欧盟国家的数据保护监管机构提出索赔的权利。

XII. 您的加利福尼亚州隐私权。
-----------------

自2020年1月1日起，如果您是加利福尼亚州居民，并且应可核实的消费者要求，您具有下列权利（但这些权利受法律允许的某些例外约束）：

* 信息。您可以要求提供有关我们在过去12个月内如何收集和使用您的个人信息的以下信息：我们收集的“个人信息”的类别（根据CCPA的预期）；我们收集个人信息的来源的类别；收集和/或出售个人信息的业务或商业目的；我们与之共享个人信息以便向您提供服务的第三方的类别。如果您要求我们删除部分或全部信息，则可能无法再访问或使用服务。
* 不歧视。您有权在不受加利福尼亚州法律禁止的歧视性行为影响下行使上述权利。

行使您的权利。您可以通过发送电子邮件至[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)，或有时可通过游戏内联系方式行使上述加利福尼亚州隐私权。我们需要确认您的身份和加利福尼亚州居民身份，以处理您行使信息、访问或删除权利的要求。如果您不向我们提供足够的详细信息，使我们能了解和响应要求，则我们无法处理您的要求。

响应时间。我们致力于在收到消费者的访问或删除要求后45日内响应。如果需要更多时间，我们会书面通知您原因和延长期限。

我们收集、使用和共享的个人信息。我们在上述隐私政策中说明收集个人信息的来源，以及收集该信息的业务和商业目的。

我们不会将您的个人信息出售给第三方。我们的确出于本隐私政策中所述的业务和商业目的与第三方共享个人信息，包括但不限于服务的广告和营销。

XIII. 隐私政策更新
------------

我们可能会不时更新本隐私政策，以保持我们对隐私的承诺。更新适用于将来，从不具有追溯性。在进行更改时，我们会更新该页面顶部的日期，如果有重大更改我们会尽合理的努力通知您。我们建议您经常访问该页面，以便随时了解任何更改。

在与代理以外的第三方共享您的数据，或将其用于最初收集或随后授权的用途之外前，我们会提供单独的选择退出或选择加入选项。若要求限制使用和披露您的个人数据，请向[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)提交书面要求。

XIV. 联系我们
---------

如果您对本隐私政策有任何疑问，请发送电子邮件至[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)。如果您希望联系我们的数据保护专员，请发送电子邮件至[dpo@kixeye.com](mailto:dpo@kixeye.com)。

KIXEYE Inc.隱私政策
===============

上次更新時間：2023年6月23日

一、我們的隱私政策介紹
-----------

KIXEYE Inc.（下稱「我們」或「KIXEYE」）是遊戲相關產業。我們也嚴正對待您的隱私和資料權利。我們致力於與您保持信任和透明的關係。本隱私政策以通俗易懂的文字編寫而成，使您易於理解當您訪問我們的網站、行動應用程式、遊戲、論壇或其他服務（統稱「服務」）時如何收集、使用、存儲和分享您的可識別資訊（「個人資料」，當上下文表明時，個人資料也可指個人資訊；如同《2018年加州消費者隱私保護法》和/或《歐盟一般資料保護規範》中所規定的）。在您使用服務時，您同意本隱私政策中所述的每一項資訊收集、使用和披露（包括記錄和追蹤）。請仔細檢閱。如果您不同意本隱私政策，請不要使用任何服務。

二、我們會收集哪些資訊/個人資料？
-----------------

### A. 您直接向我們提供的資訊。

當您與KIXEYE擁有的網站進行互動，或從第三方應用商店下載服務時，我們將按照下文所述直接收集和儲存您的資訊，但僅限於我們可以獲得的範圍。我們收集您提供給我們的資訊，而這些資訊可能包括您的：

* 姓名
* 電子郵件地址
* KIXEYE帳號資訊，如獨特的使用者名稱、ID或頭像
* 您來自各種「社交網路」（包括Facebook、Apple iTunes、Google Play、Steam等）的ID
* 我們還可能為您提供選擇，讓您完成一個其他服務使用者可見的使用者檔案。您的使用者資料可能包括：個人資料圖片；一個或多個服務使用者名稱；以及一個由KIXEYE創建並用於識別您個人資料的KIXEYE使用者ID。
* 付款或帳單資訊
* 您給我們或服務的訊息（聊天記錄、客戶支援請求）
* 幫助我們確認您為本人的資訊，以防止欺詐，發展並改善我們的服務

### B. 自動收集的資訊。

當您使用我們的服務時，包括在可利用的範圍內以及有需要時，經您同意的情況下，我們會通過Cookie和其他方式（SDK、追蹤圖元等）從您的裝置上自動收集其他資訊：

* IP位址
* 一般位置資料裝置資訊（如裝置類型、型號、作業系統、瀏覽器版本，或用於檢查裝置相容性和IDFA或GAID的唯一裝置標識符）
* IDFA指的是Apple的廣告商標識符，GAID指的是Google廣告身份。這些獨一無二的標識碼是非永久性和非個人的，這代表它們不包含關於您的敏感資訊，但確實允許在所有應用程式之間保持一致和跨應用程式追蹤。您可以透過更新裝置上的設置，選擇不分享您的裝置標識符。
* 服務通訊（遊戲內訊息、聊天紀錄）
* 連接類型

### C. 第三方提供給我們的資訊。

我們可能會透過您使用第三方的服務、網站、應用程式或其他服務，包括社交網路，來獲取第三方收集的某些資訊。

### D. 我們收集的有關您帳號的資訊。

我們將為您的裝置創建並分配一個類似於帳號的識別碼。如有需要，基於您同意的情況下，我們還將在可獲得的範圍內收集關於您的以下資訊：

* 遊戲使用者名稱；
* 裝置類型；型號；操作系統；記憶體；儲存空間；
* 電話號碼；
* 國家、地區、城市；
* 使用者名稱、角色名稱；
* 語言；
* 電子郵件地址；和
* 您的連絡人，使您能夠邀請朋友加入您的服務。

當您使用我們的服務時，我們將收集有關您使用服務並與我們的服務進行互動的方式的相關資訊，例如您的裝置何時以及在多長時間內登入我們的遊戲，您訪問的遊戲功能以及您與其他玩家之間的互動，您進行的應用內購買，您取得的進度或等級，以及其他遊戲活動。

我們還會收集有關您與本服務互動的假名使用統計數據。 這些資訊通常是透過使用伺服器日誌檔或網路紀錄檔、行動裝置軟體開發工具組和瀏覽器Cookie等追蹤技術來收集和分析某些類型的技術資訊。本服務在您的電腦上放置的一些Cookie與您的使用者ID相關聯。

### E. 透過參與社區活動收集到的資訊

當您使用服務時，即可進入服務內的線上遊戲社群，讓您不僅有機會可以與我們交流或分享資訊，還能透過以下方式與服務的其他使用者交流：

* 參與玩家論壇和留言板；
* 對其他使用者個人檔案或遊戲板發表公開評論；
* 直接在我們的網站或他們的電子郵件帳號上向其他使用者發送私人訊息或邀請；
* 與其他使用者聊天；和
* 張貼網路連結。

當您參與線上遊戲社群時，我們會存取並儲存有關您的資訊/個人資料。我們儲存的資訊因遊戲/應用程式而異，並受您和您的朋友在該遊戲/應用程式中建立的隱私設置的影響。您可以在應用程式中控制並瞭解更多關於這些設置的資訊。我們將收集以下資訊：

* 您與服務連結的使用者名稱；
* 您的裝置廣告商ID；
* 根據您登入服務的方式，Facebook使用者ID；
* 您存取裝置的IP位址；
* 您在遊戲中的聊天內容與訊息；和
* 若您提供，您的電子郵件地址和電話號碼。
* 提交的頭像

### F. 付款資訊

我們也會收集一些購買資訊（包括交易記錄，您購買的內容、價格和日期）。請注意，您的遊戲內和/或程式內購買交易由第三方支付處理商處理，如Apple（適用於iOS裝飾上的購買）、Google（適用於Android裝置上的購買）。這些第三方支付處理商是您購買的記錄商號，不會與我們分享您的財務資訊，如信用卡號碼。

### G. 客服通聯

當您向我們的客戶支援團隊尋求協助時，我們將收集並存取以下內容：

* 您的姓名和電子郵件地址；
* 您在服務上的活動資訊；
* 您的使用者名稱或ID號碼；和
* 任何與向您提供的協助有關的通聯記錄

### H. 我們絕不會收集的資訊。

我們不會向您收集任何關於您的「特殊類別的資訊」。即種族資料或有關民族血統、性行為或性取向、政治觀點、宗教或哲學信仰、工會會員資格或健康資料的資訊等。

三、我們如何以及為什麼使用這些資訊/個人資料？
-----------------------

我們使用您的個人資料和非個人資訊來：

### A. 為您提供我們的服務。

* 根據您的喜好和我們的服務條款與您溝通。
* 營運、開發、維護和改進我們的服務。
* 為客戶提供服務支援。
* 解決爭議並執行我們的服務條款。
* 為您提供遊戲中的特別/促銷優惠
* 收取與服務有關的費用、款項和其他應付款。
* 使您能夠與其他玩家連接。
* 創建一個使用者帳號來使用服務。
* 向您提供適當的服務版本，包括以您喜歡的語言提供。
* 識別、修復和排除小故障與服務錯誤。
* 開發新服務。

### B. 確保我們的服務。

* 識別和/或防止欺詐行為。
* 識別和/或防止違反服務條款的行為、非法活動或作弊。
* 驗證使用者身份，以便用於客戶支援通訊。
* 監控、確保並強化網路和資訊系統的安全性。

### C. 個人化服務或優惠活動。

* 為您提供通知、個人化的遊戲體驗等其他優惠。
* 就您感興趣的方面與您溝通，並對您的要求作出回應。
* 提供、改善並衡量我們行銷活動的效果。
* 為內部行銷和人口統計研究進行分析，以發展、改善服務或加以個人化。
* 儲存、追蹤您的遊戲屬性、進度和統計數值。

### D. 法律/其他。

我們也使用您的個人資料和非個人資訊來：

* 遵守法律義務。
* 行使、確立或維護我們的服務條款和其他法律權利。
* 我們堅信需要保護您、我們或任何其他人的安全、財務或重要利益的情況。

四、我們與誰共享這些資訊/個人資料？
------------------

除下文所述者外，未經您的同意，我們不會與非相關第三方共用您的個人資料。但是，我們可能會根據本隱私政策分享非個人資料，包括匿名、匯總或假名資料。我們可能在以下情況下與第三方共用您的資訊，包括個人資料：

### A. 第三方服務供應商。

我們可能會與第三方簽訂合約，代表我們收集或處理您的資訊或個人資料以便提供服務，如虛擬主機供應商，用以儲存您提供的個人資料，並提供災難恢復服務，以及執行我們與您簽訂的任何合約，電子郵件發送服務和分析公司（信用卡處理、發送客戶服務電子郵件）。我們與這些第三方簽訂的協定要求他們根據本隱私政策保護您的個人資料和資訊的保密性及安全性。未經您的同意，我們不會與任何第三方分享您的個人資料，以便他們向您進行行銷。

### B. KIXEYE關聯公司。

我們是StillFront AB公司集團的一部分。我們可能會在我們的子公司、母公司或關聯公司之間共用您的資訊，以便提供和/或改進我們的服務，並為您提供個人化的體驗和優惠。

### C. 繼承人或收購第三方。

如果KIXEYE與第三方合併、被收購、被購買（全部或部分）、經歷撤資、重組、破產或類似事件，根據本隱私政策收集的資訊可能會與該第三方共用。如果發生這種情況，我們將會通知您。

### D. 根據法律規定。

如果我們基於誠信認為有義務這樣做，可能會依下列原因披露個人資料：

* 遵守法律義務。
* 保障及捍衛KIXEYE、服務使用者或其他人的權利或財產。
* 保障本服務的消費者或公眾的人身安全、財務或重要利益。
* 防範法律責任。
* 監控我們的服務條款、政策或論壇/社群規則的執行情況。
* 對政府當局的合法要求作出回應，包括國家安全或執法機構要求。

五、我們如何存儲和保護您的個人資料？
------------------

### A. 保護您的個人資料。

我們採取合理的安全措施來保護您的線上和離線資訊的安全，並致力於保護客戶/使用者資訊。雖然我們採取了合理的預防措施，以防止我們的服務和客戶資料庫和記錄可能出現的安全漏洞，但我們不能保證未經授權的訪問、駭客攻擊、資料遺失或其他漏洞永遠不會發生。遺憾的是，網路上的資訊傳輸永遠無法百分百安全。雖然我們努力保護您的個人資料，但無法保證您的資料在傳輸到我們網站過程中的安全，因此任何傳輸都需要您自己承擔風險。我們強烈建議您採取措施保護您的個人資訊安全（包括您的帳號密碼），並在使用後登出您的帳號。如果您的帳號被駭客攻擊，可能導致您的帳號遭受未經授權的訪問，所以請您妥善保管自己的帳號資訊。

### B. 儲存您的個人資料。

我們收集的、與我們共用的或根據本隱私政策處理的個人資料可能會儲存在美國或我們、我們的子公司/關聯公司或第三方服務供應商營運的任何其他國家，包括使用雲端存儲。透過使用本服務，您同意將您的個人資料和非個人資料轉移到美國和其他國家，這些國家的隱私保護水準可能與您的居住國或國籍國的法律不同。因此，您的資訊可能會被外國政府當局存取，或根據適用的當地法律以其他方式存取。

六、您的隱私控管
--------

您可以控制您個人資料的收集和使用。您能隨時訪問或更正、限制收集或處理您的個人資料，並在某些情況下要求停用或永久刪除您的個人資料。若想要進行訪問、更正、限制、停用或刪除您的個人資料，請聯絡我們：[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)。在我們處理任何請求之前，我們可能會要求您驗證您的身份以保護您的隱私。這可能包括透過服務平台或其他身份驗證方法進行溝通。

未經證實、不合理或不切實際的請求可能會被拒絕。為了保護您的帳號，停用或刪除個人資料的請求需要額外的驗證，這可能包括暫時中止您的帳號和服務。一旦處理停用或刪除的請求之後，這些請求將成為永久性的，且無法恢復個人資料和帳號。

七、13歲以下兒童
---------

我們的服務並非針對13歲以下兒童，也不是為了吸引13歲以下兒童。我們不會故意收集13歲以下兒童的個人資料、照片、視頻、音訊檔或位置資料，也不會故意在不同的網站或線上服務中使用持久性識別器來辨識13歲以下兒童。如果您未滿13歲，請勿使用我們的服務，也不要向我們提交任何資訊。我們鼓勵父母和法定監護人監督其子女的網路使用方式，並指示其13歲以下的子女不要使用我們的服務來協助執行本隱私政策。如果您有理由相信13歲以下的兒童藉由我們的服務向KIXEYE提供了個人資料或個人資訊，請與我們聯絡：[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)，我們將儘快採取措施從我們的資料庫中刪除該資訊。

八、第三方隱私政策與實踐/社交網路
-----------------

本隱私政策僅適用於KIXEYE透過您使用我們的服務而收集的個人資料和資訊。使用我們的服務時，可能會藉由連結進入第三方網站，或者您可能已經透過第三方網站前往、存取、下載了我們的服務。這些第三方網站受其自身的隱私政策管轄，我們對這些網站上出現的任何內容或這些網站的任何隱私或安全慣例不承擔任何責任。為了管理您從使用我們服務的社交網路收到的關於您的資訊，您必須按照該網站的指示更新您的資訊並變更您的隱私設置。Apple適用的隱私管理工具可以在[http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/找到](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/)。Google的隱私管理工具可在 [https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/)找到。您可以前往您（行動）裝置的設定查看每項應用程式的許可權來管理某部份的資訊收集和使用。

一旦KIXEYE從社交網路接收到您的資訊，KIXEYE將根據本隱私政策存儲和使用該資訊，您可以存取和更新以下所述的資訊。在KIXEYE創建的帳號被視為活躍帳號，直到我們收到使用者要求刪除或停用該帳號為止。

九、資料保留/刪除請求的影響
--------------

我們盡量只會保留必要的個人資料。當本隱私政策不再需要個人資料時，我們會定期刪除或解除其身份識別。從商業角度看，刪除或去識別您的個人資料並不合理時，我們將依程序刪除您的個人資料，並將其安全儲存，直到我們能夠永久刪除該資料為止。請注意，我們可能會保留用於法律和會計目的的資訊，以便解決糾紛，執行我們的使用者協定，保護我們的合法權利，並遵守技術和法律要求及限制。例如，我們可能會保留有關付款或客戶服務事項的記錄。如果您已經在本服務上發送或張貼了內容，我們可能無法加以刪除。有效刪除可能需要您採取一些行動，例如從您的裝置上刪除與本服務相關的應用程式和/或內容，以及/或從您的社交網路帳號中刪除本服務的連結。請注意，如果您要求我們刪除您的帳號，您將永久失去在遊戲中的所有進度和任何未使用的虛擬物品都。另請注意，即使在您的帳號和/或個人資料被刪除或與遊戲中斷連結後，您在遊戲中的遊戲結果和人工製品，如基地、角色、船隻、補給品等，仍可能留在遊戲中（並受遊戲影響，即被活躍的玩家破壞或利用）。

X. 歐洲國家的法律依據和使用者
----------------

如果您位於歐盟、歐洲經濟區或瑞士的某個國家，以下是我們處理您的資訊時所依據的法律。

* 合約必要性。這涵蓋了我們為了向您提供您所要求的——且我們已經同意——向您提供的服務而使用的資料，例如我們的遊戲、客戶服務和聊天功能。
* 法律義務。這涵蓋了我們為遵守法律義務而使用的資料，例如維護與稅收有關的記錄或回應某些資料的有效法律請求。
* 合法權益。這涵蓋了我們使用資料的目的，即可以合理地預期您使用我們的服務，並且我們認為不會損害您的隱私，例如分析瞭解我們的使用者如何瀏覽我們的網站和應用程式，以便保持我們的網站和應用程式的安全無虞，研究並改善我們的服務，進而提供更個人化的體驗、行銷和廣告；以及

同意。在我們根據您的同意處理資料的情況下，我們將要求您明確同意。您可以隨時撤回同意，但這並不影響我們在撤回之前處理您的個人資料的合法性。

雖然您可以隨時以本隱私政策中所述的方式撤回您的同意，或反對某些類型的處理方式，但請注意，如果您在提出此類請求後繼續使用服務，我們將恢復收集有關您的個人資料，並按照本隱私政策中的其他描述進行處理。如果您完全不希望我們收集有關您的任何個人資料，應停止所有遊戲進行及使用我們的服務。

十一、歐洲國家使用者權利
------------

如果您位於歐盟、歐洲經濟區或瑞士的某個國家，您對我們所持有的關於您的個人資料擁有某些權利，我們將在下文中詳細說明這些權利，且這些權利受適用的資料隱私法豁免。其中一些權利僅適用於某些情況，詳情請見下文。我們還列出了如何行使這些權利。請注意，我們可能會要求您在回應任何行使您權利的請求之前驗證您的身份。我們將在不無故拖延的情況下，至少在一個月內對您行使這些權利的請求作出回應（儘管在某些情況下可能會再延長兩個月）。若要行使您的任何權利，請發送電子郵件至[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)。

在某些情況下，我們可能會拒絕處理請求，比如請求顯然沒有根據或過度請求，或者該請求會危害到他人的隱私。

### A. 刪除您的個人資料

在某些情況下，您可以要求我們刪除我們所持有關於您的部分個人資料，如果您希望刪除您的個人資料，請與我們聯絡：[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)。

請注意，為了處理您的請求並確保刪除，您必須從您的行動裝置中刪除我們的應用程式/遊戲，並從您玩過我們遊戲的任何裝置中清除我們的Cookies。您必須刪除您在社群網路帳號中的所有服務功能連結。當我們刪除任何資訊時，該資訊將從我們的活動資料庫中被刪除，但可能會保留在我們的檔案中。請注意，我們可能仍然會出於其他目的保留部分或全部資訊，如維護財務記錄、保護或執行法律權利、維護行銷黑名單或出於技術原因，如維護技術安全或我們資料庫的完整性。我們也可能以匿名化形式保留您的資訊。請參見上文《資料保留刪除的影響》，瞭解更多關於刪除請求的資訊。

### B. 存取與便攜性

您有權了解我們所掌握的關於您的資訊，在某些情況下，您有權要求將資訊告知您。如果您希望行使該權利，請寄信至[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)聯絡我們，並告知我們您希望行使存取權，以及您所要求的準確資訊。請注意，若資訊中包含他人的個人資訊這類情況，我們可能無法提供您所要求的所有資訊。

在某些情況下，您可以要求我們基於同意處理的資料，或以結構化、常用和機器可讀的格式履行我們與您的合約，或要求我們將該等個人資料轉移給另一方。您的權利受適用的資料隱私法律的豁免。

如果您希望我們將個人資料轉移給另一方，請確保您已對該方進行詳細說明，並注意我們只能在技術上可行的情況下這樣做。一旦第三方收到個人資料或其程序，我們將不對其安全性負責。

如果提供某些資料會干擾他人的權利（例如，提供我們持有的關於您的個人資料會洩露他人的資訊或我們的商業機密或智慧財產權），我們也可能不會向您提供適用的資料保護權利所允許的某些資料。

### C. 更正

您有權更正我們所掌握的任何不準確的個人資料。如果您要求更正，請詳細解釋為什麼您認為我們持有的相關個人資料不準確或不完整，以供我們評估是否需要更正。

### D. 僅限於存儲處理

您有權要求我們在某些情況下停止處理我們所持有的有關您的個人資料，但存儲目的除外，例如。在我們考慮是否應更正或刪除該等資料時，或基於您的反對，我們是否應永久停止處理該等資料。但請注意，如果我們停止處理個人資料，但當有正當理由時（例如為法律索賠辯護或其他保護理由）我們可能會再次使用該資料。

### E. 反對意見

您有權反對我們對您的資料進行處理，但根據我們的服務條款要求執行的情況除外。

如果我們根據合法利益處理我們所持有與您相關的資料，您也有權反對我們處理您的資料，請將電子郵件發送至[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)。請向我們詳細說明您的理由，以便我們評估是否有足夠的迫切利益讓我們繼續處理這些資料，或者我們需要處理這些資料以滿足法律訴求。

### F. 投訴

如果您想對我們如何處理您的個人資料進行投訴，請透過[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)and聯絡我們，我們將努力回應您的關切。如果您認為我們違反了資料保護法，這並不影響您向您所居住或工作的歐盟國家的資料保護監督機構提出訴求的權利。

十二、您在加州的隱私權
-----------

從2020年1月1日起，如果您是加州居民，並且在您提出可核實的消費者請求後，您有以下權利（但是，這些權利受到法律允許的某些例外情況的限制）：

* 資訊。您可以要求我們提供以下資訊，說明我們在過去12個月內如何收集並使用您的個人資訊：我們收集的「個人資訊」（根據CCPA的規定）的類別；個人資訊的來源類別；收集和/或出售個人資訊的業務或商業目的；我們與之分享個人資訊以便我們向您提供服務的第三方的類別。如果您要求我們刪除您的部分或全部資訊，您可能無法再訪問或使用服務。
* 不歧視。您有權利行使上述權利，不受加州法律禁止的歧視性做法的影響。

行使您的權利。您可以發送電子郵件至[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)聯絡我們，或不時利用遊戲內的聯絡方法行使上述加州隱私權利。我們需要確認您的身份和加州居民身份，以便處理您行使資訊、訪問或刪除權利的請求。如果您沒有向我們提供合理充分的細節，使我們能夠理解並回應您的請求，我們無法處理。

回應時間。我們的目標是在收到消費者訪問或刪除請求後的45天內對該請求作出回應。如果我們需要更多的時間，將會以書面形式通知您原因並延期。

我們收集、使用和分享的個人資訊。我們在上述隱私政策中描述了我們收集個人資訊的來源，以及我們收集這些資訊的業務和商業目的。

我們不會向第三方出售您的個人資訊。我們確實與第三方分享個人資訊，用於本隱私政策中所述的業務和商業目的，包括但不限於廣告和行銷我們的服務。

十三、更新我們的隱私政策
------------

我們可能會不時更新本隱私政策，以維持我們對隱私的承諾。更新後的政策將繼續適用，而不會追溯既往。當我們進行變更時，會在本頁頂部更新日期，如果有重大變更，則會盡合理努力通知您。我們鼓勵您經常訪問本頁面，以瞭解任何變更內容。

在我們與我們的代理人以外的第三方分享您的資料之前，或在我們將您的資料用於最初收集或隨後授權的目的以外之前，我們將提供個人選擇退出或加入的權利。若要請求限制您個人資料的使用和披露，請將書面請求提交至[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)。

十四、聯絡我們
-------

若您有任何關於本隱私政策的問題，請寄電子郵件至[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)。若您想要聯絡我們的個人資料保護專人，請寄電子郵件至[dpo@kixeye.com](mailto:dpo@kixeye.com)。

Politique de confidentialité KIXEYE Inc.
========================================

Dernière version : 23 juin 2023

I. Introduction à notre Politique de confidentialité
----------------------------------------------------

KIXEYE Inc. (ci-après « nous » ou « KIXEYE ») prend très au sérieux les jeux. Et nous prenons très au sérieux vos droits en matière de confidentialité et de données. Nous nous engageons à maintenir une relation de confiance et de transparence avec vous. Cette Politique de confidentialité est rédigée de manière claire afin que vous compreniez facilement comment nous collectons, utilisons, stockons et partageons les informations qui permettent de vous identifier (ci-après « Données personnelles », qui peuvent selon le contexte signifier également les « Informations personnelles » telles que définies par la Loi californienne de protection de la confidentialité du consommateur de 2018 et/ou le Règlement général sur la protection des données dans l’Union européenne) quand vous accédez à nos sites Internet, applications mobiles, jeux, forums ou autres services (collectivement désignés ci-après les « Services »). Dès lors que vous utilisez un Service, vous consentez à chacune des collectes, utilisations et divulgations d’informations (y compris l’enregistrement et le suivi) décrites dans la présente Politique de confidentialité. Veuillez la lire attentivement. SI VOUS N’ACCEPTEZ PAS CETTE POLITIQUE DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ, MERCI DE N’UTILISER AUCUN SERVICE.

II. Quelles Données/Informations personnelles collectons-nous ?
---------------------------------------------------------------

### A. Informations que vous nous communiquez directement.

Lorsque vous interagissez avec un site Internet appartenant à KIXEYE ou que vous téléchargez le Service à partir d’une boutique d’applications tierce, nous collectons et stockons des informations vous concernant, comme décrit ci-dessous, dans la mesure où elles sont disponibles. Nous collectons les informations que vous nous fournissez, et ces informations peuvent inclure :

* Votre nom
* Votre adresse e-mail
* Les informations de votre compte KIXEYE, telles que votre nom d’utilisateur, votre identifiant ou votre avatar
* Votre identifiant sur différents réseaux sociaux (y compris Facebook, Apple iTunes, Google Play ou Steam)
* Nous pouvons également vous proposer de remplir un profil d’utilisateur visible des autres utilisateurs du Service. Votre profil d’utilisateur peut inclure : une image de profil ; un ou plusieurs noms d’utilisateur de Service ; et un identifiant KIXEYE qui est créé par KIXEYE et utilisé pour identifier votre profil.
* Vos informations de paiement ou de facturation
* Les messages que vous nous envoyez ou les Services (rapports de chat, demandes au support technique)
* Les informations qui nous aident à vérifier qu’il s’agit bien de vous, à empêcher toute fraude et à améliorer nos Services

### B. Informations collectées automatiquement.

Nous collectons automatiquement d’autres informations sur votre appareil via les cookies et d’autres moyens (SDK, balises web, pixels de suivi…) lorsque vous utilisez nos Services, y compris, dans la mesure du possible et le cas échéant, sous réserve de votre consentement :

* Votre adresse IP
* Des informations générales sur l’appareil des données de localisation (telles que le type d’appareil, le modèle, le système d’exploitation, la version du navigateur ou les identifiants uniques de l’appareil afin de vérifier la compatibilité de l’appareil avec l’IDFA ou le GAID)
* L’IDFA est un identifiant publicitaire pour Apple et le GAID est un identifiant publicitaire pour Google. Ces identifiants uniques sont non permanents et non personnels, ce qui signifie qu’ils ne contiennent pas d’informations sensibles vous concernant, mais qu’ils nous permettent de maintenir une cohérence entre toutes les applications et le suivi entre applications. Vous pouvez désactiver le partage de l’identifiant de votre appareil en mettant à jour les paramètres de votre appareil.
* Communications de service (messages dans le jeu, rapports de chat)
* Type de connexion

### C. Informations communiquées par des tiers.

Nous pouvons avoir accès à certaines informations vous concernant collectées par des tiers, y compris des réseaux sociaux, grâce à votre utilisation des services, sites Web, applications ou autres services de ces tiers.

### D. Informations relatives à votre compte que nous collectons.

Nous allons créer et attribuer à votre appareil un identifiant semblable à un numéro de compte. Nous allons également collecter les informations suivantes vous concernant, dans la mesure du possible et le cas échéant, sous réserve de votre consentement :

* nom d’utilisateur dans le jeu ;
* type d’appareil, modèle, système d’exploitation, mémoire, stockage ;
* numéro de téléphone ;
* pays, région, ville ;
* nom d’utilisateur, nom du personnage ;
* langue ;
* adresse e-mail, et
* vos contacts afin de vous permettre d’inviter des amis à rejoindre les Services.

Lorsque vous utilisez nos Services, nous collectons des informations sur la façon dont vous utilisez et interagissez avec nos Services, telles que le moment et la durée de connexion de votre appareil à nos jeux, les fonctionnalités de jeu auxquelles vous accédez et les autres joueurs avec lesquels vous interagissez, les achats dans l’application que vous effectuez, les progrès ou les niveaux que vous atteignez, et d’autres activités de jeu.

Nous collectons également des statistiques d’utilisation pseudonymes sur vos interactions avec le Service. Ces informations sont généralement collectées au moyen de fichiers journaux de serveur ou de fichiers journaux Web, de kits de développement de logiciels pour appareils mobiles et de technologies de suivi comme les cookies de navigateur pour collecter et analyser certains types d’informations techniques. Certains cookies que le Service place sur votre ordinateur sont liés à votre numéro d’utilisateur.

### E. Collecte d’informations via votre participation aux communautés

Lorsque vous utilisez le Service, vous avez accès à la communauté de jeux en ligne au sein du Service qui vous donne la possibilité de communiquer ou de partager des informations avec nous, mais aussi avec d’autres utilisateurs de notre Service en :

* participant à des forums de joueurs et fils de discussion ;
* publiant des commentaires publics à d’autres utilisateurs, profils ou jeux ;
* envoyant des messages privés ou des invitations à d’autres joueurs, par le biais de nos sites Internet ou via leurs adresses mail ;
* discutant avec d’autres utilisateurs ; et
* en publiant des liens Internet.

Lorsque vous participez à des communautés de jeu en ligne, nous accédons et stockons des Informations/Données personnelles vous concernant. Les informations que nous stockons varient selon le jeu/l’application et sont soumises aux paramètres de confidentialité que vous et vos amis établissez dans ce jeu/cette application. Vous pouvez modifier et en savoir plus sur ces paramètres dans l’application. Nous collectons ce qui suit :

* votre nom d’utilisateur dans le Service ;
* le numéro d’annonceur de votre appareil ;
* selon votre méthode de connexion aux Services, votre ID Facebook ;
* l’adresse IP de vos appareils ;
* vos chats et messages dans le jeu ; et
* si vous les avez indiqués, votre adresse e-mail et votre numéro de téléphone ;
* les avatars proposés.

### F. Informations de paiement

Nous collectons également certaines informations sur les achats (à savoir l’historique des transactions, y compris ce que vous avez acheté, le prix et la date). Notez que vos transactions d’achat en jeu et/ou dans l’application sont traitées par des processeurs de paiement tiers, tels que Apple (pour les achats sur les appareils iOS) et Google (pour les achats sur les appareils Android). Ces processeurs de paiement tiers sont les « vendeurs officiels » pour vos achats et ne partagent pas vos données financières, comme les numéros de carte de crédit, avec nous.

### G. Contacts avec le support technique

Quand vous demandez de l’aide au support technique, nous collectons et stockons les données suivantes :

* votre nom et adresse e-mail ;
* les informations sur votre activité sur le Service ;
* votre nom d’utilisateur et votre numéro ID ; et
* toute correspondance en lien avec l’aide dont vous avez bénéficiez

### H. Informations que nous ne collectons jamais.

Nous ne collectons pas de « catégories spéciales d’informations » vous concernant. Il s’agit de données raciales ou de renseignements concernant l’origine ethnique, l’orientation ou les pratiques sexuelles, les opinions politiques, les croyances religieuses ou philosophiques, l’appartenance à un syndicat ou des données sur la santé…

III. Pourquoi et comment utilisons-nous ces Informations/Données personnelles ?
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Nous utilisons vos Données personnelles et informations non-personnelles afin de :

### A. Vous fournir nos Services.

* Communiquer avec vous selon vos préférences et nos Conditions d’utilisation.
* Exploiter, développer, maintenir et améliorer nos Services.
* Fournir un support technique des Services.
* Résoudre les conflits et appliquer nos Conditions d’utilisation.
* Vous proposer des offres promotionnelles/spéciales.
* Percevoir les frais, paiements et autres montants dus dans le cadre des Services.
* Vous permettre de vous connecter avec d’autres joueurs.
* Créer un compte utilisateur afin d’utiliser les Services.
* Vous fournir la version appropriée des Services, y compris dans la langue de votre choix.
* Identifier, corriger et résoudre les bugs et les erreurs de maintenance.
* Développer de nouveaux services.

### B. Sécuriser nos Services.

* Identifier et/ou prévenir les fraudes.
* Identifier et/ou prévenir la violation des Conditions d’utilisation, les activités illégales ou la triche.
* Vérifier l’identité des utilisateurs pour les communications du support technique.
* Surveiller, assurer et améliorer la sécurité de notre réseau et de nos systèmes d’information.

### C. Personnaliser nos Services ou nos offres promotionnelles.

* Vous fournir des informations, une expérience de jeu personnalisée et d’autres offres.
* Déterminer ensemble vos domaines d’intérêt et répondre à vos demandes.
* Proposer, optimiser et mesurer l’efficacité de nos campagnes marketing.
* Effectuer des analyses pour le marketing interne et des études démographiques afin de développer, d’améliorer ou de personnaliser les Services.
* Sauvegarder, suivre vos stats, progression et attributs dans le jeu.

### D. Législation/divers.

Nous utilisons également vos Données personnelles et informations non-personnelles afin de :

* Se conformer aux obligations légales.
* Appliquer, établir ou défendre nos Conditions d’utilisation et autres droits légaux.
* Dans les situations où nous pensons de bonne foi qu’il faut protéger la sécurité, les finances ou des intérêts importants vous concernant, nous concernant ou de toute autre personne.

IV. Avec qui partageons-nous ces Informations/Données personnelles ?
--------------------------------------------------------------------

À l'exception des cas décrits ci-dessous, nous ne partageons pas vos Données personnelles avec des tiers non affiliés sans votre consentement. Toutefois, nous pouvons partager des données non personnelles, y compris des données anonymisées, agrégées ou pseudonymisées, conformément à la présente Politique de confidentialité. Nous pouvons partager vos informations, y compris vos Données personnelles avec des tiers dans les cas suivants :

### A. Tiers fournisseurs de services.

Nous pouvons conclure un contrat avec des tiers pour collecter ou traiter vos Informations ou Données personnelles en notre nom afin de fournir les Services, tels que les fournisseurs d’hébergement pour stocker les données personnelles que vous fournissez et pour les services de restauration après un sinistre, ainsi que pour l’exécution de tout contrat que nous concluons avec vous, les services de livraison de courrier électronique et les sociétés d’analyse (traitement par carte de crédit, envoi de messages au support technique). Nos accords avec ces tiers les obligent à protéger la confidentialité et la sécurité de vos Données personnelles et Informations conformément à la présente Politique de confidentialité. Nous ne partageons pas de Données personnelles avec des tiers dans un but de prospection commerciale sans votre consentement.

### B. Sociétés affiliées KIXEYE.

Nous faisons partie des sociétés Stillfront Group AB. Nous pouvons partager vos informations avec nos filiales, nos sociétés mères ou nos sociétés affiliées pour fournir et/ou améliorer nos Services et vous proposer une expérience et des offres personnalisées.

### C. Successeur d’un tiers acquéreur.

Si KIXEYE est fusionné avec un tiers, acquis, acheté (en totalité ou en partie), subit une cession, une réorganisation, une faillite ou un événement similaire, les informations collectées en vertu de la présente Politique de confidentialité peuvent être partagées avec ce tiers. Nous vous aviserons si cela se produit.

### D. Conformément à la loi.

Nous pouvons divulguer des Données personnelles si nous pensons être tenus de le faire afin de :

* Se conformer à une obligation légale.
* Protéger et défendre les droits ou la propriété de KIXEYE, des utilisateurs des Services ou d’autres personnes.
* Protéger la sécurité personnelle, financière ou les principaux intérêts des utilisateurs des Services ou du public.
* Protéger contre toute responsabilité civile.
* S’assurer du respect et de l’application de nos Conditions d’utilisation, politiques ou règles forum/communauté.
* Répondre aux demandes légitimes des autorités publiques, y compris des organismes de sécurité nationale ou d’application de la loi.

V. Comment protégeons-nous et stockons-nous vos Données personnelles ?
----------------------------------------------------------------------

### A. Protection de vos Données personnelles.

Nous mettons en œuvre des mesures de sécurité raisonnables pour protéger la sécurité de vos informations en ligne et hors ligne, et nous nous engageons à protéger les informations des clients/utilisateurs. Bien que nous prenions des précautions raisonnables contre d’éventuelles atteintes à la sécurité de nos Services et de nos bases de données et dossiers clients, nous ne pouvons garantir que l’accès non autorisé, le piratage, la perte de données ou d’autres atteintes ne se produiront jamais. Malheureusement, la transmission des informations sur Internet n’est jamais complètement sécurisée. Bien que nous nous efforcions de protéger vos Données personnelles, nous ne pouvons pas garantir la sécurité de vos données lorsqu’elles sont transmises à notre site ; toute transmission est donc à vos risques et périls. Nous vous exhortons à prendre des mesures pour protéger vos informations personnelles (y compris le mot de passe de votre compte) et à vous déconnecter de votre compte après utilisation. En cas de piratage de votre compte, cela pourrait entraîner un accès non autorisé à votre compte, aussi merci de bien sécuriser les informations de votre compte.

### A. Stockage de vos Données personnelles.

Les Données personnelles que nous collectons, que vous partagez avec nous ou que nous traitons en vertu de la présente Politique de confidentialité peuvent être stockées aux États-Unis ou dans tout autre pays dans lequel nous, nos filiales/sociétés affiliées ou des fournisseurs de services tiers opérons, y compris par l’utilisation du stockage sur le Cloud. Dès lors que vous utilisez les Services, vous acceptez le transfert de vos Données personnelles et données non personnelles vers les États-Unis et d’autres pays qui peuvent ne pas offrir le même niveau de protection de la vie privée que les lois de votre pays de résidence ou de citoyenneté. Par conséquent, vos informations pourraient être consultées par des autorités gouvernementales étrangères, conformément à la législation locale en vigueur.

VI. Gestion de votre vie privée
-------------------------------

Vous pouvez contrôler la collecte et l’utilisation de vos Données personnelles. Vous pouvez à tout moment accéder à vos Données personnelles ou les corriger, restreindre la collecte ou le traitement de vos Données personnelles et, dans certains cas, demander la désactivation ou la suppression permanente de vos Données personnelles. Pour demander l’accès, la correction, la restriction, la désactivation ou la suppression de vos Données personnelles, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Avant de traiter toute demande, nous pouvons demander de vérifier votre identité afin de protéger votre vie privée. Cela peut inclure un échange via la plateforme des Services ou d’autres méthodes de vérification de l’identité.

Les demandes non vérifiées, déraisonnables ou peu pratiques peuvent être rejetées. Pour protéger votre compte, les demandes de désactivation ou de suppression des Données personnelles nécessitent une vérification supplémentaire, qui peut inclure une suspension temporaire de votre compte et des Services. Une fois les demandes de désactivation ou de suppression traitées, vous ne pouvez pas revenir en arrière. Les Données personnelles et votre compte ne peuvent être récupérés.

VII. Enfants de moins de 13 ans
-------------------------------

Nos Services ne sont pas destinés, ou destinés à être attrayants, aux enfants de moins de 13 ans. Nous ne collectons pas sciemment des Données personnelles, des informations personnelles, des photos, des vidéos, des fichiers audio, ou les données de localisation d’enfants de moins de 13 ans, ni n’utilisons sciemment des identificateurs persistants pour reconnaître les enfants de moins de 13 ans au fil du temps et sur différents sites Web ou services en ligne. Si vous avez moins de 13  ans, n’utilisez pas nos Services et ne nous envoyez pas d’informations. Nous encourageons les parents et les tuteurs légaux à surveiller l’utilisation d’Internet de leurs enfants et à aider à appliquer cette Politique de confidentialité en demandant à leurs enfants de moins de 13 ans de ne jamais utiliser nos Services. Si vous avez des raisons de croire qu’un enfant de moins de 13 ans a fourni des Données personnelles ou des informations personnelles à KIXEYE par le biais de nos Services, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) et nous prendrons des mesures pour supprimer ces informations de nos bases de données dès que possible.

VIII. Pratiques de confidentialité des tiers / réseaux sociaux
--------------------------------------------------------------

Cette Politique de confidentialité s’applique uniquement aux Données personnelles et aux informations collectées par KIXEYE en fonction de l’utilisation que vous faites de nos Services. Les sites Web de tiers peuvent être accessibles via des liens lors de l’utilisation de nos Services, ou vous pouvez avoir atteint, accédé ou téléchargé nos Services via des sites Web de tiers. Ces derniers sont régis par leurs propres politiques de confidentialité et nous ne sommes pas tenus responsables de tout contenu apparaissant sur ces sites Web ou de toute pratique de confidentialité ou de sécurité concernant ces sites Web. Pour gérer les informations que KIXEYE reçoit à votre sujet sur les réseaux sociaux où vous utilisez nos Services, vous devrez suivre les instructions de ce site pour mettre à jour vos informations et modifier vos paramètres de confidentialité. Les outils de gestion de la confidentialité pour les applications sur Apple sont disponibles sur [https://www.apple.com/fr/privacy/control/](https://www.apple.com/fr/privacy/control/). Les outils de gestion de la confidentialité pour Google se trouve sur [https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/). Vous pouvez gérer certains aspects de la collecte et l’utilisation des informations en allant dans les paramètres de votre appareil (mobile) et en vérifiant les autorisations de chaque application.

Lorsque KIXEYE reçoit vos informations des réseaux sociaux, ces informations sont stockées et utilisées par KIXEYE conformément à la présente Politique de confidentialité, et vous pouvez accéder à ces informations et les mettre à jour comme décrit ci-dessous. Les comptes créés avec KIXEYE sont considérés comme actifs jusqu’à ce que l’utilisateur nous demande de les supprimer ou de les désactiver.

IX. Conservation des données et effet des demandes de suppression
-----------------------------------------------------------------

Nous nous efforçons de conserver uniquement les Données personnelles nécessaires. Lorsque les Données personnelles ne sont plus requises conformément à cette Politique de confidentialité, nous les supprimons ou les anonymisons régulièrement. Lorsqu’il n’est pas commercialement raisonnable de supprimer ou de rendre anonymes vos Données personnelles, nous cessons de les traiter et nous les stockons en toute sécurité jusqu’à ce que nous puissions les supprimer définitivement. Veuillez noter que nous pouvons conserver les informations nécessaires à des fins juridiques et comptables, pour résoudre les litiges, faire respecter nos accords d’utilisation, protéger nos droits légaux et nous conformer aux exigences et contraintes techniques et juridiques. Par exemple, nous pouvons conserver des archives concernant les paiements ou le support client. Si vous avez envoyé ou publié du contenu sur le Service, il se peut que nous ne soyons pas en mesure de le supprimer. La suppression effective peut nécessiter des actions de votre part, telles que la suppression d’applications et/ou de contenu lié au Service à partir de votre appareil et/ou la suppression du lien entre le Service et vos comptes de réseaux sociaux. Veuillez noter que si vous nous demandez de supprimer votre compte toute votre progression dans le jeu et tous les éléments virtuels inutilisés seront définitivement perdus. Sachez que les résultats et les artefacts de votre partie, par exemple les bases, les personnages, les navires, les fournitures… peuvent demeurer dans le jeu (et faire l’objet d’un jeu, c.-à-d. destruction ou exploitation par des joueurs actifs). même après que votre compte et/ou vos Données personnelles ont été supprimés ou dissociés du jeu.

X. Bases juridiques pour les utilisateurs des pays européens
------------------------------------------------------------

Si vous vous trouvez dans un pays de l’Union européenne, de l’Espace économique européen, ou en Suisse, voici les bases juridiques sur lesquelles nous nous appuyons pour traiter vos informations.

* Nécessité contractuelle. Cela englobe les données que nous utilisons afin de vous fournir les Services que vous avez demandés et que nous avons convenu de vous fournir, tels que nos jeux, notre support client et la fonctionnalité de chat ;
* Obligation légale. Cela englobe les données que nous utilisons pour respecter les obligations légales, telles que la tenue de registres relatifs à la fiscalité ou pour répondre à des demandes légales en vigueur pour certaines données ;
* Intérêts légitimes. Cela englobe les données que nous utilisons à des fins auxquelles nous pouvons raisonnablement nous attendre en fonction de votre utilisation de nos Services et que nous ne croyons pas être préjudiciables à votre vie privée, telles que l’analyse pour comprendre comment nos utilisateurs naviguent sur nos sites Web et applications, pour garder nos sites Web et applications sûrs et sécurisés, pour la recherche et l’optimisation de notre Service, afin de fournir une expérience plus personnalisée, le marketing et la publicité ; et

Consentement. Dans les cas où nous traitons des données sur la base de votre consentement, nous vous demanderons votre consentement explicite. Vous pouvez retirer votre consentement à tout moment, mais cela n’affectera pas la légalité du traitement de vos données personnelles avant le retrait.

Bien que vous puissiez retirer votre consentement ou vous opposer à certains types de traitement à tout moment de la manière décrite dans la présente Politique de confidentialité, veuillez noter que si vous continuez à utiliser les Services après une telle demande, nous reprendrons la collecte des Données personnelles vous concernant et les traiterons comme indiqué dans la présente Politique de confidentialité. Si vous ne voulez pas que nous collections des Données personnelles à votre sujet, vous devez cesser de jouer à nos jeux et d’utiliser nos Services.

XI. Droits des utilisateurs dans les pays européens
---------------------------------------------------

Si vous vous trouvez dans un pays de l’Union européenne, de l’Espace économique européen, ou en Suisse, vous disposez de certains droits en ce qui concerne les Données personnelles que nous détenons à votre sujet, que nous détaillons ci-dessous, et qui sont soumis à des exemptions en vertu des lois applicables en matière de confidentialité des données. Certains de ces droits ne s’appliquent que dans certaines circonstances, comme il est indiqué plus en détail ci-dessous. Nous avons également établi comment exercer ces droits. Veuillez noter que nous pouvons vous demander à vérifier votre identité avant de répondre à toute demande d’exercice de vos droits. Nous répondrons à votre demande d’exercer ces droits sans retard indu et au moins dans un délai d’un mois (bien que cela puisse être prolongé de deux mois supplémentaires dans certaines circonstances). Pour exercer vos droits, veuillez envoyer un message à l’adresse [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Nous pouvons refuser de traiter les demandes dans certaines circonstances, par exemple lorsque les demandes sont manifestement non fondées ou excessives ou qu’elles mettent en péril la vie privée d’autrui.

### A. Suppression de vos données personnelles

Dans certaines circonstances, vous pouvez nous demander de supprimer certaines Données personnelles que nous détenons à votre sujet. Si vous souhaitez que vos Données personnelles soient supprimées, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Veuillez noter que pour traiter votre demande et assurer la suppression, vous devez supprimer nos applications/jeux de vos appareils mobiles et effacer nos cookies de tout appareil où vous avez joué à nos jeux. Vous devez également supprimer tous les liens de fonctionnalité de Service sur vos comptes de réseau social. Lorsque nous supprimons des informations, celles-ci seront supprimées de nos bases de données actives, mais peuvent rester dans nos archives. Veuillez noter, cependant, que nous pouvons toujours conserver une partie ou la totalité de ces informations à d’autres fins, comme la tenue de dossiers financiers, la protection ou l’application des droits légaux, la gestion des listes de suppression marketing ou pour des raisons techniques comme le maintien de la sécurité technique ou de l’intégrité de notre base de données. Veuillez consulter la section « Conservation des données et effet des demandes de suppression » ci-dessus pour en savoir plus sur les demandes de suppression.

### B. Accès et portabilité

Vous avez le droit de savoir quelles informations nous détenons à votre sujet et, dans certains cas, que nous vous les communiquions. Si vous souhaitez exercer ce droit, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) et nous faire savoir que vous souhaitez exercer votre droit d’accès et précisément quelles informations vous demandez. Veuillez noter que nous pourrions ne pas être en mesure de fournir toutes les informations que vous demandez, par exemple si elles comprennent des informations personnelles concernant une autre personne.

Dans certaines circonstances, vous pouvez demander les données que nous traitons sur consentement ou pour exécuter notre contrat dans un format structuré, couramment utilisé et lisible par machine ou pour demander que nous transférions ces données personnelles à une autre partie. Vos droits sont assujettis à des exemptions en vertu des lois sur la confidentialité des données en vigueur.

Si vous souhaitez que nous transférions les données personnelles à une autre partie, veuillez vous assurer de détailler cette partie et sachez que nous ne pouvons le faire que lorsque cela est techniquement possible. Nous ne sommes pas responsables de la sécurité des Données personnelles ou de leur traitement une fois reçues par le tiers.

Il se peut également que nous ne refusions de fournir certaines données si cela interfère avec d’autres droits (à savoir, lorsque la mise à disposition des Données personnelles que nous détenons à votre sujet révélerait des informations sur une autre personne ou sur nos secrets commerciaux ou notre propriété intellectuelle). conformément aux droits de protection des données en vigueur.

### C. Correction

Vous avez le droit de corriger les Données personnelles que nous possédons et qui sont inexactes. Lorsque vous demandez une correction, veuillez expliquer en détail pourquoi vous croyez que les Données personnelles que nous détenons à votre sujet sont inexactes ou incomplètes afin que nous puissions évaluer si une correction est requise.

### D. Limitation du traitement au stockage uniquement

Vous avez le droit de nous demander de cesser tout traitement des Données Personnelles que nous détenons à votre sujet à des fins autres que de stockage dans certaines circonstances, par exemple pendant que nous examinons si elles doivent être corrigées ou supprimées ou, sur la base de votre objection, si nous devrions arrêter le traitement de façon permanente. Veuillez toutefois noter que si nous cessons de traiter les Données personnelles, nous pouvons les utiliser à nouveau s’il existe des raisons valables de le faire (par exemple, pour la défense de réclamations légales ou pour une autre protection).

### E. Objection

Vous avez le droit de vous opposer au traitement des données vous concernant à d’autres fins que celles qui sont exigées par nos Conditions d’utilisation.

Vous avez également le droit de vous opposer au traitement des données vous concernant en nous envoyant un message à l’adresse [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) si nous traitons les données que nous détenons à votre sujet sur la base de notre intérêt légitime et que vous vous opposez à ce traitement. Veuillez nous fournir des détails sur votre raisonnement afin que nous puissions déterminer s’il y a un intérêt impérieux à ce que nous continuions à traiter de telles données ou si nous devons les traiter conformément à la législation en vigueur.

### F. Réclamations

Si vous souhaitez déposer une plainte concernant la façon dont nous traitons vos Données personnelles, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) et nous nous efforcerons de répondre à vos préoccupations. Ceci est sans préjudice de votre droit d’introduire une réclamation auprès de l’autorité de contrôle de la protection des données dans le pays de l’UE où vous vivez ou travaillez et où vous pensez que nous avons enfreint les lois sur la protection des données.

XII. Droits de confidentialité des résidents de Californie
----------------------------------------------------------

Depuis le 1er janvier 2020, si vous êtes un résident californien, et conformément à votre demande de consommateur vérifiable, vous pouvez être en mesure d'exercer des droits différents énumérés ci-dessous (sous réserve de certaines limitations légales) :

* Informations. Vous pouvez demander les informations suivantes relatives à notre méthode de collecte et d’utilisation de vos Informations personnelles au cours des 12 derniers mois : les catégories d’Informations personnelles que nous avons collectées (conformément à la CCPA); les catégories de sources à partir desquelles nous avons collecté des Informations personnelles; les fins commerciales pour collecter et/ou vendre des Informations personnelles; les catégories de tiers avec lesquels nous partageons des Informations personnelles afin que nous puissions vous fournir nos Services. Si vous nous demandez de supprimer une partie ou la totalité de vos informations, il se peut que vous ne puissiez plus accéder aux Services ni les utiliser.
* Non-discrimination. Vous avez le droit d’exercer les droits décrits ci-dessus sans pratiques discriminatoires interdites par la loi californienne.

Exercice de vos droits. Vous pouvez exercer vos droits à la vie privée en Californie décrits ci-dessus en nous envoyant un message à l’adresse a href="mailto:privacy@kixeye.com">privacy@kixeye.com/a>, ou via les méthodes de contact en jeu qui peuvent être indiquées. Nous devrons confirmer votre identité et votre résidence en Californie pour traiter vos demandes d’exercice de vos droits d’information, d’accès ou de suppression. Nous ne pouvons pas traiter votre demande si vous ne nous fournissez pas suffisamment de détails pour nous permettre de la comprendre et d’y répondre.

Temps de réponse. Nous tâchons de répondre à une demande d’accès ou de suppression d’un consommateur dans les 45 jours suivant la réception de cette demande. Si nous avons besoin de plus de temps, nous vous en informerons par écrit.

Informations personnelles que nous collectons, utilisons et partageons. Nous décrivons les sources à partir desquelles nous collectons des Informations personnelles et les fins commerciales pour lesquelles nous collectons lesdites informations dans la présente Politique de confidentialité ci-dessus.

Nous ne vendons pas vos Informations personnelles à des tiers. Nous partageons des Informations personnelles avec des tiers à des fins professionnelles et commerciales décrites dans la présente Politique de confidentialité, y compris, sans s’y limiter, la publicité et la commercialisation de nos Services.

XIII. Mises à jour de notre Politique de confidentialité
--------------------------------------------------------

Il peut arriver, de temps à autre, que nous mettions à jour cette Politique de confidentialité pour maintenir notre engagement en matière de confidentialité. Les mises à jour s’appliquent à partir de la date d’entrée en vigueur, mais jamais rétroactivement. Lorsque nous apportons des changements, nous mettons à jour la date en haut de cette page et nous ferons des efforts raisonnables pour vous prévenir si les changements sont importants. Nous vous encourageons à consulter cette page fréquemment pour vous tenir au courant de tout changement.

Avant de partager vos données avec des tiers autres que nos agents, ou avant de les utiliser à des fins autres que celles pour lesquelles elles ont été initialement collectées ou autorisées, nous vous laisserons le choix de refuser ou d’accepter. Toute demande, visant à limiter l’utilisation et la divulgation de vos Données personnelles, doit faire l’objet d’une demande écrite envoyée à [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

XIV. Nous contacter
-------------------

Pour toute question concernant cette Politique de confidentialité, merci de nous envoyer un message à l’adresse [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Si vous souhaitez contacter notre responsable de la protection des données, veuillez nous envoyer un message à l’adresse [dpo@kixeye.com](mailto:dpo@kixeye.com).

Datenschutzrichtlinien von KIXEYE Inc.
======================================

Letzte Aktualisierung: 23. Juni 2023

I. Einführung in unsere Datenschutzrichtlinien
----------------------------------------------

KIXEYE Inc. („wir“ oder „KIXEYE“) nimmt Spiele ernst. Und wir nehmen den Schutz deiner Daten und deine Rechte bezüglich dieser Daten ernst. Wir verpflichten uns zur Pflege einer Geschäftsbeziehung zu dir, die von Vertrauen und Transparenz geprägt ist. Diese Datenschutzrichtlinien sind in verständlicher Sprache gehalten, damit du leicht nachvollziehen kannst, wie wir Daten, mit denen du identifiziert werden kannst („Personenbezogene Daten“ – dazu gehören, wenn im Zusammenhang darauf hingewiesen wird, auch „Personenbezogene Daten“ gemäß des California Consumer Privacy Protection Act (Verbraucherdatenschutzgesetz für Kalifornien) von 2018 und/oder gemäß der Datenschutz-Grundverordnung der EU), sammeln, verwenden, speichern und teilen, wenn du unsere Websites, mobilen Apps, Spiele, Foren oder anderen Dienste (zusammen die „Dienste“) nutzt. Durch die Nutzung eines Dienstes erklärst du dich mit jeder Sammlung, Verwendung und Weitergabe von Daten (einschließlich Aufzeichnung und Tracking) einverstanden, die in diesen Datenschutzrichtlinien beschrieben wird. Bitte lies sie sorgfältig durch. WENN DU DIESEN DATENSCHUTZRICHTLINIEN NICHT ZUSTIMMST, BITTEN WIR DICH, KEINEN DIESER DIENSTE ZU NUTZEN.

II. Welche Daten/personenbezogenen Daten sammeln wir?
-----------------------------------------------------

### A. Daten, die du uns unmittelbar zur Verfügung stellst

Wenn du auf eine zu KIXEYE gehörende Website zugreifst oder den Dienst von einem externen App-Store herunterlädst, sammeln und speichern wir Daten unmittelbar von dir, wie unten beschrieben, soweit sie uns zur Verfügung stehen. Wir sammeln die Daten, die du uns zur Verfügung stellst; hierzu kann Folgendes gehören:

* Name
* E-Mail-Adresse
* KIXEYE-Konto-Daten wie dein eindeutiger Nutzername, deine ID oder dein Avatar
* Deine ID aus verschiedenen sozialen Netzwerken (einschließlich Facebook, Apple iTunes, Google Play, Steam usw.)
* Möglicherweise bieten wir dir die Erstellung eines Nutzerprofils an, das von anderen Nutzer/innen der Dienste angesehen werden kann. Dein Nutzerprofil kann Folgendes beinhalten: ein Profilbild, einen oder mehrere Nutzernamen für die Dienste und eine KIXEYE-Nutzer-ID-Nummer, die von KIXEYE erstellt wird und der Identifizierung deines Profils dient.
* Zahlungs- oder Rechnungsinformationen
* Deine Nachrichten an uns oder die Dienste (Chat-Protokolle, Anfragen an den Kunden-Support)
* Daten, die uns helfen, deine Identität zu bestätigen, Betrug zu unterbinden und unsere Dienste weiterzuentwickeln und zu verbessern

### B. Automatisch gesammelte Daten

Wenn du unsere Dienste nutzt, sammeln wir durch Cookies und weitere Technologien (SDKs, Tracking-Pixel usw.) weitere Daten automatisch von deinem Gerät. Dazu gehören folgende Daten, sofern sie verfügbar sind, wenn ihre Sammlung notwendig ist und wenn du dein Einverständnis gegeben hast:

* IP-Adresse
* Allgemeine Standortdaten-Geräteinformationen wie Geräteart, Modell, Betriebssystem, Browser-Version oder eindeutige Geräteidentifikatoren zur Überprüfung von Gerätekompatibilität und IDFA oder GAID
* IDFA steht für Identifier for Advertisers auf Apple-Geräten und GAID steht für Google Advertising Identity. Diese eindeutigen Identifikatoren sind nicht permanent und nicht personenbezogen, enthalten also keine vertraulichen Daten über dich, ermöglichen aber ein einheitliches Verhalten der Dienste in allen Apps und das Tracking über Apps hinweg. Du kannst das Teilen deines Geräteidentifikators in den Einstellungen auf deinem Gerät deaktivieren.
* Unterhaltungen auf den Diensten (Nachrichten im Spiel, Chat-Protokolle)
* Verbindungsart

### C. Daten, die von Dritten an uns weitergegeben werden

Wir erhalten gegebenenfalls Zugriff auf bestimmte Daten, die Dritte, einschließlich soziale Netzwerke, von dir gesammelt haben, da du deren Dienste, Websites, Apps oder andere Services genutzt hast.

### D. Von uns gesammelte Daten zu deinem Nutzerkonto

Wir erstellen und teilen deinem Gerät einen Identifikator zu, ähnlich einer Kontonummer. Außerdem sammeln wir folgende Daten über dich, sofern sie verfügbar sind, wenn ihre Sammlung notwendig ist und wenn du dein Einverständnis gegeben hast:

* Nutzername im Spiel,
* Geräteart, Modell, Betriebssystem, Arbeitsspeicher, Festspeicher,
* Telefonnummer,
* Land, Region, Stadt,
* Nutzername, Charaktername,
* Sprache,
* E-Mail-Adresse und
* Deine Kontakte, damit du Freunde zur Nutzung der Dienste einladen kannst.

Wenn du unsere Dienste nutzt, sammeln wir Daten darüber, wie du unsere Dienste nutzt und mit ihnen interagierst. Dazu gehören etwa, wann und wie lange dein Gerät bei unseren Spielen angemeldet ist, auf welche Spiele-Features du zugreifst und mit welchen anderen Spieler/innen du interagierst, deine In-App-Käufe, dein Spielfortschritt oder erreichter Level und weitere Aktivitäten im Spiel.

Zusätzlich sammeln wir pseudonymisierte Nutzungsstatistiken über deine Interaktionen mit den Diensten. Diese Daten werden üblicherweise über Server-Logdateien oder Web-Logdateien, Software Development Kits für Mobilgeräte und Tracking-Technologien wie Browser-Cookies erhoben, mit denen bestimmte technische Informationen gesammelt und analysiert werden. Manche der Cookies, welche die Dienste auf deinem Computer speichern, sind mit deiner/deinen Nutzer-ID-Nummer/n verbunden.

### E. Daten, die durch deine Teilnahme an Communitys gesammelt werden

Durch deine Nutzung der Dienste erhältst du Zugang zur Online-Spiele-Community innerhalb der Dienste. Darüber kannst du nicht nur mit uns kommunizieren und Informationen teilen, sondern auch mit anderen Nutzer/innen unserer Dienste, und zwar durch:

* Teilnahme an Spielerforen und Nachrichtenforen,
* Posten öffentlicher Kommentare zu anderen Nutzer/innen und Profilen oder auf Spielforen,
* Versand von privaten Nachrichten oder Einladungen an andere Nutzer/innen, direkt über unsere Websites oder an deren E-Mail-Konten,
* Chat mit anderen Nutzer/innen und
* Posten von Weblinks.

Wenn du an Online-Spiele-Communitys teilnimmst, greifen wir auf Daten/personenbezogene Daten von dir zu und speichern diese. Welche Daten wir speichern ist abhängig vom jeweiligen Spiel/der jeweiligen App und den Datenschutzeinstellungen, die du und deine Freunde in diesem Spiel/dieser App vornehmen. Innerhalb der App erfährst du mehr über diese Einstellungen und kannst sie ändern. Wir sammeln folgende Daten:

* Deinen Nutzernamen innerhalb der Dienste,
* die Werbe-ID deines Geräts,
* deine Facebook-Nutzer-ID, abhängig von deiner Anmeldemethode für die Dienste,
* die IP-Adresse deiner Geräte, über die der Zugriff erfolgt,
* deine Chats und Nachrichten im Spiel und
* deine E-Mail-Adresse und Telefonnummer, sofern du sie uns zur Verfügung gestellt hast.
* Übertragene Avatare

### F. Zahlungsinformationen

Wir sammeln auch einige Daten über deine Einkäufe (deinen Transaktionsverlauf, einschließlich was du wann und zu welchem Preis erworben hast). Beachte bitte, dass deine Einkäufe im Spiel und/oder in der App von externen Zahlungsabwicklern wie Apple (für Käufe auf iOS-Geräten) oder Google (für Käufe auf Android-Geräten) verarbeitet werden. Diese externen Zahlungsabwickler sind die zuständigen Händler für deine Einkäufe, sie teilen deine Finanzdaten wie z. B. Kreditkartennummern nicht mit uns.

### G. Kommunikation mit dem Kunden-Support

Wenn du unser Kunden-Support-Team um Unterstützung bittest, sammeln und speichern wir:

* Deinen Namen und deine E-Mail-Adresse,
* Daten über deine Aktivitäten in den Diensten,
* deinen Nutzernamen oder deine Nutzer-ID-Nummer und
* sämtlichen Schriftverkehr im Zusammenhang mit der dir gebotenen Unterstützung.

### H. Daten, die wir niemals sammeln

Wir erheben keine Daten „besonderer Kategorien“ von dir oder über dich. Dazu gehören rassische oder ethnische Herkunft, sexuelle Praktiken oder Orientierung, politische Meinungen, religiöse oder philosophische Überzeugungen, Gewerkschaftszugehörigkeit oder Gesundheitsdaten usw.

III. Wie und warum verwenden wir diese Daten/personenbezogenen Daten?
---------------------------------------------------------------------

Wir verwenden deine personenbezogenen und nicht personenbezogenen Daten zu folgenden Zwecken:

### A. Bereitstellung unserer Dienste

* Unsere Kommunikation mit dir, im Einklang mit deinen Einstellungen und unseren Nutzungsbedingungen
* Betrieb, Weiterentwicklung, Unterhalt und Verbesserung unserer Dienste
* Bereitstellung von Kunden-Support für die Dienste.
* Streitbeilegung und Durchsetzung unserer Nutzungsbedingungen.
* Bereitstellung von Sonder-/Aktionsangeboten in unseren Spielen
* Eintreibung von Gebühren, Zahlungen und anderer Beträge, die uns für die Dienste geschuldet werden.
* Schaffung von Möglichkeiten, dich mit anderen Spieler/innen zu verbinden.
* Erstellung eines Nutzerkontos für die Nutzung der Dienste.
* Bereitstellung der Dienste in der für dich passenden Version, einschließlich deiner bevorzugten Sprache.
* Identifizierung, Behebung und Problembehandlung von Fehlern in Programmen und Diensten.
* Entwicklung neuer Dienste.

### B. Absicherung unserer Dienste

* Identifikation und/oder Unterbindung von Betrug.
* Identifikation und/oder Unterbindung von Verletzungen unserer Nutzungsbedingungen, illegalen Aktivitäten oder Schwindeleien
* Überprüfung von Nutzeridentitäten für Kommunikationen mit dem Kunden-Support.
* Überwachung, Gewährleistung und Verbesserung der Sicherheit unseres Netzwerks und unserer Datenverarbeitungssysteme

### C. Personalisierung unserer Dienste oder Erstellung von Angeboten

* Bereitstellung von Benachrichtigungen, personalisierter Spielerfahrung und weiteren Angeboten
* Kommunikation bezüglich deiner Interessengebiete und Beantwortung deiner Anfragen.
* Durchführung und Optimierung unserer Marketing-Kampagnen und Messung der Effektivität dieser Kampagnen
* Durchführung von Analysen für interne Marketing- und Demografiestudien zur Weiterentwicklung, Verbesserung oder Personalisierung der Dienste
* Speicherung und Nachverfolgung deiner Attribute, deines Fortschritts und deiner Werte im Spiel

### D. Rechtliches/Weiteres

Wir verwenden deine personenbezogenen und nicht personenbezogenen Daten auch zu folgenden Zwecken:

* Erfüllung gesetzlicher Pflichten.
* Ausübung, Durchsetzung und Verteidigung unserer Nutzungsbedingungen und anderer gesetzlicher Rechte
* Für Fälle, in welchen wir in gutem Glauben die Notwendigkeit sehen, die Sicherheit, die finanziellen Interessen oder die Ansprüche von dir, von uns oder von einer anderen Person schützen zu müssen.

IV. An wen geben wir diese Daten/personenbezogenen Daten weiter?
----------------------------------------------------------------

Deine personenbezogenen Daten geben wir nur in den unten beschriebenen Fällen ohne deine Zustimmung an nicht verbundene Dritte weiter. Möglicherweise geben wir jedoch nicht personenbezogene Daten, einschließlich anonymisierter, aggregierter oder pseudonymisierter Daten, in Übereinstimmung mit diesen Datenschutzrichtlinien weiter. Deine Daten, einschließlich personenbezogener Daten, können in den folgenden Fällen an Dritte weitergegeben werden:

### A. Externe Diensteanbieter

Wir können Verträge mit Dritten abschließen, welche zur Bereitstellung der Dienste in unserem Auftrag deine Daten oder personenbezogenen Daten erheben oder verarbeiten.Dazu gehören Hosting-Anbieter, welche die von dir bereitgestellten personenbezogenen Daten speichern und im Notfall deren Wiederherstellung ermöglichen, sowie Dienstleister, welche uns die Erfüllung von mit dir geschlossenen Verträgen ermöglichen, weiterhin Betreiber von E-Mail-Diensten und Analyse-Unternehmen (Abwicklung von Kreditkartenzahlungen, Versand von Kundenservice-E-Mails). Unsere Übereinkünfte mit diesen Dritten verpflichten sie, die Vertraulichkeit und Sicherheit deiner personenbezogenen und sonstigen Daten im Einklang mit diesen Datenschutzrichtlinien zu schützen. Ohne dein Einverständnis geben wir keine personenbezogenen Daten zu Marketing-Zwecken an Dritte weiter.

### B. Mit KIXEYE verbundene Unternehmen

Wir sind Teil des Konzerns StillFront Group AB. Wir können deine Daten mit unseren Tochterunternehmen, unserer Dachgesellschaft oder mit verbundenen Unternehmen teilen, um unsere Dienste zu erfüllen und/oder zu verbessern und um dir personalisierte Erfahrungen und Angebote zur Verfügung zu stellen.

### C. Ein Nachfolger oder übernehmender Dritter

Wenn KIXEYE mit einem Dritten fusioniert, von diesem übernommen wird oder aufgekauft wird (vollständig oder teilweise), von einer Desinvestition, Umstrukturierung, Insolvenz oder einem ähnlichen Ereignis betroffen ist, können Daten, die im Rahmen dieser Datenschutzrichtlinien erhoben wurden, an den betreffenden Dritten weitergegeben werden. Sollte dieser Fall eintreten, werden wir dich darüber informieren.

### D. Aufgrund gesetzlicher Vorgaben

Wir können personenbezogene Daten weitergeben, wenn wir aufgrund guten Glaubens der Überzeugung sind, dass wir hierzu aus folgenden Gründen verpflichtet sind:

* Erfüllung einer gesetzlichen Pflicht.
* Wahrung und Verteidigung der Rechte und des Eigentums von KIXEYE, von Nutzer/innen der Dienste oder von anderen.
* Wahrung der persönlichen Sicherheit, der finanziellen oder sonstigen Ansprüche von Nutzer/innen der Dienste oder der Öffentlichkeit
* Schutz vor gesetzlicher Haftung.
* Überwachung der Einhaltung und Durchsetzung unserer Nutzungsbedingungen, Grundsätze oder Regeln bezüglich der Foren bzw. der Community
* Reaktion auf gesetzliche Anfragen von Behörden, einschließlich solcher Behörden, die für die Wahrung der öffentlichen Sicherheit oder der Strafverfolgung zuständig sind

V. Wie speichern und schützen wir deine personenbezogenen Daten?
----------------------------------------------------------------

### A. Schutz deiner personenbezogenen Daten

Wir ergreifen angemessene Sicherheitsmaßnahmen, um die Sicherheit deiner Daten online und offline zu schützen, und wir verpflichten uns dem Schutz von Kunden-/Nutzerdaten. Wir ergreifen angemessene Vorsichtsmaßnahmen gegen mögliche Sicherheitsverletzungen bei unseren Diensten und unseren Kundendatensätzen, können jedoch unerlaubte Zugriffe, Hacking, Datenverluste oder andere Verletzungen nicht völlig ausschließen. Die Datenübertragung über das Internet ist niemals vollständig sicher. Wir engagieren uns für den Schutz deiner personenbezogenen Daten, jedoch können wir die Sicherheit deiner Daten nicht garantieren, während sie zu unserer Site übertragen werden; du trägst also das Risiko für jegliche Datenübertragung. Wir empfehlen dir dringend, Maßnahmen zum Schutz deiner personenbezogenen Daten (einschließlich des Passworts für dein Nutzerkonto) zu ergreifen und dich nach der Nutzung von deinem Konto abzumelden. Wird dein Konto gehackt, können unerlaubte Zugriffe darauf erfolgen. Sorge daher bitte für die Sicherheit deiner Kontodaten.

### B. Speicherung deiner personenbezogenen Daten

Personenbezogene Daten, die wir im Rahmen dieser Datenschutzrichtlinien sammeln, übermittelt bekommen oder verarbeiten, können in den USA oder einem beliebigen anderen Land gespeichert werden, in dem wir, unsere Tochterunternehmen/verbundenen Unternehmen oder externe Anbieter tätig sind. Hierunter fällt auch die Nutzung von Cloud-Speicherdiensten. Durch die Nutzung der Dienste erklärst du dich damit einverstanden, dass deine personenbezogenen und nicht personenbezogenen Daten in die USA und andere Länder übertragen werden. Diese Länder bieten möglicherweise nicht dasselbe Niveau an Datenschutz, wie es die Gesetze des Landes garantieren, in dem du ansässig bist oder dessen Staatsbürgerschaft du besitzt. Daher könnte durch ausländische Regierungsbehörden oder auf sonstige Weise im Rahmen des vor Ort anwendbaren Rechts auf deine Daten zugegriffen werden.

VI. Deine Kontrolle über deine Daten
------------------------------------

Du hast die Kontrolle über die Erhebung und Verwendung deiner personenbezogenen Daten. Du kannst jederzeit auf deine personenbezogenen Daten zugreifen, sie berichtigen, ihre Sammlung oder Verarbeitung begrenzen und unter bestimmten Umständen die Deaktivierung oder dauerhafte Löschung deiner personenbezogenen Daten beantragen. Möchtest du auf deine personenbezogenen Daten zugreifen, sie berichtigen, ihre Verwendung begrenzen, sie deaktivieren oder löschen lassen, kontaktiere uns bitte unter [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Bevor wir deine Anfrage bearbeiten, können wir dich zum Schutz deiner Privatsphäre bitten, deine Identität zu bestätigen. Dies kann die Kommunikation über die Dienste-Plattform oder andere Methoden der Identitätsbestätigung einschließen.

Wir behalten uns vor, Anfragen abzulehnen, die unbestätigt, nicht nachvollziehbar oder nicht praktikabel sind. Zum Schutz deines Kontos erfordern Anträge zur Deaktivierung oder Löschung personenbezogener Daten eine zusätzliche Bestätigung, was eine vorübergehende Deaktivierung deines Kontos und der Dienste einschließen kann. Sobald Anträge auf Deaktivierung oder Löschung bearbeitet werden, sind sie unwiderruflich. Die personenbezogenen Daten und das Konto können dann nicht wiederhergestellt werden.

VII. Kinder unter 13 Jahren
---------------------------

Unsere Dienste richten sich nicht an Kinder unter 13 Jahren und haben diese nicht als Zielgruppe. Wir sammeln nicht wissentlich personenbezogene Daten, Informationen zur Person, Fotos, Videos, Audiodateien oder Ortsdaten von oder über Kinder/n unter 13 Jahren. Ebenso nutzen wir nicht wissentlich dauerhafte Identifikatoren, um Kinder unter 13 Jahren im Zeitverlauf und über verschiedene Websites und Online-Services hinweg wiederzuerkennen. Bitte nutze unsere Dienste nicht und übermittle keine Daten an uns, wenn du jünger als 13 Jahre bist. Wir bestärken Eltern und Vormunde darin, die Internet-Nutzung ihrer Kinder zu überwachen und uns bei der Durchsetzung dieser Datenschutzrichtlinien zu unterstützen, indem sie ihre Kinder unter 13 Jahren dazu anweisen, niemals unsere Dienste zu nutzen. Wenn Grund zu der Annahme besteht, dass ein Kind unter 13 Jahren über unsere Dienste personenbezogene Daten oder Informationen zur Person an KIXEYE übermittelt hat, kontaktiere uns bitte unter [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Wir werden Maßnahmen ergreifen, um diese Daten so bald wie möglich aus unseren Datenbanken zu löschen.

VIII. Datenschutzrichtlinien und Verfahren externer Anbieter/Soziale Netzwerke
------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Diese Datenschutzrichtlinien gelten nur für personenbezogene Daten und Informationen, die KIXEYE durch deine Nutzung unserer Dienste erhebt. Bei der Nutzung unserer Dienste kann über Links der Zugriff auf externe Websites möglich sein, oder du hast möglicherweise über externe Websites unsere Dienste erreicht, auf sie zugegriffen oder sie heruntergeladen. Für diese externen Websites gelten eigene Datenschutzregelungen. Wir haften nicht und übernehmen keine Verantwortung für den Inhalt dieser Websites oder jegliche Datenschutz- oder Sicherheitsmaßnahmen dieser Websites. Möchtest du kontrollieren, welche Daten KIXEYE von den sozialen Netzwerken übermittelt bekommt, auf denen du unsere Dienste nutzt, folge bitte den Anweisungen auf der jeweiligen Site zur Aktualisierung deiner Daten und Anpassung deiner Datenschutzeinstellungen. Auf die Datenschutzeinstellungen von Apple-Anwendungen kann unter dieser Adresse zugegriffen werden: [http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/). Auf die Datenschutzeinstellungen von Google kann unter dieser Adresse zugegriffen werden: [https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/). Bestimmte Bereiche der Sammlung und Verwendung von Daten kannst du unter den Einstellungen deines (Mobil-)Geräts verwalten, indem du die Berechtigungen der jeweiligen Anwendung anpasst.

Sobald KIXEYE deine Daten von sozialen Netzwerken erhält, werden diese Daten im Einklang mit diesen Datenschutzrichtlinien von KIXEYE gespeichert und verwendet, und du kannst wie unten beschrieben auf diese Daten zugreifen und sie aktualisieren. Bei KIXEYE erstellte Konten gelten als aktiv, bis wir eine Nutzeranfrage mit der Bitte um Löschung oder Deaktivierung erhalten.

IX. Datenspeicherung/Folge von Löschanträgen
--------------------------------------------

Unser Ziel ist es, personenbezogene Daten nur zu speichern, soweit dies notwendig ist. Wenn wir personenbezogenen Daten im Rahmen dieser Datenschutzrichtlinien nicht mehr benötigen, werden wir sie bei Gelegenheit löschen oder anonymisieren. Sollte die Löschung oder Anonymisierung deiner personenbezogenen Daten wirtschaftlich nicht sinnvoll sein, werden wir deine personenbezogenen Daten der Verarbeitung entziehen und sie sicher aufbewahren, bis wir in der Lage sind, sie dauerhaft zu löschen. Beachte bitte, dass Daten möglicherweise gespeichert bleiben, weil wir sie aufgrund gesetzlicher Vorgaben oder für unsere Buchhaltung, zur Streitbeilegung, zur Durchsetzung unserer Nutzungsbedingungen, zur Wahrung unserer gesetzlichen Rechte oder zur Erfüllung technischer und rechtlicher Vorgaben und Beschränkungen benötigen. Aufzeichnungen über Zahlungen und Sachverhalte mit Relevanz für den Kundenservice etwa bleiben möglicherweise gespeichert. Inhalte, die du an die Dienste gesandt oder auf ihnen gepostet hast, können wir möglicherweise nicht löschen. Für eine effektive Löschung musst du möglicherweise Schritte unternehmen, etwa die Löschung von Apps und/oder Inhalten mit Bezug zu den Diensten von deinem Gerät, und/oder die Trennung der Dienste von deinen Nutzerkonten auf sozialen Netzwerken. Beachte bitte, dass bei einem Antrag auf Löschung deines Kontos dein gesamter Spielfortschritt und sämtliche ungenutzten virtuellen Gegenstände dauerhaft verloren gehen. Produkte und Überbleibsel aus deiner Spielaktivität wie z. B. Basen, Charaktere, Schiffe, Vorräte usw. können im Spiel erhalten bleiben (und weiterhin verwendet werden, d. h. von aktiven Spieler/innen zerstört oder genutzt werden), auch nachdem dein Konto und/oder deine personenbezogenen Daten gelöscht oder vom Spiel getrennt wurde/n.

X. Rechtliche Grundlagen für europäische Länder und Nutzer
----------------------------------------------------------

Wenn du in einem Land der Europäischen Union, des Europäischen Wirtschaftsraums oder in der Schweiz ansässig bist, gelten für dich die folgenden rechtlichen Grundlagen für unsere Verarbeitung deiner Daten.

* Vertragliche Notwendigkeit. Dies umfasst Daten, die wir verwenden, um dir Dienste bereitzustellen, die du angefordert hast und deren Bereitstellung wir zugestimmt haben, wie etwa unsere Spiele, unser Kundenservice und die Chat-Funktion.
* Gesetzliche Verpflichtung. Dies umfasst Daten, die wir verwenden, um gesetzliche Verpflichtungen zu erfüllen. Dazu gehören etwa Aufzeichnungen, die für steuerliche Angelegenheiten oder für die Beantwortung von rechtlich zulässigen Abfragen von Daten notwendig sind.
* Berechtigte Interessen. Dies umfasst Daten, die wir für Zwecke verwenden, die durch deine Nutzung der Dienste als vorausgesetzt betrachtet werden können und von denen wir annehmen, dass sie deine Privatsphäre nicht beeinträchtigen. Dazu gehören Analysen zur Navigation unserer Nutzer auf unseren Websites und in unseren Apps, die Gewährleistung der Sicherheit unserer Websites und Apps, die Überprüfung und Optimierung unserer Dienste, die Bereitstellung einer stärker personalisierten Nutzererfahrung sowie Marketing und Werbung.

Einverständnis. In Fällen, in denen wir Daten aufgrund deines Einverständnisses verarbeiten, fragen wir nach deinem ausdrücklichen Einverständnis. Du kannst dein Einverständnis jederzeit widerrufen, dies hat jedoch keinen Einfluss auf die Rechtmäßigkeit der Verarbeitung deiner personenbezogenen Daten vor einem solchen Widerruf.

Du kannst jederzeit, wie in diesen Datenschutzrichtlinien erläutert, dein Einverständnis widerrufen oder bestimmten Arten der Datenverarbeitung widersprechen. Wenn du die Dienste nach solchen Anfragen nach wie vor nutzt, werden wir weiterhin personenbezogene Daten von dir erheben und verarbeiten, wie es anderweitig in diesen Datenschutzrichtlinien dargelegt ist. Wenn du grundsätzlich nicht möchtest, dass wir personenbezogene Daten von dir sammeln, solltest du unsere Spiele und unsere Dienste nicht mehr nutzen.

XI. Nutzer und Nutzerrechte in europäischen Ländern
---------------------------------------------------

Wenn du in einem Land der Europäischen Union, des Europäischen Wirtschaftsraums oder in der Schweiz ansässig bist, hast du bestimmte Rechte in Bezug auf die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir von dir gespeichert haben. Diese Rechte führen wir unten auf, sie unterliegen Ausnahmen gemäß anwendbaren Datenschutzgesetzen. Manche gelten nur unter bestimmten Umständen, Näheres hierzu ist unten aufgeführt. Wir legen auch dar, wie du diese Rechte ausüben kannst. Beachte bitte, dass wir von dir möglicherweise eine Bestätigung deiner Identität anfordern, bevor wir auf Anträge zur Ausübung deiner Rechte reagieren. Wir werden auf deinen Antrag zur Ausübung deiner Rechte unverzüglich und spätestens innerhalb eines Monats reagieren (diese Frist kann sich unter bestimmten Umständen allerdings um zwei weitere Monate verlängern). Sende zur Ausübung deiner Rechte bitte eine E-Mail an [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Wir können unter bestimmten Umständen die Bearbeitung von Anträgen ablehnen, etwa dann, wenn Anträge nachweislich unbegründet oder unverhältnismäßig sind, oder wenn sie die Privatsphäre Dritter beeinträchtigen.

### A. Löschung deiner personenbezogenen Daten

Unter bestimmten Umständen kannst du die Löschung mancher der personenbezogenen Daten beantragen, die wir von dir gespeichert haben. Möchtest du eine Löschung deiner personenbezogenen Daten veranlassen, kontaktiere uns bitte unter [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Beachte bitte, dass eine Bearbeitung deines Antrags und die Löschung der Daten voraussetzt, dass du unsere Apps/Spiele von deinen Mobilgeräten löschst und unsere Cookies von allen Geräten entfernst, auf denen du unsere Spiele genutzt hast. Du musst auch sämtliche funktionalen Links zu den Diensten in den Nutzerkonten deiner sozialen Netzwerke löschen. Wenn wir Daten löschen, werden sie in unseren aktiven Datenbanken gelöscht, verbleiben aber möglicherweise in unseren Archiven. Möglicherweise bleibt ein Teil oder die Gesamtheit dieser Daten aber zu anderen Zwecken gespeichert, etwa für Bilanzen, die Wahrung oder Durchsetzung gesetzlicher Ansprüche, Opt-out-Listen für Werbung, oder aus technischen Gründen, z. B. zur Gewähr der technischen Sicherheit oder der Richtigkeit unserer Datenbanken. Ebenso können deine Daten in anonymisierter Form gespeichert bleiben. Weiter oben unter „Datenspeicherung/Folge von Löschanträgen“ findest du weitere Informationen zu Löschanträgen.

### B. Zugriff und Übertragbarkeit

Du hast ein Recht darauf zu erfahren, welche Daten wir über dich gespeichert haben, und in manchen Fällen ein Recht darauf, dass dir diese Daten übermittelt werden. Möchtest du dieses Recht ausüben, kontaktiere uns bitte unter [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) und teile uns mit, dass du dein Zugriffsrecht ausüben möchtest und genau welche Daten du erfragen möchtest. Möglicherweise können wir dir nicht alle Daten übermitteln, deren Übermittlung du wünschst, z. B. dann, wenn die Daten personenbezogene Daten einer anderen Person enthalten.

Unter bestimmten Umständen kannst du die Daten, die wir mit deinem Einverständnis oder zur Erfüllung unseres Vertrages mit dir verarbeiten, in einem strukturierten, gängigen und maschinenlesbaren Format anfordern, oder die Übertragung solcher personenbezogener Daten an eine andere Partei beantragen. Deine Rechte unterliegen Ausnahmen unter anwendbaren Datenschutzgesetzen.

Wenn du die Übertragung der personenbezogenen Daten an eine andere Partei von uns wünschst, benenne bitte diese Partei und bedenke, dass wir diesem Wunsch nur unter dem Vorbehalt der technischen Machbarkeit entsprechen können. Sobald die andere Partei die personenbezogenen Daten erhalten hat, sind wir für deren Sicherheit oder Verarbeitung nicht mehr verantwortlich.

Möglicherweise stellen wir dir im Rahmen anwendbarer Datenschutzrechte bestimmte Daten nicht zur Verfügung, weil deren Übermittlung die Rechte einer anderen Person verletzen würde. Dies gilt z. B. dann, wenn die Übermittlung deiner bei uns gespeicherten personenbezogenen Daten Informationen über eine andere Person oder unsere Betriebsgeheimnisse oder intellektuelles Eigentum preisgeben würde.

### C. Berichtigung

Du hast das Recht, inkorrekte personenbezogene Daten, die bei uns gespeichert sind, zu berichtigen. Wenn du eine Berichtigung anfragst, erkläre uns bitte detailliert, warum du die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir über dich gespeichert haben, für inkorrekt oder unvollständig hältst. Wir prüfen dann, ob eine Berichtigung erforderlich ist.

### D. Beschränkung der Verarbeitung ausschließlich für die Speicherung

Unter bestimmten Umständen hast du das Recht, uns die Verarbeitung der personenbezogenen Daten, die wir über dich gespeichert haben, für andere Zwecke als den der Speicherung zu untersagen. Dies betrifft z. B. Fälle, in denen wir die Korrektur oder die Löschung der Daten prüfen, oder wenn wir aufgrund deines Widerspruchs die dauerhafte Unterlassung der Verarbeitung prüfen. Sollten wir die Verarbeitung der personenbezogenen Daten einstellen, verwenden wir sie jedoch möglicherweise erneut, wenn hierfür berechtigte Gründe vorliegen (z. B. für die Geltendmachung rechtlicher Ansprüche oder zum Schutz eines Dritten).

### E. Widerspruch

Du hast das Recht, einer Verarbeitung von Daten über dich durch uns zu widersprechen, die nicht für die Erfüllung unserer Nutzungsbedingungen erforderlich ist.

Du hast auch das Recht, unserer Verarbeitung von Daten über dich durch eine E-Mail an [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) zu widersprechen, wenn wir die Daten, die wir über dich gespeichert haben, aufgrund berechtigter Interessen verarbeiten und du eine solche Verarbeitung ablehnst. Bitte nenne uns Gründe für deine Argumentation, damit wir prüfen können, ob wir ein zwingendes übergeordnetes Interesse daran haben, diese Daten weiterhin zu verarbeiten, oder ob wir sie im Zusammenhang mit Rechtsansprüchen verarbeiten müssen.

### F. Beschwerden

Wenn du eine Beschwerde gegen unsere Verarbeitung deiner personenbezogenen Daten einlegen willst, kontaktiere uns bitte unter [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com); wir werden auf dein Anliegen reagieren. Solltest du der Meinung sein, dass wir gegen Datenschutzrecht des EU-Staates verstoßen haben, in dem du lebst oder arbeitest, bleibt dein Recht auf die Geltendmachung von Ansprüchen bei der zuständigen Datenschutzbehörde jenes Staates hiervon unberührt.

XII. Deine Datenschutzrechte in Kalifornien
-------------------------------------------

Wenn du in Kalifornien ansässig bist, stehen dir infolge einer nachweisbaren Verbraucheranfrage von deiner Seite mit Gültigkeit ab 1. Januar 2020 untenstehende Rechte zu (für diese Rechte gelten jedoch bestimmte gesetzlich erlaubte Ausnahmen):

* Auskunft. Du kannst Auskunft über folgende Informationen bezüglich unserer Sammlung und Verwendung deiner personenbezogenen Daten während der letzten 12 Monate verlangen: Die Kategorien der personenbezogenen Daten gemäß des Verbraucherdatenschutzgesetzes für Kalifornien (California Consumer Privacy Act, CCPA), die wir gesammelt haben, die Kategorien der Quellen, von denen wir personenbezogene Daten erhoben haben, der Geschäfts- oder Handelszweck für die Sammlung und/oder den Verkauf von personenbezogenen Daten, die Kategorien von Dritten, denen wir personenbezogene Daten übertragen haben, um dir unsere Dienste bereitstellen zu können. Wenn du uns um Löschung eines Teils oder aller deiner Daten ersuchst, kannst du möglicherweise nicht mehr auf die Dienste zugreifen und sie nicht mehr nutzen.
* Gleichbehandlung. Du hast bei der Ausübung der oben genanten Rechte Anspruch auf Schutz vor diskriminierenden Praktiken, die nach kalifornischem Recht verboten sind.

Ausübung deiner Rechte. Du kannst deine oben genannten Datenschutzrechte nach kalifornischem Recht ausüben, indem du uns bei Gelegenheit via E-Mail unter [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) oder über die im Spiel bereitgestellten Kontaktwege eine Nachricht sendest. Zur Bearbeitung deiner Anfragen bezüglich der Ausübung deiner Rechte auf Auskunft, Zugriff oder Löschung müssen wir deine Identität und deine Ansässigkeit in Kalifornien überprüfen. Wir können deine Anfrage nur bearbeiten, wenn du uns in angemessenem Umfang Einzelheiten nennst, die es uns erlauben, sie zu verstehen und auf sie zu reagieren.

Reaktionszeit. Wir streben eine Reaktionszeit von 45 Tagen oder weniger nach Erhalt einer Verbraucheranfrage auf Zugriff oder Löschung an. Wenn wir mehr Zeit benötigen, werden wir dich schriftlich über den Grund und die Dauer informieren.

Personenbezogene Daten, die wir sammeln, verwenden und teilen. Wir erläutern weiter oben in diesen Datenschutzrichtlinien die Quellen, aus denen wir personenbezogene Daten erheben, und die Geschäfts- und Handelszwecke für die Sammlung dieser Daten.

Wir verkaufen deine personenbezogenen Daten nicht an Dritte. Wir übermitteln personenbezogene Daten an Dritte zu den in diesen Datenschutzrichtlinien erläuterten Geschäfts- und Handelszwecken. Dazu gehören unter anderem die Bewerbung und die Vermarktung unserer Dienste.

XIII.  Aktualisierung unserer Datenschutzrichtlinien
----------------------------------------------------

Diese Datenschutzrichtlinien können bei Gelegenheit von uns aktualisiert werden, damit wir unserer Verpflichtung zum Datenschutz gerecht werden. Aktualisierungen gelten stets für die Zukunft und niemals rückwirkend. Wenn wir Veränderungen vornehmen, aktualisieren wir das Datum oben auf dieser Seite und ergreifen angemessene Maßnahmen um dich zu informieren, wenn die Änderungen wesentlich sind. Wir empfehlen dir, diese Seite häufig zu besuchen, um über Änderungen auf dem Laufenden zu bleiben.

Wir ermöglichen dir ein individuelles Opt-out oder Opt-in, ehe wir deine Daten an Dritte, die nicht unsere Beauftragten sind, weitergeben, oder ehe wir sie für einen Zweck verwenden, für den sie ursprünglich nicht erhoben oder im Folgenden autorisiert wurden. Möchtest du die Verwendung und Weitergabe deiner personenbezogenen Daten begrenzen lassen, sende bitte eine schriftliche Anfrage an privacy@kixeye.com.

XIV. Kontakt
------------

Wenn du Fragen in Bezug auf diese Datenschutzrichtlinien hast, kannst du per E-Mail an [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) mit uns Kontakt aufnehmen. Unser Datenschutzbeauftragter ist per E-Mail an [dpo@kixeye.com](mailto:dpo@kixeye.com) erreichbar.

Informativa sulla privacy di KIXEYE Inc.
========================================

Ultimo aggiornamento: 23 giugno 2023

I. Introduzione alla nostra Informativa sulla privacy
-----------------------------------------------------

Noi di KIXEYE Inc. ("noi" o "KIXEYE") prendiamo&nbsp molto sul serio i videogiochi. E facciamo sul serio anche per quanto riguarda la tua privacy e i tuoi diritti sui dati. Ci impegniamo a mantenere con gli utenti un rapporto di fiducia e trasparenza. Questa Informativa sulla privacy è scritta in un linguaggio semplice per facilitare la comprensione del modo in cui raccogliamo, usiamo, conserviamo e condividiamo le informazioni che identificano gli utenti ("dati personali" – con “dati personali” si indicano anche, in base al contesto, “le informazioni personali” come stabilito dall'Atto di protezione della privacy del consumatore della California (California Consumer Privacy Protection Act) del 2018 e/o dal Regolamento generale della protezione dei dati della CE) quando accedono ai nostri siti web, alle applicazioni mobili, ai giochi, ai forum o ad altri servizi (collettivamente i "Servizi"). Quando utilizzi un Servizio, acconsenti ogni volta alla raccolta, utilizzo e divulgazione delle informazioni (inclusi la registrazione e il tracciamento) descritti nella presente Informativa sulla privacy. Ti preghiamo di leggerla attentamente. SE NON ACCETTI LA PRESENTE INFORMATIVA SULLA PRIVACY, NON POTRAI USARE ALCUN SERVIZIO.

II. Quali informazioni/dati personali raccogliamo?
--------------------------------------------------

### A. Le informazioni fornite direttamente dall'utente.

Quando interagisci con un sito web di proprietà di KIXEYE o scarichi il Servizio da un app store di terze parti, raccogliamo e memorizzeremo le tue informazioni direttamente come descritto di seguito, nella misura in cui sono a nostra disposizione. Raccogliamo le informazioni che ci fornisci e questi dati possono includere:

* Nome
* Indirizzo e-mail
* Informazioni sull'account KIXEYE, come nome utente, ID o avatar univoci
* Il tuo ID da vari “social network” (inclusi Facebook, Apple iTunes, Google Play, Steam, ecc.)
* Potremmo anche offrirti la possibilità di completare un profilo utente visibile agli altri utenti del Servizio. Il tuo profilo utente può includere: un'immagine del profilo; uno o più nomi utente del Servizio e un numero ID utente KIXEYE creato da KIXEYE e utilizzato per identificare il tuo profilo.
* Informazioni di pagamento o fatturazione
* I messaggi inviati a noi o ai Servizi (registri di chat, richieste di assistenza clienti)
* Informazioni che ci aiutano a verificare l'identità degli utenti, a prevenire le frodi e a sviluppare e migliorare i nostri Servizi.

### B. Informazioni raccolte automaticamente.

Raccogliamo automaticamente altre informazioni dal tuo dispositivo tramite cookie e altri mezzi (SDK, pixel di tracciamento ecc.) quando utilizzi i nostri Servizi, inclusi, nella misura in cui sono disponibili e quando richiesto, previo consenso:

* Indirizzo IP
* Dati di posizione generali, informazioni sul dispositivo (tipo di dispositivo, modello, sistema operativo, versione del browser o identificatori univoci del dispositivo per verificarne la compatibilità e IDFA o GAID)
* IDFA sta per Identificatore per inserzionisti su Apple e GAID sta per Identità pubblicitaria di Google. Questi identificatori univoci non sono permanenti, né personali, nel senso che non contengono informazioni sensibili sull'utente, ma consentono di garantire la coerenza tra tutte le app e il monitoraggio tra app. È possibile disattivare la condivisione dell'identificatore del dispositivo modificando le impostazioni sul dispositivo.
* Comunicazioni di servizio (messaggi di gioco, registri di chat)
* Tipo di connessione

### C. Informazioni fornite a noi da terzi.

Potremmo avere accesso a determinate informazioni dell'utente raccolte da terze parti, inclusi i social network, mediante l'utilizzo dei loro servizi, siti web, applicazioni o altro.

### D. Informazioni che raccogliamo in merito al tuo account.

Creeremo e assegneremo al tuo dispositivo un identificatore simile a un numero di conto. Raccoglieremo anche le seguenti informazioni su di te, nella misura in cui sono disponibili e, se necessario, in base al tuo consenso:

* Nome utente nel gioco;
* Tipo di dispositivo; modello; sistema operativo; memoria; conservazione;
* Numero di telefono;
* Paese, regione, città;
* Nome utente, nome del personaggio;
* Lingua;
* Indirizzo e-mail;
* I tuoi contatti per consentirti di invitare amici a unirsi a te nel Servizio.

Quando utilizzi i nostri Servizi, raccoglieremo informazioni sui modi in cui usi e interagisci con i nostri Servizi, per esempio quando e per quanto tempo il tuo dispositivo è connesso ai nostri giochi, le funzionalità di gioco a cui accedi e altri giocatori con cui interagisci, gli acquisti in-app che effettui, i progressi o i livelli raggiunti e altre attività di gioco.

Raccogliamo anche statistiche di utilizzo pseudonime sulle tue interazioni con il Servizio. Queste informazioni vengono in genere raccolte tramite l'uso di file di registro del server o file di registro web, kit di sviluppo software per dispositivi mobili e tecnologie di tracciamento come i cookie del browser per raccogliere e analizzare determinati tipi di informazioni tecniche. Alcuni dei cookie che il Servizio inserisce sul tuo computer sono collegati al tuo numero (o numeri) ID utente. 

### E. Informazioni raccolte attraverso la tua partecipazione alle community

Quando utilizzi il Servizio, avrai accesso alla community di gioco online all'interno del Servizio, che ti dà l'opportunità di comunicare o condividere informazioni non solo con noi, ma anche con altri utenti del nostro Servizio attraverso:

* Partecipazione ai forum dei giocatori e alle bacheche dei messaggi;
* Pubblicazione di commenti pubblici su profili di altri utenti o bacheche del gioco;
* Invio di messaggi privati o inviti ad altri utenti, direttamente sui nostri siti web o ai loro account di posta elettronica;
* Chat con altri utenti; e
* Inserimento di link web.

Quando partecipi alle community di gioco online, noi accediamo e archiviamo informazioni/dati personali su di te. Le informazioni che memorizziamo variano a seconda del gioco/dell'applicazione e dipendono dalle impostazioni sulla privacy che tu e i tuoi amici stabilite in quel gioco/applicazione. Puoi controllare e scoprire di più su queste impostazioni all'interno dell'applicazione. Raccoglieremo le seguenti informazioni:

* Nome utente nel Servizio;
* ID inserzionista del tuo dispositivo;
* A seconda di come accedi ai Servizi, ID utente di Facebook;
* Indirizzo IP dei tuoi dispositivi di accesso;
* Le tue chat e i messaggi di gioco;
* Se forniti da te, il tuo indirizzo e-mail e il tuo numero di telefono;
* Avatar inviati.

### F. Informazioni di pagamento

Raccoglieremo anche alcune informazioni sugli acquisti (che consistono nella cronologia delle transazioni, incluso ciò che hai acquistato, il prezzo e la data). Tieni presente che le tue transazioni di acquisto nel gioco e/o in-app vengono elaborate da processori di pagamento di terze parti, come Apple (per acquisti su dispositivi iOS), Google (per acquisti su dispositivi Android). Questi processori di pagamento di terze parti sono il “commerciante registrato” per i tuoi acquisti e non condividono le tue informazioni finanziarie, come i numeri delle carte di credito, con noi.

### G. Corrispondenza con l'assistenza clienti

Quando chiedi aiuto al nostro team di assistenza clienti, raccogliamo e archiviamo:

* Nome e indirizzo e-mail;
* Informazioni sulla tua attività sul Servizio;
* Nome utente o numero ID;
* Qualsiasi corrispondenza connessa all'assistenza fornita.

### H. Informazioni che non raccogliamo mai.

Non raccogliamo alcuna "categoria speciale”di informazioni da o su di te, ovvero dati o informazioni razziali riguardanti l'origine etnica, le pratiche o l'orientamento sessuale, le opinioni politiche, le credenze religiose o filosofiche, l'appartenenza a un sindacato o i dati sanitari ecc.

III. Come e perché utilizziamo queste informazioni/questi dati personali?
-------------------------------------------------------------------------

Utilizziamo i tuoi dati personali e le informazioni non personali per:

### A. Fornirti i nostri Servizi.

* Comunicare con te in base alle tue preferenze e ai nostri Termini di servizio.
* Gestire, sviluppare, manutenere e migliorare i nostri Servizi.
* Fornire assistenza ai clienti relativa ai Servizi.
* Risolvere le controversie e far rispettare i nostri Termini d'uso.
* Rendere disponibili per te offerte di gioco speciali/promozionali.
* Riscuotere quote, pagamenti e altri importi dovuti in relazione ai Servizi.
* Permettere agli utenti di collegarsi tra loro.
* Creare un account utente per utilizzare i Servizi.
* Fornire la versione appropriata dei Servizi, anche nella lingua preferita.
* Identificare, correggere e risolvere i bug e gli errori del Servizio.
* Sviluppare nuovi Servizi.

### B. Proteggere i nostri Servizi.

* Identificare e/o prevenire le frodi.
* Identificare e/o prevenire la violazioni dei Termini di servizio, attività illegali o frodi.
* Verificare le identità degli utenti per le comunicazioni dell'assistenza clienti.
* Monitorare, garantire e migliorare la sicurezza della nostra rete e dei nostri sistemi informativi.

### C. Personalizzare i nostri Servizi o le offerte promozionali.

* Fornirti avvisi, esperienza di gioco personalizzata e altre offerte.
* Comunicare con l'utente in merito alle sue aree di interesse e rispondere alle sue richieste.
* Servire, ottimizzare e misurare l'efficacia delle nostre campagne di marketing.
* Effettuare analisi per il marketing interno e studi demografici per migliorare o personalizzare i Servizi.
* Salvare i progressi e le statistiche del gioco.

### D. Legale/Altro.

Utilizziamo i tuoi dati personali e le informazioni non personali anche per:

* Rispettare gli obblighi legali.
* Esercitare, stabilire o difendere i nostri Termini di servizio e altri diritti legali.
* Nei casi in cui riteniamo in buona fede la necessità di proteggere la sicurezza, o interessi importanti o finanziari dell'utente, nostri o di qualsiasi altra persona.

IV. Con chi condividiamo queste informazioni/dati personali?
------------------------------------------------------------

Salvo quanto descritto di seguito, non condivideremo i dati personali dell'utente con terze parti non affiliate senza richiedere il consenso. Tuttavia, possiamo condividere dati non personali, inclusi dati anonimi, aggregati o pseudonimizzati in conformità con la presente Informativa sulla privacy. Potremmo condividere le informazioni dell'utente, inclusi i dati personali con terzi nei seguenti casi:

### A. Fornitori di servizi di terze parti.

Potremmo stipulare un contratto con terze parti per raccogliere o elaborare le tue informazioni o i tuoi dati personali per nostro conto al fine di fornire Servizi di provider di hosting per archiviare i dati personali che fornisci e per i servizi di ripristino di emergenza, nonché per l'esecuzione di qualsiasi contratto che stipuliamo con te, servizi di consegna di posta elettronica e società di analisi (elaborazione della carta di credito, invio di e-mail al servizio clienti). I nostri accordi con tali terze parti richiedono loro di proteggere la riservatezza e la sicurezza dei dati personali e delle informazioni in linea con la presente Informativa sulla privacy. Non condividiamo le informazioni personali con terzi per fini commerciali senza il consenso dell'utente.

### B. Società affiliate di KIXEYE.

Facciamo parte del gruppo di società StillFront AB. Potremmo condividere le tue informazioni tra le nostre società consociate, genitori o affiliate per fornire e/o migliorare i nostri Servizi e arricchire la tua esperienza e le offerte personalizzate.

### C. Successore di acquisizione di terze parti.

Se KIXEYE effettua una fusione con una terza parte, viene acquisita, acquistata (in tutto o in parte), viene ceduta, effettua una riorganizzazione, si verifica un fallimento o un evento simile, le informazioni raccolte ai sensi della presente Informativa sulla privacy possono essere condivise con tale terza parte. L'utente riceverà tutte le informazioni del caso.

### D. Come richiesto dalla legge.

Possiamo divulgare i dati personali se riteniamo, in buona fede, di essere obbligati a farlo per:

* Rispettare un obbligo legale.
* Proteggere e difendere i diritti o la proprietà di KIXEYE, degli utenti dei Servizi o di altri.
* Proteggere la sicurezza personale o interessi importanti o finanziari degli utenti dei Servizi o del pubblico.
* Proteggere da responsabilità legale.
* Monitorare la conformità con e l'applicazione dei nostri Termini di servizio, delle norme o delle regole del forum/della community.
* Rispondere a richieste legittime da parte delle autorità pubbliche, comprese le forze dell'ordine o della sicurezza nazionale.

V. Come proteggiamo e archiviamo i dati personali?
--------------------------------------------------

### A. Protezione dei dati personali.

Utilizziamo misure di sicurezza ragionevoli per proteggere la sicurezza delle tue informazioni sia online che offline e ci impegniamo a proteggere le informazioni del cliente/utente. Sebbene prendiamo ragionevoli precauzioni contro possibili violazioni della sicurezza dei nostri Servizi e dei database e archivi dei nostri clienti, non possiamo garantire che non si verificheranno mai accessi non autorizzati, episodi di pirateria informatica, perdita di dati o altre violazioni. Sfortunatamente, la trasmissione di informazioni su Internet non è mai completamente sicura. Sebbene ci sforziamo di proteggere i tuoi dati personali, non possiamo garantirne la sicurezza dei mentre vengono trasmessi al nostro sito; quindi qualsiasi trasmissione viene effettuata a proprio rischio. Ti invitiamo a prendere provvedimenti per mantenere le tue informazioni personali al sicuro (inclusa la password del tuo account) e a uscire dal tuo account dopo l'uso. Se il tuo account viene violato, ciò potrebbe comportare un accesso non autorizzato a esso, quindi ti preghiamo di proteggere le informazioni del tuo account.

### A. Conservazione dei dati personali.

I dati personali che raccogliamo, vengono condivisi con noi o vengono elaborati ai sensi della presente Informativa sulla privacy, possono essere archiviati negli Stati Uniti o in qualsiasi altro paese in cui operiamo noi, le nostre consociate/affiliate o i fornitori di Servizi di terze parti, anche attraverso l'uso di cloud storage. Utilizzando i Servizi, acconsenti al trasferimento dei dati personali e non personali negli Stati Uniti e in altri paesi, che potrebbero non offrire lo stesso livello di protezione della privacy delle leggi del tuo paese di residenza o cittadinanza. Di conseguenza, le tue informazioni potrebbero essere accessibili da autorità governative straniere o, in altro modo, in conformità con le leggi locali applicabili.

VI. Controllo sulla privacy
---------------------------

L'utente ha il controllo sulla raccolta e sull'utilizzo dei propri dati personali. Può in qualsiasi momento accedere o modificare i dati personali, limitarne la raccolta o l'elaborazione e, in alcuni casi, richiederne la disattivazione o la cancellazione permanente. Per richiedere l'accesso, la modifica, la limitazione, la disattivazione o la cancellazione dei dati personali, contattaci all'indirizzo [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Prima di elaborare qualsiasi richiesta, potremmo chiederti di verificare la tua identità per proteggere la tua privacy. Ciò può includere la comunicazione tramite la piattaforma dei Servizi o altri metodi di verifica dell'identità.

Le richieste non verificate, irragionevoli o impraticabili possono essere respinte. Per proteggere l'account dell'utente, le richieste di disattivazione o cancellazione dei dati personali richiedono un'ulteriore verifica, che può includere una sospensione temporanea dell'account e dei Servizi. Una volta elaborate le richieste di disattivazione o eliminazione, queste sono permanenti e i dati personali e l'account non potranno più essere ripristinati.

VII. Bambini di età inferiore ai 13 anni
----------------------------------------

I nostri Servizi non sono diretti a o intesi per i bambini di età inferiore ai 13 anni. Non raccogliamo consapevolmente Dati personali, informazioni personali, foto, video, file audio o dati sulla posizione di bambini di età inferiore ai 13 anni o utilizziamo consapevolmente identificatori persistenti per riconoscere i bambini di età inferiore ai 13 anni nel tempo e attraverso diversi siti web o Servizi online. Se hai meno di 13 anni, non utilizzare i nostri Servizi e non inviarci alcuna informazione. Incoraggiamo i genitori e i tutori legali a monitorare l'utilizzo di Internet dei propri figli e a contribuire a far rispettare la presente Informativa sulla privacy istruendo i minori di 13 anni a non utilizzare mai i nostri Servizi. Se si ha motivo di credere che un bambino di età inferiore ai 13 anni abbia fornito Dati personali o informazioni personali a KIXEYE attraverso i nostri Servizi, basta contattarci all'indirizzo [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) e provvederemo a eliminare tali informazioni dai nostri database il più presto possibile.

VIII. Pratiche e Informative sulla privacy di terze parti/social network
------------------------------------------------------------------------

La presente Informativa sulla privacy si applica solo ai dati personali e alle informazioni raccolti da KIXEYE attraverso l'utilizzo dei Servizi. I siti web di terzi possono essere accessibili tramite collegamenti durante l'utilizzo dei nostri Servizi oppure è possibile che l'utente abbia raggiunto, effettuato l'accesso e scaricato i nostri Servizi tramite siti web di terzi. Questi siti web di terze parti sono regolati dalle rispettive informative sulla privacy e non siamo responsabili per i contenuti visualizzati su tali siti web o su eventuali pratiche sulla privacy o sulla sicurezza adottate da tali siti web. Per gestire le informazioni che KIXEYE riceve su di te dai social network in cui utilizzi i nostri Servizi, dovrai seguire le istruzioni nei relativi siti per aggiornare le tue informazioni e modificare le Impostazioni sulla privacy. Gli strumenti di gestione della privacy per le applicazioni su Apple sono disponibili all'indirizzo [http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/). Gli strumenti di gestione della privacy per Google sono disponibili su [https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/). Puoi gestire alcuni aspetti della raccolta e dell'utilizzo delle informazioni accedendo alle impostazioni del tuo dispositivo (mobile) ed esaminando le autorizzazioni di ciascuna applicazione.

Una volta che KIXEYE riceve le tue informazioni dai social network, tali informazioni vengono memorizzate e utilizzate da KIXEYE in conformità con la presente Informativa sulla privacy e puoi accedere e aggiornare tali informazioni come descritto di seguito. Gli account creati con KIXEYE sono considerati attivi finché non riceviamo una richiesta dell'utente per eliminarli o disattivarli.

IX. Conservazione dei dati/Effetto delle richieste di cancellazione
-------------------------------------------------------------------

Ci sforziamo di conservare solo la quantità di dati personali necessaria. Quando i dati personali non saranno più necessari ai sensi della presente Informativa sulla privacy, li cancelleremo periodicamente o li anonimizzeremo. Quando non è commercialmente ragionevole eliminare o anonimizzare i dati personali, li rimuoveremo dall'elaborazione e li conserveremo in modo sicuro fino a quando non saremo in grado di eliminarli definitivamente. Ti preghiamo di notare che possiamo conservare le informazioni necessarie per scopi legali e contabili, per risolvere controversie, far rispettare i nostri accordi con gli utenti, proteggere i nostri diritti legali e rispettare requisiti e vincoli tecnici e legali. Per esempio, possiamo conservare registrazioni relative a pagamenti o questioni relative al servizio clienti. Se hai inviato o pubblicato contenuti sul Servizio, potremmo non essere in grado di eliminarli. L'eliminazione efficace potrebbe richiedere azioni da parte tua, come l'eliminazione di app e/o contenuti relativi al Servizio dal tuo dispositivo e/o lo scollegamento del Servizio dai tuoi account di social network. Tieni presente che se ci chiedi di eliminare il tuo account, tutti i tuoi progressi nel gioco e tutti gli oggetti virtuali inutilizzati andranno persi definitivamente. Ricorda che i risultati e i manufatti nel gioco, per es. basi, personaggi, navi, rifornimenti ecc. possono rimanere attivi nel gioco (e soggetti al gioco, ovvero distruzione o sfruttamento da parte di giocatori attivi) anche dopo che il tuo account e/o i tuoi dati personali sono stati cancellati o dissociati dal gioco.

X. Basi legali per gli utenti dei paesi europei
-----------------------------------------------

Se ti trovi in un paese dell'Unione Europea, dello Spazio Economico Europeo o della Svizzera, le seguenti sono le basi legali su cui facciamo affidamento per elaborare le tue informazioni.

* Necessità contrattuale. Ciò copre i dati da noi utilizzati per fornirti i Servizi che hai richiesto - e che abbiamo concordato - come i nostri giochi, servizi clienti e funzionalità di chat;
* Obbligazione legale. Ciò copre i dati da noi utilizzati per ottemperare a obblighi legali, come per esempio mantenere i registri relativi alle imposte o per rispondere a richieste legali valide per determinati dati;
* Interessi legittimi. Ciò copre i dati da noi utilizzati per scopi che ci si può ragionevolmente aspettare con l'utilizzo dei nostri Servizi e che non riteniamo siano dannosi per la tua privacy, come l'analisi per capire come i nostri utenti navigano nei nostri siti web e nelle app, per mantenere i nostri siti web e app sicuri e protetti, ricerca e ottimizzazione del nostro Servizio, per fornire un'esperienza maggiormente personalizzata, marketing e pubblicità;

Consenso. Nei casi in cui trattiamo i dati sulla base del tuo consenso, chiederemo il tuo esplicito consenso. Puoi revocare il consenso in qualsiasi momento, ma ciò non pregiudica la liceità del trattamento dei tuoi dati personali prima di tale revoca.

Sebbene tu possa revocare il tuo consenso oppure opporti a determinati tipi di trattamento in qualsiasi momento nei modi descritti nella presente Informativa sulla privacy, tieni presente che se continui a utilizzare i Servizi dopo tali richieste, riprenderemo a raccogliere dati personali su di te e a elaborarli come altrimenti descritto nella presente Informativa. Se non desideri che raccogliamo alcun dato personale su di te, dovrai interrompi qualsiasi gioco e utilizzo dei nostri Servizi.

XI. Diritti degli utenti dei paesi europei
------------------------------------------

Se ti trovi in un paese nell'Unione Europea, nello Spazio economico europeo o in Svizzera, hai determinati diritti in relazione ai dati personali che deteniamo su di te, che dettaglieremo di seguito e che sono soggetti a esenzioni ai sensi delle leggi applicabili sulla privacy dei dati. Alcuni di questi si applicano solo in determinate circostanze, come illustrato più dettagliatamente di seguito. Abbiamo inoltre stabilito come esercitare tali diritti. Tieni presente che potremmo richiederti di verificare la tua identità prima di rispondere a qualsiasi richiesta di esercizio dei tuoi diritti. Risponderemo alla tua richiesta di esercitare tali diritti senza indebito ritardo e almeno entro un mese (sebbene ciò possa essere prorogato di altri due mesi in determinate circostanze). Per esercitare i tuoi diritti, invia un'e-mail a [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Potremmo rifiutarci di elaborare le richieste in determinate circostanze, per esempio quando le richieste sono manifestamente infondate o eccessive o mettono a rischio la privacy di altri.

### A. Cancellazione dei dati personali

In alcune circostanze, potresti richiedere la cancellazione di alcuni dei dati personali che deteniamo su di te. Se desideri che i tuoi dati personali vengano cancellati, contattaci all'indirizzo [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Tieni presente che per elaborare la tua richiesta e garantire l'eliminazione, dovrai eliminare le nostre app/giochi dai tuoi dispositivi mobili e cancellare i nostri cookie da qualsiasi dispositivo su cui hai giocato ai nostri giochi. È inoltre necessario rimuovere tutti i collegamenti alle funzionalità del Servizio dagli account dei social network. Quando cancelliamo le informazione, verranno cancellata dai nostri database attivi ma potrebbero rimanere nei nostri archivi. Ti preghiamo di notare, tuttavia, che potremmo ancora conservare alcune o tutte queste informazioni per altri scopi come la conservazione di registri finanziari, la protezione o l'applicazione di diritti legali, il mantenimento di elenchi di soppressione del marketing o per motivi tecnici come il mantenimento della sicurezza tecnica o l'integrità del nostro database. Potremmo anche conservare le tue informazioni in forma anonima. Vai alla voce “Conservazione dei dati/Effetto delle richieste di cancellazione” sopra per ulteriori informazioni sulle richieste di eliminazione.

### B Accesso e portabilità

Hai il diritto di sapere quali informazioni conserviamo su di te e, in alcuni casi, di farti comunicare le informazioni. Se desideri esercitare questo diritto, contattaci all'indirizzo [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) e facci sapere che desideri esercitare il tuo diritto di accesso e precisamente quali informazioni stai richiedendo. Ricorda che potremmo non essere in grado di fornire tutte le informazioni richieste, per esempio se queste includono informazioni personali su un'altra persona.

In alcune circostanze, puoi richiedere i dati che elaboriamo in base al consenso o per eseguire il nostro contratto con te in un formato strutturato, di uso comune e leggibile da una macchina oppure puoi richiedere il trasferimento di tali dati personali a un'altra parte. I tuoi diritti sono soggetti a esenzioni ai sensi delle leggi applicabili sulla privacy dei dati.

Se desideri che trasferiamo i dati personali a un'altra parte, assicurati di fornire tutti i dettagli sulla suddetta parte e ricorda che possiamo farlo solo quando è tecnicamente possibile. Non siamo responsabili della sicurezza dei dati personali o del loro trattamento una volta ricevuti dalla terza parte.

Potremmo inoltre non fornirti determinati dati se farlo interferisse con i diritti di un altro (p. es. laddove fornire i dati personali in nostro possesso rivelerebbe informazioni su un'altra persona o sui nostri segreti commerciali o proprietà intellettuale) come consentito dai diritti di protezione dei dati applicabili.

### C. Correzione

Hai il diritto di correggere qualsiasi dato personale in nostro possesso che reputi impreciso. Laddove richiederai la correzione, spiega in dettaglio perché ritieni che i dati personali che deteniamo su di te siano inaccurati o incompleti in modo che possiamo valutare se sia necessaria una correzione.

### D. Limitazione dell'elaborazione alla sola conservazione

Hai il diritto di richiederci di interrompere l'elaborazione dei dati personali che deteniamo su di te per scopi diversi da quelli di archiviazione in determinate circostanze, p es. mentre valutiamo se debbano essere corretti o eliminati o, in base alla tua obiezione, se dobbiamo interromperne definitivamente l'elaborazione. Ti preghiamo di notare, tuttavia, che se interrompiamo l'elaborazione dei dati personali, potremmo utilizzarli di nuovo se ci sono motivi validi per farlo (per esempio per la difesa di rivendicazioni legali o per la protezione di altri).

### E. Obiezione

Hai il diritto di opporti al trattamento dei tuoi dati diverso da dove richiesto per eseguire i nostri Termini di servizio.

Hai anche il diritto di opporti al trattamento dei tuoi dati inviandoci un'e-mail a [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) se stiamo elaborando i dati in nostro possesso sulla base del nostro legittimo interesse e vuoi opporti a tale trattamento. Ti preghiamo di fornirci dettagli sul tuo ragionamento in modo che possiamo valutare se esiste un interesse prevalente impellente nel continuare a trattare tali dati o se necessitiamo di elaborarli in relazione a rivendicazioni legali.

### F. Reclami

Se desideri presentare un reclamo su come trattiamo i tuoi dati personali, ti preghiamo di contattarci all'indirizzo [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) e faremo il possibile per rispondere ai tuoi dubbi. Ciò non pregiudica il tuo diritto di avviare un reclamo presso l'autorità di controllo della protezione dei dati nel paese dell'UE in cui vivi o lavori in cui ritieni che abbiamo violato le leggi sulla protezione dei dati.

XII. I tuoi diritti alla privacy in California.
-----------------------------------------------

A partire dal 1° gennaio 2020, se risiedi in California, e su tua richiesta verificabile di consumatore, hai i diritti elencati di seguito (tuttavia, questi diritti sono soggetti ad alcune eccezioni consentite dalla legge):

* Informazione. Puoi richiedere le seguenti informazioni su come abbiamo raccolto e utilizzato le tue informazioni personali negli ultimi 12 mesi: le categorie di “informazioni personali” (come previsto dal CCPA) che abbiamo raccolto; le categorie di fonti da cui abbiamo raccolto le informazioni personali; lo scopo aziendale o commerciale per la raccolta e/o la vendita di informazioni personali; le categorie di terze parti con le quali condividiamo le informazioni personali in modo che possiamo fornirti i nostri servizi. Se ci chiedi di eliminare alcune o tutte le tue informazioni, potresti non essere più in grado di accedere o utilizzare i Servizi.
* Non discriminazione. Hai il diritto di esercitare i diritti sopra descritti senza pratiche discriminatorie proibite dalla legge della California.

Esercitare i tuoi diritti. Puoi esercitare i tuoi diritti alla privacy della California descritti sopra inviandoci un'e-mail a [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) o ai metodi di contatto nel gioco di volta in volta. Dovremo confermare la tua identità e la tua residenza in California per elaborare le tue richieste di esercitare i tuoi diritti di informazione, accesso o cancellazione. Non possiamo elaborare la tua richiesta se non ci fornisci dettagli ragionevolmente sufficienti per permetterci di comprenderla e rispondere.

Tempi di risposta. Miriamo a rispondere a una richiesta di accesso o cancellazione da parte di un consumatore entro 45 giorni dalla ricezione della stessa. Se abbiamo bisogno di più tempo, ti informeremo del motivo e della proroga per iscritto.

Informazioni personali che raccogliamo, utilizziamo e condividiamo. Descriviamo le fonti da cui raccogliamo le informazioni personali e gli scopi aziendali e commerciali per i quali raccogliamo queste informazioni nei precedenti punti della presente Informativa sulla privacy.

Non vendiamo le tue informazioni personali a terzi. Condividiamo le informazioni personali con terze parti per gli scopi aziendali e commerciali descritti nella presente Informativa sulla privacy, inclusi, a titolo esemplificativo, pubblicità e marketing dei nostri Servizi.

XIII. Aggiornamenti all'Informativa sulla privacy
-------------------------------------------------

Di volta in volta, potremmo aggiornare questa Informativa sulla privacy per garantire al meglio la tutela della privacy. Gli aggiornamenti valgono per il futuro e non sono mai retroattivi. Quando effettuiamo modifiche, aggiorneremo la data nella parte superiore di questa pagina e faremo ogni ragionevole sforzo per informare l'utente in caso di modifiche sostanziali. Invitiamo l'utente a visitare questa pagina spesso per non perdere nessun aggiornamento su eventuali modifiche.

Prima di condividere i dati con terze parti diverse dai nostri agenti, o prima di utilizzarli per uno scopo diverso da quello per cui sono stati originariamente raccolti o successivamente autorizzati, daremo all'utente la possibilità di scegliere. Per richiedere di limitare l'uso e la divulgazione delle informazioni personali, ti preghiamo di inviare una richiesta scritta a [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

XIV. Contattaci
---------------

In caso di domande sulla presente Informativa sulla privacy, l'utente può scriverci all'indirizzo [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Per contattare il nostro responsabile della protezione dei dati, è possibile scrivere a [dpo@kixeye.com](mailto:dpo@kixeye.com).

KIXEYEプライバシーポリシー
================

最後更新日：2023年6月23日

I. 弊社のプライバシーポリシーについて
--------------------

KIXEYE Inc. （以下「弊社」または「KIXEYE」と呼ぶ）は、ゲームに対して真摯に取り組んでいる会社です。お客様のプライバシーとデータの権利に対しても同じであり、弊社はお客様と信頼と透明性がある関係を維持することをお約束します。本プライバシーポリシーは、お客様が弊社のウェブサイト、モバイルアプリケーション、ゲーム、フォーラム、またはその他のサービス（総称して「サービス」）にアクセスする際に、弊社がお客様を識別できる情報をどのように収集、使用、保管、および共有するかについて容易に理解できるように、わかりやすい言葉で書かれています（「個人データ」 – 「個人データ」は、文脈によって、2018年のカリフォルニア消費者プライバシー保護法および/またはEU一般データ保護規則に規定されている「個人情報」を意味する場合もあります）。弊社のサービスを使用する場合、本プライバシーポリシーに記載されている情報の収集、使用、開示（記録と追跡を含む）のそれぞれに同意するものとします。よくお読みください。本プライバシーポリシーに同意しない場合は、いかなるサービスも使用しないでください。

II. 収集する情報/個人データ
----------------

### A. お客様が直接弊社に提供する情報。

KIXEYEが所有するウェブサイトを使用する場合、または第三者のアプリストアから弊社のサービスをダウンロードする場合、以下で説明されるように、弊社に利用可能な範囲で直接お客様から情報を収集して保管します。その情報には以下が含まれる可能性があります。

* 氏名
* メールアドレス
* 固有のユーザー名やID、アバターのようなKIXEYEのアカウント情報
* 様々なソーシャルネットワーク（Facebook、Apple iTunes、Google Play、Steamなどを含む）からのID
* 他のサービスユーザーに表示されるユーザープロファイルを完成させるオプションを提供する場合もあります。 ユーザープロファイルには、1つ以上のサービスユーザー名、KIXEYEによって作成され、お客様プロファイルを識別するために使用されるKIXEYEユーザーID番号が含まれる場合があります。
* 支払や請求情報
* お客様からの弊社やサービスに対するメッセージ（チャットログ、カスタマーサポートへのリクエスト）
* お客様の本人識別、詐欺防止、サービス向上に役立つ情報

### B. 自動的に収集される情報。

弊社は、お客様が弊社のサービスを使用する際に、Cookieおよびその他の方法（SDK、トラッキングピクセルなど）を介してデバイスからその他の情報を自動的に収集致します。これには、利用可能な範囲で、必要に応じてお客様の同意が必要な以下の情報が含まれます。

* IPアドレス
* 一般的な位置データデバイス情報（デバイスの種類、モデル、OS、ブラウザのバージョン、デバイス互換性確認およびIDFA/GAID向けのデバイス固有の識別子など）
* IDFAはアップルの広告主向け識別子、GAIDはグーグル広告IDの略です。こうした固有の識別子は非永続、非個人的です。お客様のプライベートな情報を含んでいませんが、すべてのアプリとクロスアプリトラッキングでの一貫性を実現します。お客様はデバイスの設定をアップデートすることで、識別子の共有を停止できます。
* サービスコミュニケーション（ゲーム内メッセージ、チャットログ）
* 接続タイプ

### C. 第三者から弊社に提供される情報。

弊社は、お客様がソーシャルネットワークを含む第三者のサービス、ウェブサイト、アプリケーションや他のサービスを利用中に集められた特定の情報に対し、アクセスする場合があります。

### D. お客様のアカウントに関して収集する情報。

弊社は、アカウント番号に類似した識別子を作成してデバイスに割り当てます。 また、利用可能な範囲で、必要に応じて、お客様の同意に基づいて、お客様に関する以下の情報を収集致します。

* ゲームのユーザー名
* デバイスタイプ、モデル、オペレーティング・システム、メモリ、 ストレージ
* 電話番号
* 国、地域、都市
* ユーザー名、キャラクター名、
* 言語
* メールアドレス
* サービスに友達を招待するために使用する連絡先。

お客様が弊社のサービスを使用する場合、その使用および操作方法に関する情報を収集します。その情報の例としては、お客様のデバイスが弊社のゲームにログインする時間と期間、アクセスするゲーム機能、および操作する他のプレーヤーなど、アプリ内での購入、達成した進捗状況やレベル、その他のゲームプレイアクティビティが挙げられます。

また、お客様の本サービスとの使用状況に関する仮名の使用統計も収集します。 この情報は通常、サーバーログファイルまたはウェブログファイル、モバイルデバイスソフトウェア開発キット、および特定の種類の技術情報を収集および分析するためのブラウザCookieなどの追跡テクノロジーを用いて収集されます。 本サービスがお客様のコンピューターに配置するCookieの一部は、ユーザーID番号にリンクされています。

### E. コミュニティへの参加を通じて収集される情報

本サービスでは、オンラインゲームコミュニティにアクセスできます。これにより、以下を通じて弊社だけでなく他のユーザーと情報を伝達または共有する機会が得られます。

* プレイヤーフォーラムや掲示板への参加
* 他のプロフィールやゲームボードへのパブリックコメントの投稿
* 弊社のウェブサイトまたはそのEメールアカウントのいずれでの、他のユーザーへのプライベートメッセージまたは招待状の送信
* 他のユーザーとのチャット
* ウェブリンクの投稿

お客様がオンラインゲームコミュニティに参加する際、弊社はお客様に関する情報/個人データにアクセスして保管します。弊社が保管する情報はゲーム/アプリケーションによって異なり、お客様と友人がそのゲーム/アプリケーションで確立するプライバシー設定の影響を受けます。弊社は、以下の情報を収集致します。

* サービス内のユーザー名
* デバイスの広告ID
* サービスへのログイン方法に応じて、FacebookユーザーID
* アクセスデバイスのIPアドレス
* ゲーム内のチャットとメッセージ
* 提供された場合、お客様のEメールアドレスと電話番号。
* アバター

### F. 支払い情報

弊社は、いくつかの購入情報（購入したもの、価格、日付などの取引履歴で構成される）も収集致します。ゲーム内および/またはアプリ内における購入取引は、Apple（iOSデバイスでの購入の場合）、Google（Androidデバイスでの購入の場合）などの第三者支払い処理業者によって処理されることにご注意ください。このような第三者支払い処理業者は、購入記録の責任者であり、クレジットカード番号などの財務情報を弊社と共有することはありません。

### G. カスタマーサポート対応

カスタマーサポートチームにサポートを依頼する場合、以下を収集して保管致します。

* 名前とEメールアドレス。
* 本サービスでにおけるお客様のアクティビティに関する情報
* ユーザー名またはID番号
* お客様に提供されるサポートに関連する情報

### H. 弊社が収集しない情報。

弊社はお客様の「特別カテゴリー情報」を一切収集しません。これは人種データや出身民族に関する情報、性的慣習や嗜好、政治的意見、宗教的や哲学的な信条、各種団体への加入、健康に関するデータを指します。

III. この情報/個人データの使用方法と理由
-----------------------

弊社は、お客様の個人データおよび非個人情報を以下の目的で使用します。

### A．お客様へのサービス提供。

* お客様の好みと弊社の利用規約に従ったサービスの提供。
* サービスの運用、改善、維持、向上。
* サービスに関するカスタマーサポートを提供します。
* 紛争を解決し、弊社の利用規約を施行します。
* ゲーム内でお客様が利用できるおける特別/プロモーションオファーの提供
* 料金、支払い金額、それ以外のサービス関連して請求された金額を集めます。
* 他のプレーヤーへの連絡を可能にします。
* サービスを利用するのに必要なユーザーアカウントを作成します。
* お好みの言語など、お客様に適したバージョンでのサービスを提供します。
* バグやサービスエラーの特定、修正、解決を行います。
* 新しいサービスの開発。

### B．弊社サービスの安全保持

* 詐欺を発見、防止します。
* 利用規約違反、違法行為、不正行為の特定および/または防止。
* カスタマーサポートへの連絡の際にユーザーIDを確認します。
* ネットワークや情報システムのセキュリティ監視、維持、強化。

### C．弊社のサービスやオファーPRのカスタマイズ。

* 通知、パーソナライズされたゲーム体験、その他のオファーの供。
* お客様の興味のある分野について伺い、ご要望にお応えします。
* マーケティングキャンペーンの効果の提供、最適化、測定。
* サービス開発、改善、またはパーソナライズを目的とした、内部マーケティングおよび人口統計調査の分析実行。
* ゲーム属性、進行状況、統計の保管、追跡。

### D．法律/その他。

弊社は、お客様の個人データおよび非個人情報を以下の目的でも使用致します。

* 法的義務を遵守します。
* 弊社の利用規約およびその他の法的権利を行使、確立、または防御するため。
* お客様、弊社、または第三者の安全、経済的または重要な利益を誠実に保護する必要性がある場合。

IV. 本情報/個人データを共有する人物
--------------------

以下に記載されている場合を除き、弊社はお客様の同意なしに個人データを関係のない第三者と共有することはありません。ただし、本プライバシーポリシーに従って、匿名化、集約化、偽名化されたデータなど非個人データを共有することはあります。個人データを含むお客様の情報を第三者に共有する場合は以下のとおりです：

### A. 第三者のサービスプロバイダー

弊社はサービスを提供するにあたり、お客様の情報ないし個人データの収集や処理といった業務の代行を第三者と契約することがあります。これにお客様が提供した個人データの保管、ディザスタリカバリサービス、およびお客様と締結した契約の履行を担うホスティングプロバイダー、Eメール配信サービス、分析会社（クレジットカード処理、カスタマーサービスメールの送信）などが含まれます。こうした第三者との契約では、本プライバシーポリシーに沿って、お客様の個人データおよび情報の機密性とセキュリティを守ることが第三者に義務付けられています。お客様の同意なしに、弊社がお客様へマーケティングを行う可能性がある第三者と個人情報を共有することはありません。

### B. KIXEYEの関連会社

弊社は、StillFrontABグループの一員です。弊社のサービスを改善し、お客様に合った体験やオファーを提供するために、KIXEYEの子会社、親会社、または関連会社間でお客様の情報を共有する場合があります。

### C. 後継者または第三者の買収。

KIXEYE（のすべてまたは一部）が第三者と合併するか、第三者に吸収、買収されるか、あるいは分割、組織再編、破産、またはそれと同様の事態が発生した場合、本プライバシーポリシーに基づいて収集された情報が、この第三者に共有される可能性があります。そのような場合には、弊社からお客様にご連絡致します。

### D. 法律で義務付けられている場合。

弊社は、以下の目的で法律により開示する義務がある場合、個人データを開示する場合があります。

* 法的義務を遵守する。
* KIXEYE、本サービスのユーザー、それ以外の者の権利あるいは財産を保護し、防御する。
* 本サービスのユーザーまたは一般の人々の安全、経済的または重要な利益を保護する。
* 法的責任から守る。
* 利用規約、ポリシー、またはフォーラム/コミュニティ規則の遵守を監視して施行する。
* 国家安全保障機関や法執行機関などの公的機関による合法的な要求に応じる。

V. 個人データの保管および保護方法
------------------

### A. 個人データの保護。

弊社は、オンラインとオフラインの両方でお客様の情報のセキュリティを保護するために合理的なセキュリティ対策を実行し、お客様/ユーザー情報の保護に取り組んでおります。本サービスおよびお客様のデータベースと記録のセキュリティ侵害の可能性に対して合理的な予防措置を講じていますが、不正アクセス、ハッキング、データ損失、またはその他の侵害が発生しないことを保証することはできません。残念ながら、インターネットを介した情報送信は完全に安全とは言い切れません。 弊社はお客様の個人データ保護に努めていますが、弊社のサイトに送信されている間のお客様のデータのセキュリティを保証することはできません。 したがって、送信によるデータ侵害はお客様の責任とします。個人情報（アカウントのパスワードを含む）を安全に保管し、使用後にアカウントからログアウトする措置を講じることをお勧めします。 お客様のアカウントがハッキングされた場合、アカウントへの不正アクセスに繋がる場合があるため、アカウント情報を安全に保管してください。

### B. 個人データの保管。

弊社が収集や共有した個人データ、または本プライバシーポリシーに基づいて処理された個人データは、クラウドストレージの使用を含め、弊社、弊社の子会社/関連会社、または第三者のサービスプロバイダーが事業を展開するアメリカまたはそれ以外の国に保管される場合があります。お客様が本サービスを利用すると、アメリカおよびお客様の居住国または市民権を有する国と法的に同レベルのプライバシー保護を提供していない可能性のある他の国へお客様の個人データおよび非個人データが転送されることに同意したとみなされます。その結果として、お客様の情報は、現地の適用法に従って、外国の政府当局によって、またはその他の方法でアクセスされる可能性があります。

VI. お客様による個人情報の管理
-----------------

お客様は、ご自身の個人データの収集および使用を管理でき、いつでも個人データへのアクセスや訂正ならびに収集や処理の制限、場合によっては個人データの停止や永久削除を要求することもできます。個人データへのアクセス、訂正、制限、停止、削除をご希望の場合は、[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)までご連絡ください。ご希望のプロセスを進めるにあたり、プライバシー保護の観点から、お客様の身元確認をお願いする場合があります。具体的な方法としては、本サービスプラットフォームを介した問い合わせやその他の方法による本人確認などがあります。

認証されない、不合理または非現実的なご要請は拒否される場合があります。お客様のアカウントを保護する関係から、個人データの無効化や削除のご要請には、追加の確認が必須であり、その際にお客様のアカウントおよびサービスが一時的停止となる場合があります。一度処理された無効化や削除の要請は撤回できず、個人データとアカウントは復元できなくなります。

VII.13歳未満のお子様について
-----------------

弊社のサービスは、13歳未満の子供たちに向けられたものでも、13歳未満の子供たちに魅力的なサービスを提供することを意図したものでもありません。弊社は、13歳未満のお子様の個人データ、個人情報、写真、動画、音声ファイル、位置情報をそうと知りながら収集したり、13歳未満のお子様を認識する永続的な識別子を様々なウェブサイトやオンラインサービスの間で故意に長期間使用したりすることはありません。13歳未満のお客様は、弊社のサービスを使わず、弊社に情報を送信しないでください。保護者様および法定後見人様には、お子様のインターネット利用状況を監督し、13歳未満のお子様が弊社のサービスを利用しないように指導して本プライバシーポリシーの履行に協力していただくことをお勧めします。13歳未満のお子様が弊社のサービスを通じてKIXEYEに個人データまたは個人情報を提供したと信じるに足る理由がある場合は、弊社へすみやかにご連絡ください。可能な限り速やかにその情報を弊社データベースから削除するための措置を講じます。

VIII. 第三者のプライバシーポリシーと慣行/ソーシャルネットワーク
-----------------------------------

本プライバシーポリシーは、KIXEYEがお客様による弊社サービスの使用を通じて収集した個人データおよび情報にのみ適用されます。当社のサービスを使用する際に、リンクから第三者のウェブサイトにアクセスできる場合、または第三者のウェブサイトから当社のサービスにアクセスし、ダウンロードできる場合があります。このようなサードパーティのウェブサイトは、独自のプライバシーポリシーに準拠しており、そのサードパーティウェブサイトに表示されるコンテンツ、またはプライバシーやセキュリティの慣行について弊社は責任を負わないものとします。お客様が弊社のサービスを使用するソーシャルネットワークからKIXEYEが受け取る情報を管理するためには、そのサイトの指示に従って情報を更新し、プライバシー設定を変更する必要があります。Appleのアプリケーションのプライバシー管理ツールは、[http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/)、Googleのプライバシー管理ツールは、[https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/からアクセスできます](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/)。（モバイル）デバイス設定に移動し、各アプリケーションのアクセス許可を確認することで、情報の収集と使用の特定の設定を管理できます。

一度KIXEYEがソーシャルネットワークからお客様情報を受け取ると、その情報は本プライバシーポリシーに従ってKIXEYEによって保管および使用され、お客様は、以下で説明されるように、その情報にアクセスして更新することができます。 KIXEYEで作成されたアカウントは、削除または非アクティブ化リクエストをお客様から受け取るまで、アクティブであると見なされます。

IX. データの保持/削除要請の影響
------------------

弊社は、必要な個人データだけをを保持するよう努めています。 本プライバシーポリシーで個人データが不要になった場合、定期的に削除または匿名化を行います。お客様の個人データを削除または匿名化することが商業的に合理的でない場合、弊社はお客様の個人データを処理を停止し、完全に削除できるようになるまで安全に保管致します。 紛争の解決、ユーザー契約施行、弊社の法的権利の保護、技術的および法的要件と制約の遵守のために、法的および会計上の目的で必要な情報を保持する場合があることをご了承ください。 例えば、支払いやカスタマーサービスの問題に関する記録を保持する場合があります。 また、本サービスにコンテンツを送信または投稿した場合、削除できない場合があります。効果的な削除には、デバイスからの本サービスに関連するアプリやコンテンツの削除、ソーシャルネットワークアカウントからの本サービスのリンク解除など、ユーザー側でのアクションが必要になる場合がございます。アカウント削除を依頼した場合、ゲームのデータはすべて失われ、未使用の仮想アイテムも永久に失われることをご理解ください。アカウントや個人データがゲームから削除または切り離された後も、基地、キャラクター、船、物資などのゲームの結果とアーティファクトはゲーム内で継続的に使用される可能性があります（ゲームプレイの対象、つまりアクティブなプレーヤーによる破壊または悪用の対象となる）。

X. ヨーロッパ諸国のユーザーに対する法的根拠
-----------------------

欧州連合、欧州経済領域の国、またはスイスにお住まいの場合、以下は、お客様の情報を処理する際に当社が依存する法的根拠です。

* 契約上の必要性：これには、ゲーム、カスタマーサービス、チャット機能など、お客様が要求した、および弊社がお客様に提供することに同意したサービスを提供するために当社が使用するデータが含まれます。
* 法的義務：これは、税金に関連する記録を維持するため、または特定のデータに対する有効な法的要求に対応するためなど、法的義務を遵守するために弊社が使用するデータを対象とします。
* 正当な利益：これは、ユーザーが弊社のサービスを使用することで合理的に取得することが期待でき、ユーザーが弊社ウェブサイトやアプリを使用する方法を理解するための分析、当サイトを安全に維持するための分析、よりパーソナライズされた体験、マーケティング、広告を提供するためのサービス調査と最適化など、お客様のプライバシーに害を及ぼすとは考えられない目的で当社が使用するデータを対象とます。

同意：お客様の同意に基づいてデータを処理する場合、弊社は明示的な同意を求めます。 お客様はいつでも同意を撤回することができますが、撤回前のお客様の個人データの処理の合法性に影響を与えません。

本プライバシーポリシーに記載されている方法で、いつでも特定の種類の処理に対する同意または異議を申し立てを行うことができますが、かかる要求の後に本サービスを継続して使用する場合は、本プライバシーポリシーに別段の記載がない限り、お客様に関する個人データの収集を再開致します。お客様が弊社による自身の個人データ収集を望まない場合、すべてのゲームプレイおよび当サービスの使用を停止して頂く必要があります。

XI. ヨーロッパ諸国のユーザー権利
------------------

お客様が欧州連合、欧州経済領域の国、またはスイスにお住まいの場合、当社が保持するお客様の個人データに関して一定の権利を有します。これについては、以下で詳しく説明しますが、該当するデータプライバシー法の下で免除の対象となり、これらの一部は特定の状況でのみ適用されます。 また、これらの権利を行使する方法についても説明致します。弊社が権利行使の要請に応じる前に、本人確認を実施する場合がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。お客様からのかかる権利行使の要請に、遅滞なく、少なくとも1か月以内に対応致します（状況によってはさらに2か月延長される場合がある）。 お客様の権利を行使するには、privacy @ kixeye.comにお問い合わせください。

要請が明らかに根拠のない、または過度である場合や、他者のプライバシーを危険に晒す要請など、特定の状況では、その処理を拒否する場合があります。

### A. 個人データの削除

状況によっては、弊社が保持しているお客様の個人データの一部を消去するように要求できる場合があります。 個人データの削除をご希望の場合は、[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)までお問い合わせください。

お客様の要求を処理して確実にデータ削除するには、モバイルデバイスからアプリ/ゲームを削除し、ゲームをプレイしたデバイスからCookieを消去する必要があります。また、ソーシャルネットワークアカウント内のすべてのサービス機能リンクを削除する必要もあります。 情報を削除する際、アクティブなデータベースからは削除されますが、アーカイブに残る場合があります。ただし、財務記録の維持、法的権利の保護または履行、マーケティング抑制リストの維持、または技術的理由による技術的セキュリティやデータベースの整合性の維持など、その情報の一部またはすべてを保持する場合があることをご了承ください。さらに、匿名化された形式でお客様の情報を保持する場合がございます。 削除要請の詳細については、上記のデータの保持/削除要請の影響を参照してください。

### B アクセスと移植性

お客様には、弊社がお客様についてどのような情報を保持しているかを知る権利があり、場合によっては、その情報を伝達される権利もあります。本権利を行使したい場合は、[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)までご連絡頂き、アクセス権を行使したいこと、および正確にどの情報を要求しているかをお知らせください。他者の個人情報が含まれている場合など、ご希望の情報をすべてご提供できない場合がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。

場合によってお客様は、同意に基づいて処理されるデータのを要求、または構造化され、一般的に使用される機械読み取り可能な形式での契約履行のため、そのような個人データを別の当事者に転送するためにデータを要求できる場合があります。お客様の権利は、適用されるデータプライバシーおよび法律の下で免除の対象となります。ータを別の当事者に転送することを要求するために。

お客様が自身の個人データを他の当事者に転送することを希望する場合は、その当事者を明確にし、技術的に可能な場合にのみ転送できることに注意してください。 当社は、第三者が受け取った個人データまたはその処理のセキュリティについて責任を負いません。

また、該当するデータ保護権で許可されているように、提供することで他人の権利を妨げる場合（弊社が保持する個人データを提供すると、他者、企業秘密または知的財産に関する情報が明らかになる場合など）、特定のデータを提供しない場合があります。

### C. 修正

お客様には、弊社が保持している不正確な個人データを修正する権利があります。 修正を希望する場合は、その必要性を判断できるよう、弊社が保有するお客様の個人情報が不正確または不完全である理由を詳しく説明してください。

### D. 処理を保管のみに制限

お客様には、特定の状況における保管目的以外で、当社が保持するお客様の個人データの処理を停止するよう要求できる権利があります（弊社は、修正または削除する必要があるかどうか、またはお客様の異議に基づいて、処理を完全に停止する必要があるかどうかなどについては検討致します）。ただし、個人データの処理を停止した場合でも、正当な理由がある際（法的請求の防御や他者の保護など）に、個人データを再度使用する場合があることをご了承ください。

### E. 異議申し立て

お客様は、弊社の利用規約に基づいて実行する必要がある場合を除き、お客様に関するデータ処理に異議を唱える権利を有しています。

また、弊社が正当な利益に基づいて保持しているデータを処理しており、そのような処理に異議を申し立てる場合は、[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)にEメールを送信してお客様に関するデータの処理に異議を申し立てる権利があります。弊社がそのようなデータの処理を継続することに優先する利益があるかどうか、または法的請求に関連して処理する必要があるかどうかを評価できるように、その理由の詳細をお知らせください。

### F. 苦情

お客様の個人データ処理方法に対して弊社に苦情を申し立てる場合は、[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)までご連絡ください。お客様の懸念に全力で対応できるよう努めます。これは、弊社がデータ保護法に違反していると思われることに対して、居住または勤務しているEU加盟国のデータ保護監督当局に申し立てを行う権利を損なうものではありません。

XII. カリフォルニアプライバシー権利
--------------------

2020年1月1日より、カリフォルニア州の住民である場合、検証可能な消費者の要求に応じて、以下に示す権利を保持します（ただし、これらの権利は法律で許可されている特定の例外の対象となります）。

* 情報：過去12か月間に弊社がお客様の個人情報をどのように収集および使用したかについて、下記の情報を要求できます - 弊社が収集した「個人情報」のカテゴリ」（CCPAで意図されている）、 個人情報を収集したソースのカテゴリ、個人情報を収集および/または販売するビジネスまたは商業目的、当社が個人情報を共有する第三者のカテゴリー（弊社がお客様にサービスを提供するため）。 お客様の情報の一部または全部を削除するよう弊社に依頼した場合、本サービスにアクセスまたは使用できなくなる可能性があります。
* 無差別：お客様は、カリフォルニア州法で禁止されている差別的慣行を受けることなく、上記の権利を行使する権利を保持します。

権利の行使：上記のカリフォルニア州のプライバシー権を行使するには、[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)に問い合わせるか、ゲーム内の連絡方法でお問い合わせください。お客様の情報権、アクセス権、または削除権を行使するための要請を処理するには、お客様の身元とカリフォルニア州在住を確認する必要があります。処理のために必要な十分な詳細を提供しない場合、弊社はお客様の要求を処理することができません。

応答時間：弊社は、アクセスまたは削除の消費者の要求を受け取ってから45日以内に応答することを目指しています。 追加の時間が必要な場合は、理由と延長を書面でお知らせ致します。

弊社が収集、使用、共有する個人情報：上記のプライバシーポリシーで、個人情報を収集するソースと、この情報を収集するビジネスおよび商業目的について説明しています。

弊社は、お客様の個人情報を第三者に販売することはありません。 本プライバシーポリシーに記載されているビジネスおよび商業目的で、弊社のサービスの広告およびマーケティングを含むがこれらに限定されない個人情報を第三者と共有致します。

XIII. プライバシーポリシーの更新
-------------------

弊社はプライバシー保護を維持するために、本プライバシーポリシーを随時更新します。更新は今後も適用され、決して遡って適用されることはありません。変更があった場合は、このページの上部にある日付が更新され、重要な変更があった場合にはお知らせするために合理的な努力を致します。このページを時折、閲覧して最新の変更点を確認することをお勧めします。

弊社がお客様のデータを弊社の代理人以外の第三者と共有する場合や、当初収集された目的以外に使用するか、後から許可された目的に使用する場合には、前もって拒否ないし受諾の選択肢をお客様に提供致します。個人データの使用と開示の制限を希望される場合は、[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)に書面で要請書を提出してください。

XIV. 問い合わせ
----------

このプライバシーポリシーについてのご質問は、[privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)までメールにて、お問い合わせください。当社のデータ保護責任者へ連絡したい場合は、[dpo@kixeye.com](mailto:dpo@kixeye.com)までメールにて、お問い合わせください。

KIXEYE Inc. 개인 정보 보호 정책
=======================

최종 업데이트 : 2023 년 6 월 23 일

I. 개인 정보 보호 정책 소개
-----------------

KIXEYE Inc. ("우리" 또는 "KIXEYE")는 게임에 대해 진지합니다. 그리고 귀하의 개인 정보 및 데이터 권리를 중요하게 생각합니다. 우리는 신뢰할 수 있고 투명한 관계를 귀하와 유지하기 위해 최선을 다하고 있습니다. 본 개인 정보 보호 정책은 귀하가 우리 웹사이트, 모바일 앱, 게임, 포럼 또는 그 외 서비스(통칭 "서비스")에 접근 시 식별할 수 있는 정보("개인 데이터" – “개인 데이터”는 문맥 상 2018년 캘리포니아 소비자 개인 정보 보호법 및/또는 EU 일반 데이터 보호 규정에 명시된 “개인 정보”를 의미할 수도 있음)를 우리가 어떻게 수집, 사용, 저장 및 공유하는지 쉽게 이해할 수 있도록 일반적인 언어로 작성되었습니다. 귀하가 서비스를 이용 시 귀하는 본 개인 정보 보호 정책에 설명된 정보 수집, 사용 및 공개(기록 및 추적 포함)에 각각 동의합니다. 본 문서를 자세히 읽어 보시기 바랍니다. 이 개인 정보 보호 정책에 동의하지 않는 경우, 그 어떤 서비스도 이용하지 마십시오.

II. 어떤 정보/개인 데이터를 수집하나요?
------------------------

### A. 귀하가 직접적으로 우리에게 제공하는 정보.

귀하가 KIXEYE 소유 웹사이트를 접하거나 제삼자 앱 스토어에서 서비스를 다운로드할 때, 당사는 우리가 사용할 수 있는 한도 안에서 아래에 설명된 바와 같이 귀하로부터 직접 정보를 수집하고 저장합니다. 우리는 귀하가 제공한 정보를 수집하며, 이는 다음과 같은 정보를 포함할 수 있습니다.

* 이름
* 이메일 주소
* 고유한 사용자 이름, ID, 또는 아바타와 같은 KIXEYE 계정 정보
* 귀하의 다양한 “소셜 네트워크” ID(Facebook, Apple iTunes, Google Play, Steam 등 포함)
* 우리는 또한 다른 서비스 사용자에게 표시되는 사용자 프로필을 작성하는 옵션을 제공할 수도 있습니다. 귀하의 사용자 프로필에는 다음이 포함될 수 있습니다. 프로필 이미지; 하나 이상의 서비스 사용자 이름; 그리고 KIXEYE에서 생성하여 귀하의 프로필을 식별하는 데 사용되는 KIXEYE 사용자 ID 번호.
* 결제 또는 청구 정보
* 귀하가 우리 또는 서비스로 보낸 메시지(채팅 로그, 고객 지원 요청)
* 귀하가 실제 사용자임을 확인하고 부정행위를 방지하며 서비스 개발 및 개선하는 데 도움이 되는 정보

### B. 자동으로 수집되는 정보.

우리는 귀하가 당사 서비스를 사용할 때, 사용 가능한 범위까지, 그리고 필요한 경우 귀하의 동의에 따라, 쿠키 및 기타 수단(SDK, 추적 픽셀 등)을 통해 귀하의 기기에서 자동으로 기타 정보를 수집합니다.

* IP 주소
* 일반 위치 데이터 기기 정보(예: 기기 유형, 모델, 운영 체제, 브라우저 버전 또는 기기 호환성 및 IDFA 또는 GAID 확인을 위한 고유 기기 식별자)
* IDFA는 Apple에서 광고주 식별자(Identifier for Advertisers)를 의미하고 GAID는 Google 광고 아이덴티티(Google Advertising Identity)를 의미합니다. 이러한 고유 식별자는 비영구적이고 비개인적이며, 사용자에 대한 민감한 정보를 포함하지는 않지만 모든 앱과 교차 앱 추적에 걸쳐 일관성을 허용한다는 것을 의미합니다. 귀하는 자신의 기기 설정을 업데이트하여 기기 식별자 공유를 해제할 수 있습니다.
* 서비스 커뮤니케에션(인게임 메시지, 채팅 로그)
* 연결 타입

### C. 제삼자가 우리에게 제공한 정보.

우리는 귀하의 제삼자 서비스, 웹사이트, 애플리케이션 또는 기타 서비스 사용을 통해 제삼자가 귀하로부터 수집한 특정 정보에 접근할 수 있습니다.

### D. 귀하 계정 관련 우리가 수집하는 정보.

우리는 계정 번호와 유사한 식별자를 생성하여 귀하의 기기에 지정할 것입니다. 또한 우리는 귀하의 동의에 따라 이용 가능한 범위 내에서 필요한 경우 귀하에 대한 다음 정보를 수집합니다.

* 게임 사용자 이름;
* 기기 종류; 모델; 운영 체제; 메모리; 저장
* 전화번호;
* 국가; 지역; 도시;
* 사용자 이름, 캐릭터 이름;
* 언어;
* 이메일 주소; 및
* 친구를 서비스에 초대할 수 있는 연락처.

귀하가 당사 서비스를 사용할 때, 우리는 귀하의 기기가 당사의 게임에 접속된 시기와 기간, 귀하가 접근하는 게임 기능 및 귀하가 소통하는 다른 플레이어, 귀하의 인앱 구매, 진행 상황 또는 달성 레벨 및 기타 게임 플레이 활동 등 귀하가 당사 서비스를 사용하고 상호 작용하는 방식에 대한 정보를 수집합니다.

우리는 또한 귀하의 서비스 상호 작용에 대한 가명 사용 통계를 수집합니다. 이 정보는 일반적으로 서버 로그 파일 또는 웹 로그 파일, 모바일 기기 소프트웨어 개발 키트 및 브라우저 쿠키와 같은 추적 기술을 사용하여 특정 유형의 기술 정보를 수집하고 분석합니다. 서비스가 귀하의 컴퓨터에 저장하는 일부 쿠키는 귀하의 사용자 ID 번호와 연결됩니다.

### E. 귀하의 커뮤니티 참여를 통해 수집된 정보.

귀하가 본 서비스를 사용할 때 귀하는 서비스 내의 온라인 게임 커뮤니티에 접근하여 당사뿐만 아니라 당사 서비스의 다른 사용자와 소통하거나 정보를 공유할 수 있는 기회를 다음을 통해 얻게 됩니다.

* 플레이어 포럼 및 게시판 참여;
* 다른 사용자 프로필 또는 게임 게시판에 공개 댓글 게시;
* 다른 사용자에게 당사 웹 사이트에서 직접 또는 해당 사용자 이메일 계정으로 비공개 메시지 또는 초대 전송;
* 다른 사용자와 채팅; 및
* 웹 링크 게시.

귀하가 온라인 게임 커뮤니티에 참여 시 우리는 귀하에 대한 정보/개인 데이터에 접근하고 저장합니다. 우리가 저장하는 정보는 게임/애플리케이션에 따라 다르며 귀하와 귀하의 친구들이 해당 게임/애플리케이션에서 설정한 개인 정보 보호 설정의 영향을 받습니다. 귀하는 애플리케이션 내에서 이러한 설정을 제어하고 자세히 알아볼 수 있습니다. 우리는 다음 정보를 수집합니다.

* 귀하의 서비스 내 사용자 이름;
* 귀하의 기기 광고주 ID;
* 서비스에 로그인하는 방법에 따라 Facebook 사용자 ID;
* 귀하의 접근 기기들의 IP 주소;
* 귀하의 게임 내 채팅 및 메시지; 및
* 귀하가 제공한 경우, 귀하의 이메일 주소 및 전화번호.
* 제출된 아바타

### F. 결제 정보

우리는 또한 일부 구매 정보(귀하가 구매한 항목, 가격 및 날짜를 포함한 거래 내역으로 구성)를 수집합니다. 게임 내 및/또는 앱 내 구매 거래는 Apple(iOS 기기에서 구매), Google(Android 기기에서 구매)과 같은 제삼자 결제 프로세서에서 처리됩니다. 이러한 제삼자 결제 프로세서는 귀하의 구매에 대한 “기록 상 판매자”이며 신용 카드 번호와 같은 귀하의 금융 정보를 당사와 공유하지 않습니다.

### G. 고객 지원 서신

귀하가 당사 고객 지원 팀에 지원을 요청할 경우, 우리는 다음을 수집 및 저장합니다.

* 귀하의 이름 및 이메일 주소;
* 귀하의 서비스 상 활동 관련 정보;
* 귀하의 사용자 이름 또는 ID 번호; 및
* 귀하에게 제공된 지원에 관련된 모든 서신

### H. 우리가 절대 수집하지 않는 정보.

우리는 귀하로부터 또는 귀하에 대한 어떤 "특별 범주" 정보도 수집하지 않습니다. 이는 인종적 데이터나 인종적 기원, 성적 관행이나 성향, 정치적 의견, 종교적 또는 철학적 신념, 노조 가입 또는 건강 데이터에 관한 정보입니다.

III. 이 정보/개인 데이터를 어떻게 그리고 왜 사용하나요?
----------------------------------

우리는 다음을 위해 귀하의 개인 데이터 및 비개인 정보를 사용합니다.

### A. 우리의 서비스를 제공.

* 귀하의 선호도 및 당사 서비스 약관에 따라 귀하와 소통.
* 우리의 서비스를 운영, 개발, 유지 및 개선.
* 서비스를 위한 고객 지원 제공.
* 분쟁을 해결하고 우리의 서비스 약관 시행.
* 귀하에게 특별/홍보용 인게임 오퍼 제공.
* 서비스와 관련된 수수료, 지불금 및 기타 금액을 징수.
* 사용자가 다른 플레이어들과 연결될 수 있도록 함.
* 서비스 이용을 위해 사용자 계정 생성.
* 사용자 선호 언어를 포함해 사용자에게 적합한 서비스 버전 제공.
* 버그 및 서비스 오류 식별, 수정 및 해결.
* 신규 서비스 개발.

### B. 우리 서비스의 보안.

* 사기 식별 및/또는 예방.
* 서비스 약관 위반, 불법 활동이나 부정 행위 식별 및/또는 예방.
* 고객 지원 커뮤니케이션을 위한 사용자 신원 확인.
* 우리 네트워크와 정보 시스템의 보안을 감시, 보장 및 강화.

### C. 맞춤형 서비스 또는 프로모션 제공.

* 귀하에게 통지, 개인화된 게임 경험 및 기타 오퍼 제공.
* 귀하의 관심 영역에 대해 귀하와 소통하고 귀하의 요청에 응답.
* 우리 마케팅 캠페인의 효과를 제공, 최적화하고 측정.
* 내부 마케팅 및 인구 통계 연구에 대한 분석을 수행하여 서비스를 개발, 개선 또는 개인화.
* 귀하의 게임 속성, 진행도 및 상태를 저장하고 추적.

### D. 법률/기타.

우리는 또한 다음을 위해 귀하의 개인 데이터 및 비개인 정보를 사용합니다.

* 법적 의무 준수.
* 서비스 약관 및 기타 법적 권리를 행사, 설립 또는 변호.
* 귀하, 당사 또는 다른 사람의 안전, 재정적 또는 중요한 이익을 보호할 필요가 있다고 우리가 선의로 믿는 경우.

IV. 누구에게 이 정보/개인 데이터가 공유되나요?
----------------------------

아래 설명된 경우를 제외하고, 우리는 귀하의 동의 없이 귀하의 개인 데이터를 독립적인 제삼자와 공유하지 않을 것입니다. 그러나 이 개인 정보 보호 정책에 따라 익명, 집계 또는 가명화된 데이터를 포함한 비개인적 데이터는 공유할 수 있습니다. 우리는 다음과 같은 경우 개인 데이터를 포함한 귀하의 정보를 제삼자와 공유할 수 있습니다.

### A. 제삼자 서비스 제공자.

우리는 귀하가 제공하는 개인 데이터를 저장하는 호스팅 제공자 및 재해 복구 서비스, 또한 귀하와 맺는 모든 계약의 수행, 이메일 전달 서비스 및 분석 회사(신용카드 처리, 고객 서비스 이메일 전송) 등의 서비스 제공을 위해 당사를 대표하여 귀하의 정보 또는 개인 데이터를 수집 또는 처리할 목적으로 제삼자와 계약할 수 있습니다. 우리의 이러한 제삼자와의 계약은 본 개인 정보 보호 정책에 따라 제삼자가 귀하의 개인 데이터 및 정보의 기밀 및 보안을 유지하도록 요구합니다. 우리는 귀하의 동의 없이 제삼자가 귀하에게 광고할 수 있도록 제삼자와 개인 데이터를 공유하지 않습니다.

### B. KIXEYE 계열사.

우리는 StillFront AB 그룹의 일원입니다. 우리는 당사의 서비스를 제공 및/또는 개선하고 귀하에게 제공되는 개인화된 경험과 제안을 확장하기 위해 귀하의 정보를 당사의 자회사, 모회사 또는 계열사 간에 공유할 수 있습니다.

### C. 인수 제삼자의 후임.

KIXEYE가 제삼자와 합병되거나 취득, 구매(전체 또는 일부), 매각, 재편성, 파산 또는 이와 유사한 사건을 경험하는 경우, 본 개인 정보 보호 정책에 따라 수집된 정보는 해당 제삼자와 공유될 수 있습니다. 이런 일이 발생하면 사용자에게 알려드릴 것입니다.

### D. 법률에 따라 요구되는 경우.

우리는 다음과 같은 의무가 있다고 선의로 믿는 경우 개인 정보를 공개할 수 있습니다.

* 법적 의무 준수.
* KIXEYE, 서비스 사용자 또는 그 외 다른 사람들의 권리 또는 재산을 보호 및 방어.
* 서비스 사용자 또는 대중의 개인 안전, 재정적 또는 중요한 이익을 보호.
* 법적 책임으로부터의 보호.
* 서비스 약관, 정책 또는 포럼/커뮤니티 규칙 시행 및 준수 여부 감시.
* 국가 안보 또는 법률 집행 기관을 포함한 공공 기관의 합법적인 요청에 응답.

V. 사용자 개인 데이터 저장 및 보호 방법
------------------------

### A. 귀하의 개인 데이터 보호.

우리는 온라인과 오프라인 모두에서 귀하의 정보를 보호하기 위해 합리적인 보안 조치를 구현하고 고객/사용자 정보를 보호하기 위해 최선을 다하고 있습니다. 당사는 발생할 수 있는 서비스와 고객 데이터베이스 및 기록의 보안 침해에 대해 합리적인 예방 조치를 취하고 있으나, 무단 접근, 해킹, 데이터 손실 또는 기타 침해가 발생하지 않는다고 보장할 수는 없습니다. 안타깝게도 인터넷을 통한 정보 전송은 완전히 안전할 수가 없습니다. 우리는 귀하의 개인 데이터를 보호하기 위해 노력하고 있지만 당사 사이트로 전송되는 동안 귀하의 데이터의 보안을 보장할 수 없습니다. 따라서 모든 전송은 귀하에게 책임이 있습니다. 우리는 귀하가 개인 정보(계정 비밀번호 포함)를 안전하게 유지하기 위한 조치를 취하고, 사용 후 계정에서 로그아웃하실 것을 권고 드립니다. 계정이 해킹되면 계정에 대한 무단 접근으로 이어질 수 있으므로 계정 정보를 안전하게 보관하십시오.

### B. 귀하의 개인 데이터 저장.

우리가 수집하거나, 공유 받거나 또는 본 개인 정보 보호 정책에 따라 처리되는 개인 데이터는 미국 또는 우리의 자회사/계열사 또는 제삼자 서비스 제공자가 운영하는 다른 모든 국가에 저장될 수 있으며, 이에는 클라우드 스토리지 사용이 포함됩니다. 본 서비스를 이용함으로써 귀하는 귀하의 개인 데이터 및 비개인적 데이터를 귀하의 거주 국가 또는 귀하가 시민권을 가진 국가의 법률과 동일한 수준의 개인 정보 보호를 제공하지 않을 수 있는 미국 및 기타 국가로 이전하는 데 동의합니다. 따라서 귀하의 정보는 외국 정부 기관 또는 적용되는 지역 법률에 따라 접근될 수 있습니다.

VI. 사용자 개인 정보 제어
----------------

귀하는 귀하의 개인 데이터 수집 및 사용을 제어할 수 있습니다. 귀하는 언제든지 개인 데이터에 접근하거나 수정하고, 개인 데이터의 수집 또는 처리를 제한하고, 경우에 따라 개인 데이터의 비활성화 또는 영구 삭제를 요청할 수 있습니다. 귀하의 개인 데이터에 대한 접근, 수정, 제한, 비활성화 또는 삭제를 요청하려면 [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)으로 문의하십시오. 우리는 요청을 처리하기 전에 귀하의 개인 정보를 보호하기 위해 신원 확인을 요청할 수 있습니다. 여기에는 서비스 플랫폼을 통한 소통 또는 기타 신원 확인 방법이 포함될 수 있습니다.

증명되지 않았거나, 부당하거나 무리한 요청은 거절당할 수 있습니다. 귀하의 계정 보호를 위하여 계정 비활성화 혹은 개인 데이터 삭제 요청 시 추가 확인 절차가 필요하며, 이는 일시적인 사용자 계정 및 서비스 중단을 포함할 수 있습니다. 비활성화 혹은 삭제 요청이 처리되면 이는 영구적이며 해당 개인 데이터와 계정은 복구될 수 없습니다.

VII. 13세 미만 아동
--------------

우리의 서비스는 13세 미만 아동을 대상으로 하거나 끌어들이기 위해 의도하지 않습니다. 우리는 의도적으로 13세 미만 아동의 개인 데이터, 개인 정보, 사진, 영상, 음성 파일, 혹은 위치 데이터를 수집하거나 영구 식별자를 지속적으로 사용하여 다른 웹사이트나 온라인 서비스에서 13세 미만 아동들을 식별해내지 않습니다. 귀하가 13세 미만일 경우 본 서비스를 사용해서는 안 되며 우리에게 일체의 정보도 제공하지 마십시오. 우리는 부모와 법적 보호자들의 아동의 인터넷 사용에 대한 관찰을 권장하며, 해당 개인 정보 보호 정책의 준수를 위하여 13세 미만 아동의 본 서비스 이용을 금지하길 부탁드립니다. 13세 미만 아동이 개인 데이터나 개인 정보를 본 서비스를 통하여 KIXEYE에 제공했다고 추정되는 경우 [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)으로 문의하시면 최대한 빠른 시일 내로 해당 정보를 데이터 베이스에서 삭제하기 위한 절차를 밟게 됩니다.

VIII. 제삼자 개인 정보 보호 정책 및 관행/소셜 네트워크
----------------------------------

이 개인 정보 보호 정책은 귀하의 서비스 사용을 통해 KIXEYE가 수집한 개인 데이터 및 정보에만 적용됩니다. 제삼자 웹사이트는 우리 서비스를 사용할 때 링크를 통해 접근할 수 있으며, 귀하는 제삼자 웹사이트를 통해 우리 서비스에 도달, 접근, 다운로드했을 수 있습니다. 이러한 제삼자 웹사이트는 그 회사 자체 개인 정보 보호 정책의 적용을 받으며 당사는 해당 웹사이트에 나타나는 콘텐츠 또는 해당 웹사이트의 개인 정보 보호 또는 보안 관행에 대해 책임을 지지 않습니다. 귀하가 당사 서비스를 사용하는 소셜 네트워크에서 KIXEYE가 귀하에 대해 수신하는 정보를 관리하려면 해당 사이트의 지침에 따라 귀하의 정보를 업데이트하고 개인 정보 설정을 변경해야 합니다. Apple의 애플리케이션에 대한 개인 정보 관리 도구는 [http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/)에서 찾을 수 있습니다. Google 용 개인 정보 관리 도구는 [https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/)에서 찾을 수 있습니다. 귀하는 (모바일) 기기의 설정으로 이동 후 각 애플리케이션의 권한을 검토하여 정보 수집 및 사용의 특정 측면을 관리할 수 ​​있습니다.

KIXEYE가 소셜 네트워크에서 귀하의 정보를 수신하면 해당 정보는 본 개인 정보 보호 정책에 따라 KIXEYE에 의해 저장 및 사용되며 귀하는 아래에 설명된 대로 해당 정보에 접근하고 업데이트할 수 있습니다. KIXEYE에서 생성된 계정은 사용자의 삭제 또는 비활성화 요청을 받을 때까지 활성 상태로 간주됩니다.

IX. 데이터 보유/삭제 요청의 영향
--------------------

우리는 필요한 만큼의 개인 데이터만 보유하기 위해 노력하고 있습니다. 본 개인 정보 보호 정책에 따라 개인 데이터가 더 이상 필요하지 않은 경우 우리는 주기적으로 데이터를 삭제하거나 익명화할 것입니다. 귀하의 개인 데이터를 삭제하거나 익명화하는 것이 상업적으로 합리적이지 않은 경우 우리는 귀하의 개인 데이터를 처리에서 제거하고 영구적으로 삭제할 수 있을 때까지 안전하게 저장합니다. 우리는 법률 및 회계 목적, 분쟁 해결, 사용자 계약 시행, 우리의 법적 권리 보호, 기술 및 법적 요구와 제약 사항을 준수하는데 필요한 정보를 보유할 수 있음을 알려드립니다. 예를 들어, 우리는 결제 또는 고객 서비스 문제와 관련된 기록을 보유할 수 있습니다. 귀하가 서비스에 콘텐츠를 보내거나 게시한 경우 당사는 이를 삭제하지 못할 수 있습니다. 효과적인 삭제는 귀하의 기기에서 서비스와 관련된 앱 및/또는 콘텐츠를 삭제하거나 귀하의 소셜 네트워크 계정에서 서비스 연결을 해제하는 등 귀하의 조치가 필요할 수 있습니다. 귀하가 우리에게 계정 삭제를 요청하면 게임의 모든 진행도와 사용하지 않은 가상 아이템이 영구적으로 손실됨을 알려드립니다. 게임 내 플레이의 결과와 아티팩트, 예를 들어 기지, 캐릭터, 선박, 보급품 등은 귀하의 계정 및/또는 개인 데이터가 게임에서 삭제되거나 분리된 후에도 게임에 계속 남아있을 수 있습니다(그리고 게임 플레이, 즉 활성 플레이어에 의한 파괴 또는 착취 대상이 될 수 있음).

X. 유럽 국가 사용자를 위한 법적 근거
----------------------

귀하가 유럽 연합, 유럽 경제 지역에 있는 국가 또는 스위스에 거주하는 경우 우리가 귀하의 정보를 처리하는 데 사용하는 법적 근거는 다음과 같습니다.

* 계약상의 필요성. 여기에는 당사의 게임, 고객 서비스 및 채팅 기능과 같이 귀하가 우리에게 제공을 요청하고 우리가 귀하에게 제공을 동의한 서비스를 제공하기 위해 당사가 사용하는 데이터가 포함됩니다.
* 법적 의무. 여기에는 세금 관련 기록을 유지하거나 특정 데이터에 대한 유효한 법적 요청에 응답하는 등 법적 의무를 준수하기 위해 당사가 사용하는 데이터가 포함됩니다.
* 정당한 이익. 여기에는 귀하의 서비스 사용과 관련하여 합리적으로 예상할 수 있고 귀하의 개인 정보에 해롭지 않다고 생각되는 목적으로 당사가 사용하는 데이터가 포함되며, 이에는 사용자가 우리 웹사이트 및 앱을 탐색하는 방식을 이해하고, 우리 웹사이트 및 앱을 안전하고 안정적으로 유지하고, 우리 서비스를 연구 및 최적화하고, 더 개인화된 경험, 마케팅 및 광고를 제공하기 위한 분석 정보 등이 있습니다.

동의. 우리가 귀하의 동의를 기반으로 데이터를 처리하는 경우, 우리는 귀하의 명시적 동의를 요청할 것입니다. 귀하는 언제든지 동의를 철회할 수 있지만 철회 이전 귀하의 개인 데이터 처리의 합법성에 영향을 미치지는 않습니다.

귀하는 본 개인 정보 보호 정책에 설명된 방식으로 언제든지 특정 유형의 처리에 대한 귀하의 동의를 철회하거나 이의를 제기할 수 있지만, 그러한 요청 후에도 서비스를 계속 사용하면 귀하에 대한 개인 데이터 수집이 재개되며 이 개인 정보 보호 정책에 달리 설명된 대로 처리될 것입니다. 우리가 귀하에 대한 개인 데이터를 전혀 수집하지 않기를 원할 경우 귀하는 모든 게임 플레이 및 당사 서비스 사용을 중단해야 합니다.

XI. 유럽 국가 사용자 권한
----------------

귀하가 유럽 연합, 유럽 경제 지역에 있는 국가 또는 스위스에 거주하는 경우 귀하에 대해 우리가 보유하고 있는 개인 데이터와 관련하여 특정 권리가 있고, 이는 당사가 아래에 자세히 설명하고 있으며, 이는 적용 가능한 데이터 개인 정보 법률에 따라 면제 대상입니다. 이중 일부는 아래에 자세히 설명된 특정 상황에서만 적용됩니다. 우리는 또한 그러한 권리를 행사하는 방법을 제시하였습니다. 우리는 귀하의 권리 행사 요청에 응답하기 전에 귀하의 신원 확인을 요구할 수 있음을 알려드립니다. 당사는 부당한 지체 없이 최소한 1 개월 이내에 귀하의 이러한 권리 행사 요청에 응답할 것입니다(특정 상황에서는 2개월 더 연장될 수 있음). 귀하의 권리를 행사하려면 [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)으로 이메일을 보내주십시오.

우리는 명백한 근거가 없는 요청, 과도하거나 다른 사람의 개인 정보를 위협하는 요청과 같은 특정 상황에서 요청 처리를 거부할 수 있습니다.

### A. 귀하의 개인 데이터 삭제

경우에 따라 귀하는 우리가 귀하에 대해 보유하고 있는 일부 개인 데이터를 삭제하도록 요청할 수 있습니다. 개인 데이터를 삭제하려면 [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)으로 문의해 주십시오.

귀하의 요청을 처리하고 삭제를 확인하려면 귀하는 귀하의 모바일 기기에서 당사의 앱/게임을 삭제하고 당사 게임을 플레이한 모든 기기에서 당사의 쿠키를 삭제해야 합니다. 또한 소셜 네트워크 계정 내의 모든 서비스 기능 링크를 제거해야 합니다. 우리가 정보를 삭제하면 당사의 활성 데이터베이스에서 해당 정보가 삭제되지만 당사 아카이브에는 남아있을 수 있습니다. 그러나 우리는 재무 기록 유지, 법적 권리 보호 또는 시행, 마케팅 억제 목록 유지, 기술 보안 또는 데이터베이스 무결성 유지와 같은 기술적 이유 등 다른 목적을 위해 해당 정보의 일부 또는 전부를 여전히 보유할 수 있습니다. 또한 귀하의 정보는 익명화된 형태로 보관될 수 있습니다. 삭제 요청에 대한 자세한 내용은 위의 “데이터 보유/삭제 요청의 영향”을 참조하십시오.

### B. 접근 및 이동성

귀하는 우리가 귀하에 대해 어떤 정보를 보유하고 있는지 알 권리가 있으며 경우에 따라 그 정보를 전달받을 권리가 있습니다. 이 권리를 행사하려면 [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)으로 연락하여 귀하의 접근 권한을 행사하고 싶다는 사실과 정확히 어떤 정보를 요청하는지 알려주십시오. 예를 들어 해당 정보에 다른 사람에 대한 개인 정보가 포함된 경우 등에는 귀하가 요청한 모든 정보를 제공하지 못할 수도 있음을 알려드립니다.

일부의 경우 귀하는 동의에 따라 우리가 처리하는 데이터를 요청하거나, 구조화되고 일반적으로 사용되며 기계가 읽을 수 있는 형식으로 귀하와의 계약을 수행하거나, 그러한 개인 데이터를 다른 당사자에게 전송하도록 요청할 수 있습니다. 귀하의 권리는 해당 데이터 개인 정보 보호법에 따라 면제됩니다.

귀하가 개인 데이터를 다른 당사자에게 전송하기를 원하는 경우 해당 당사자를 자세히 설명해야 하며, 이는 기술적으로 가능한 경우에만 전송할 수 있음을 알려드립니다. 우리는 제삼자가 받은 개인 데이터의 보안 또는 처리에 대해 책임을 지지 않습니다.

또한 해당 데이터 보호 권한에 따라 허용되는 대로, 우리가 특정 데이터를 제공하는 것이 다른 사람의 권리를 방해하는 경우(예: 우리가 귀하에 대해 보유한 개인 데이터를 제공하면 다른 사람에 대한 정보 또는 당사의 기업 비밀 또는 지적 재산이 공개되는 경우) 귀하에게 특정 데이터를 제공하지 않을 수 있습니다.

### C. 정정

귀하는 우리가 보유한 부정확 한 개인 데이터를 수정할 권리가 있습니다. 귀하가 수정을 요청하는 경우 수정이 필요한지 우리가 평가할 수 있도록 당사가 보유한 귀하의 개인 정보가 부정확하거나 불완전하다고 생각하는 이유를 자세히 설명해 주십시오.

### D. 저장만으로 처리 제한

귀하는 특정 상황, 예를 들어 우리가 해당 개인 데이터를 수정 또는 삭제해야 할지, 또는 귀하의 이의에 따라 영구적으로 처리를 중단해야 할지 고려하는 동안 귀하에 대해 우리가 보유하고 있는 개인 데이터의 보관 목적 이외의 처리를 중단할 것을 요청할 권리가 있습니다. 그러나 우리가 해당 개인 데이터 처리를 중단한 후에도 당사에게 유효한 근거가 있는 경우 해당 데이터를 다시 사용할 수 있습니다(예: 법적 청구의 방어 또는 다른 사람의 보호).

### E. 이의

귀하는 당사 서비스 약관에 따라 수행해야 하는 경우 외에 귀하에 대한 데이터 처리에 반대할 권리가 있습니다.

귀하는 또한 당사가 정당한 이익을 기반으로 귀하에 대해 보유한 데이터를 처리 시 귀하가 그러한 처리에 반대하는 경우 [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)으로 이메일을 보내 귀하에 대한 데이터 처리에 반대할 권리가 있습니다. 당사가 그러한 데이터를 계속 처리하는 데 있어 설득력 있는 중요한 이유가 있는지 아니면 법적 청구와 관련하여 처리해야 하는지를 평가할 수 있도록 귀하의 사유에 대한 세부 정보를 제공하시기 바랍니다.

### F. 불만

우리가 귀하의 개인 데이터를 처리하는 방법에 대해 불만을 제기하고자 하는 경우 [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)으로 연락하시면 귀하의 우려 사항에 대응하기 위해 노력할 것입니다. 이는 귀하가 거주하거나 근무하는 유럽 연합 국가 내 우리가 데이터 보호법을 위반했다고 생각하는 지역에서 데이터 보호 감독 기관에 청구할 수 있는 귀하의 권리를 침해하지 않습니다.

XII. 캘리포니아 프라이버시 권리.
--------------------

2020년 1월 1일부터 귀하가 캘리포니아 거주자인 경우 확인 가능한 소비자 요청에 따라 귀하는 아래 나열된 권리를 갖습니다(그러나 이러한 권리는 법률에서 허용하는 특정 예외의 적용을 받음).

* 정보. 귀하는 지난 12개월 동안 우리가 귀하의 개인 정보를 어떻게 수집하고 사용했는지에 대한 다음 정보를 요청할 수 있습니다. 당사가 수집한 “개인 정보”의 범주(CCPA에서 고려한 대로); 당사가 개인 정보를 수집한 출처의 범주; 개인 정보 수집 및/또는 판매를 위한 사업 또는 상업적 목적; 당사가 귀하에게 서비스를 제공할 수 있도록 개인 정보를 공유하는 제삼자의 범주. 귀하가 귀하의 정보의 일부 또는 전체를 삭제하도록 요청하는 경우 귀하는 더 이상 서비스 접근 또는 사용이 불가할 수 있습니다.
* 차별 금지. 귀하는 캘리포니아 법에 의해 금지된 차별적 관행 없이 위에 설명된 권리를 행사할 수 있습니다.

귀하의 권리 행사. 귀하는 [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)으로 이메일을 보내거나 때때로 게임 내 연락 방법을 사용하여 상위 설명된 캘리포니아 개인 정보 보호 권리를 행사할 수 있습니다. 귀하의 정보, 접근 또는 삭제 권한을 행사하기 위한 귀하의 요청을 처리하려면 귀하의 신원과 캘리포니아 거주지를 확인해야 합니다. 우리가 귀하의 요청을 이해하고 응답할 수 있도록 합리적으로 충분한 세부 정보를 제공하지 않으면 당사는 귀하의 요청을 처리할 수 없습니다.

응답 시간. 우리는 요청을 받은 후 45일 이내에 접근 또는 삭제에 대한 소비자 요청에 응답하는 것을 목표로 하고 있습니다. 당사가 시간이 더 필요한 경우 서면으로 이유와 연장을 알려드립니다.

당사가 수집, 사용 및 공유하는 개인 정보. 우리는 위의 개인 정보 보호 정책에서 개인 정보를 수집하는 출처와 이 정보를 수집하는 사업 및 상업적 목적을 설명합니다.

우리는 귀하의 개인 정보를 제삼자에게 판매하지 않습니다. 우리는 당사 서비스의 광고 및 마케팅을 포함하되 이에 국한되지 않고 본 개인 정보 보호 정책에 설명된 사업 및 상업적 목적을 위해 개인 정보를 제삼자와 공유합니다.

XIII. 개인 정보 보호 정책 업데이트
----------------------

가끔 우리는 개인 정보 보호를 위하여 본 개인 정보 보호 정책을 업데이트할 수 있습니다. 업데이트는 향후 적용되며 소급 적용되지 않습니다. 변경사항이 있을 경우 우리는 본 페이지 맨 위의 날짜를 업데이트할 것이며, 중요한 변경사항일 경우 합당한 노력을 기울여 통지할 것입니다. 최신 변경사항 확인을 위해 본 페이지를 자주 방문하시기 바랍니다.

우리는 귀하의 데이터를 우리의 대리인이 아닌 제삼자와 공유하기 전에, 또는 원래의 수집 목적이나 이후에 승인된 목적과 다르게 사용하기 전에 귀하에게 개별적으로 동의 또는 거부할 수 있는 기회를 제공할 것입니다. 개인 데이터의 사용 및 공개를 제한하도록 요청하려면 privacy@kixeye으로 서면 요청을 제출하십시오.

XIV. 문의하기
---------

본 개인 정보 보호 정책에 문의 사항이 있으시면 우리 이메일 주소 [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com)으로 연락 주십시오. 우리 데이터 보호 책임자에게 연락하시려면 [dpo@kixeye.com](mailto:dpo@kixeye.com)으로 이메일을 보내시면 됩니다.

Política de Privacidade da KIXEYE Inc.
======================================

Última atualização: 23 de junho de 2023

I. Introdução à nossa Política de Privacidade
---------------------------------------------

A KIXEYE Inc. ("nós" ou "KIXEYE") leva os jogos a sério. Também levamos a sério a sua privacidade e direitos de dados. Temos o compromisso de manter com você uma relação de confiança e transparência. Esta Política de Privacidade é escrita em linguagem simples para facilitar a compreensão de como coletamos, usamos, armazenamos e compartilhamos informações que são identificáveis para você ("Dados Pessoais" – “Dados Pessoais” podem, quando o contexto indicar, significar também “Informações Pessoais“ conforme definido previsto na Lei de Proteção à Privacidade do Consumidor da Califórnia de 2018 e/ou Regulamento Geral de Proteção de Dados da UE) quando você acessa nossos sites, aplicativos móveis, jogos, fóruns ou outros serviços (coletivamente, os "Serviços"). Quando você usa um Serviço, você consente com cada uma das coletas, usos e divulgações de informações (incluindo registro e rastreamento) descritos nesta Política de Privacidade. Leia com atenção. SE VOCÊ NÃO CONCORDAR COM ESTA POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDADE, NÃO USE NENHUM SERVIÇO.

II. quaisInformações/Dados Pessoais coletamos?
----------------------------------------------

### A. Informações que você fornece a nós Diretamente.

Quando você interage com um site de propriedade da KIXEYE ou baixa o Serviço de uma loja de aplicativos de terceiros, coletaremos e armazenaremos suas informações diretamente conforme descrito a seguir, na medida em que estiverem disponíveis para nós. Coletamos as informações que você nos fornece, que podem incluir:

* Nome
* Endereço de e-mail
* Informações da conta da KIXEYE, como nome de usuário único, ID ou avatar
* Seu ID de várias “Redes Sociais” (incluindo Facebook, Apple iTunes, Google Play, Steam etc.)
* Também podemos oferecer a opção de preencher um perfil de usuário visível para outros usuários do Serviço. Seu perfil de usuário pode incluir: uma imagem de perfil; um ou mais nomes de usuário do Serviço, e um número de ID de usuário criado pela KIXEYE e usado para identificar seu perfil.
* Informações de pagamento ou cobrança
* Suas mensagens enviadas para nós ou para os Serviços (registros de chat, solicitações de suporte ao cliente)
* Informações que nos ajudam a verificar sua identidade, evitar fraudes e aprimorar nossos Serviços

### B. Informações coletadas automaticamente.

Coletamos outras informações automaticamente de seu dispositivo utilizando cookies e outros meios (SDKs, pixels de rastreamento etc.) quando você usa nossos Serviços, abrangendo, na medida em que estiver disponível, e quando necessário, sujeito ao seu consentimento:

* Endereço IP
* Informações Gerais de Dados de Localização do Dispositivo (como tipo, modelo, sistema operacional, versão do navegador ou identificadores exclusivos de dispositivo, para verificar a compatibilidade do dispositivo e IDFA ou GAID)
* IDFA significa Identificador de Anunciantes na Apple e GAID significa Identidade de Publicidade do Google. Esses identificadores exclusivos não são permanentes nem pessoais, o que significa que não contêm informações confidenciais sobre você, mas possibilitam consistência em todos os aplicativos e o rastreamento entre aplicativos. Você pode optar por não compartilhar seu identificador de dispositivo atualizando as configurações em seu dispositivo.
* Comunicações de serviço (mensagens no jogo, registros de chat)
* Tipo de conexão

### C. Informações fornecidas a nós por terceiros.

Podemos ter acesso a determinadas informações coletadas de você por terceiros, incluindo Redes Sociais, por meio do uso de serviços, sites, aplicativos ou outros serviços desses terceiros.

### D. Informações que coletamos relacionadas à sua conta.

Criaremos e atribuiremos ao seu dispositivo um identificador semelhante a um número de conta. Coletaremos também as seguintes informações sobre você na medida em que estiverem disponíveis e, se necessário, com base em seu consentimento:

* Nome de usuário do jogo
* Tipo de dispositivo; modelo; sistema operacional; memória; armazenamento;
* Número de telefone;
* País, região, cidade;
* Nome de usuário, nome do personagem;
* Idioma;
* Endereço de e-mail, e
* Seus contatos para permitir que você convide amigos para participar do Serviço.

Quando você usa nossos Serviços, coletamos informações sobre as maneiras como você usa e interage com nossos Serviços, como quando e por quanto tempo seu dispositivo permanece conectado aos nossos jogos, os recursos de jogo que você acessa e outros jogadores com quem você interage, compras que você faz dentro do aplicativo, progresso ou níveis que você atinge e outras atividades de jogo.

Também coletamos estatísticas de uso sob pseudônimos sobre suas interações com o Serviço. Essas informações são normalmente coletadas por meio do uso de arquivos de log do servidor ou arquivos de log da Web, kits de desenvolvimento de software para dispositivos móveis e tecnologias de rastreamento, como cookies de navegador, para coletar e analisar certos tipos de informações técnicas. Alguns dos cookies que o Serviço coloca em seu computador estão vinculados ao(s) seu(s) número(s) de ID de usuário. 

### E. Informações coletadas por meio de sua participação em comunidades

Ao usar o Serviço, você terá acesso à comunidade de jogos on-line no Serviço, que lhe dá a oportunidade de se comunicar ou compartilhar informações não apenas conosco, mas também com outros usuários de nosso Serviço através de:

* Participação em fóruns de jogadores e quadros de mensagens;
* Publicação de comentários públicos nos perfis de outros usuários ou painéis de jogos;
* Envio de mensagens privadas ou convites para outros usuários, seja diretamente em nossos sites ou para suas contas de e-mail;
* Chats com outros usuários; e
* Publicação de links da Web.

Quando você participa de comunidades de jogos on-line, acessamos e armazenamos informações/dados pessoais sobre você. As informações que armazenamos variam de acordo com jogo/aplicativo e são afetadas pelas configurações de privacidade estabelecidas por você e seus amigos nesse jogo/aplicativo. Você pode controlar e descobrir mais sobre essas configurações no aplicativo. Coletaremos as seguintes informações:

* Seu nome de usuário no Serviço;
* O ID de anunciante do dispositivo;
* Dependendo de como você faz login nos Serviços, o ID de usuário do Facebook;
* O endereço IP de seus dispositivos de acesso;
* Seus chats e mensagens no jogo, e
* Se fornecido por você, seu endereço de e-mail e número de telefone.
* Avatares enviados

### F. Informações de pagamento

Coletaremos também algumas informações de compra (que consistem no histórico de transações, incluindo o que você comprou, o preço e a data). Observe que suas transações de compra no jogo e/ou no aplicativo são tratadas por processadores de pagamento de terceiros, como Apple (para compras em dispositivos iOS), Google (para compras em dispositivos Android). Esses processadores de pagamento de terceiros são o “estabelecimento registrado“ de suas compras e não compartilham suas informações financeiras, como números de cartão de crédito, conosco.

### G. Correspondência do Atendimento ao Cliente

Quando você solicitar assistência de nossa equipe de Atendimento ao Cliente, coletaremos e armazenaremos:

* Seu nome e endereço de e-mail;
* Informações sobre sua atividade no Serviço;
* Seu nome de usuário ou número de ID, e
* Qualquer correspondência relacionada à assistência prestada a você

### H. Informações que nunca coletamos.

Não coletamos nenhuma "categoria especial de informações” de ou sobre você. Tratam-se de dados ou informações raciais sobre origem étnica, práticas ou orientações sexuais, opiniões políticas, crenças religiosas ou filosóficas, associação a sindicatos ou dados de saúde etc.

III. Como e por que usamos essas informações/Dados Pessoais?
------------------------------------------------------------

Usamos os Dados Pessoais e as informações não pessoais para:

### A. Fornecer nossos Serviços.

* Realizar a comunicação com você de acordo com suas preferências e nossos Termos do Serviço.
* Operar, desenvolver, manter e melhorar nossos Serviços.
* Fornecer suporte ao cliente para os Serviços.
* Solucionar disputas e aplicar nossos Termos do Serviço.
* Disponibilizar para você ofertas especiais/promocionais dentro do jogo
* Coletar taxas, pagamentos e outros valores devidos relacionados aos Serviços.
* Possibilitar sua conexão a outros jogadores.
* Criar uma conta de usuário para usar os Serviços.
* Fornecer a versão apropriada dos Serviços, inclusive no seu idioma preferencial.
* Identificar, corrigir e solucionar erros e erros de serviço.
* Desenvolver novos serviços.

### B. Proteger nossos Serviços.

* Identificar e/ou impedir fraudes.
* Identificar e/ou impedir violações dos Termos do Serviço, atividades ilegais ou trapaças.
* Verificar a identidade do usuário para comunicação do suporte ao cliente.
* Monitorar, assegurar e aprimorar a segurança de nossa rede e sistemas de informação.

### C. Personalizar nossos Serviços ou oferecer promoções.

* Fornecer avisos, experiência de jogo personalizada e outras ofertas para você.
* Comunicar-lhe sobre suas áreas de interesse e responder às suas solicitações.
* Fornecer, otimizar e medir a eficácia de nossas campanhas de marketing.
* Realizar análises de marketing interno e estudos demográficos para desenvolver, melhorar ou personalizar os Serviços.
* Salvar, acompanhar os atributos, o progresso e as estatísticas de seu jogo.

### D. Jurídico/outro.

Também usamos os Dados Pessoais e as informações não pessoais para:

* Cumprir obrigações legais.
* Exercer, estabelecer ou defender nossos Termos do Serviço e outros direitos legais.
* Casos em que acreditamos de boa-fé na necessidade de proteger a segurança, as finanças ou interesses importantes seus, nossos ou de qualquer outra pessoa.

IV. Com quem compartilhamos tais Informações/Dados Pessoais?
------------------------------------------------------------

Exceto conforme descrito a seguir, não compartilharemos seus Dados Pessoais com terceiros não afiliados sem o seu consentimento. No entanto, podemos compartilhar dados não pessoais, incluindo dados anônimos, agregados ou apresentados sob pseudônimo, de acordo com esta Política de Privacidade. Podemos compartilhar suas informações, inclusive Dados Pessoais, com terceiros nas seguintes situações:

### A. Provedores de serviços terceirizados.

Podemos contratar terceiros para coletar ou processar suas informações ou Dados Pessoais em nosso nome para fornecer os Serviços, como provedores de hospedagem para armazenar os dados pessoais que você fornece e para serviços de recuperação após desastres, bem como para a realização de qualquer contrato que celebrarmos com você, serviços de entrega de e-mail e empresas de análise (processamento de cartão de crédito, envio de e-mails de atendimento ao cliente). Nossos contratos com esses terceiros exigem que eles protejam a confidencialidade e a segurança de seus Dados Pessoais e de suas informações de acordo com esta Política de Privacidade. Não compartilhamos Dados Pessoais com terceiros para que eles negociem com você sem o seu consentimento.

### B. Empresas afiliadas da KIXEYE.

Somos parte do grupo de empresas StillFront AB. Podemos compartilhar suas informações entre nossas empresas subsidiárias, controladoras ou afiliadas para fornecer e/ou melhorar nossos Serviços e ampliar sua experiência e ofertas personalizadas.

### C. Terceiro sucessor ou adquirente.

Se a KIXEYE for fundida com um terceiro, adquirida, comprada (total ou parcialmente), sofrer alienação, reorganização, falência ou evento similar, as informações coletadas sob esta Política de Privacidade poderão ser compartilhadas com esse terceiro. Caso isso ocorra, nós o notificaremos.

### D. Conforme exigido pela lei.

Poderemos divulgar Dados Pessoais se acreditarmos de boa-fé que somos obrigados a fazê-lo para:

* Cumprir uma obrigação legal.
* Proteger e defender os direitos ou a propriedade da KIXEYE, de usuários dos Serviços ou de outros.
* Proteger a segurança pessoal, financeira ou interesse importante dos usuários dos Serviços ou do público.
* Proteger contra responsabilidade legal.
* Monitorar a conformidade e aplicar nossos Termos de Serviço, nossas políticas ou regras de fórum/comunidade.
* Responder a solicitações legais de autoridades públicas, inclusive de agências de segurança nacional ou de aplicação da lei.

V. Como armazenamos e protegemos seus Dados Pessoais?
-----------------------------------------------------

### A. Proteção de seus Dados Pessoais.

Implementamos medidas razoáveis de segurança para proteger a segurança de suas informações, tanto on-line como off-line, e estamos comprometidos com a proteção das informações de clientes/usuários. Embora tomemos precauções razoáveis contra possíveis violações de segurança de nossos Serviços e bancos de dados e registros de clientes, não podemos assegurar que nunca ocorram acessos não autorizados, invasões, perdas de dados ou outras violações. Infelizmente, a transmissão de informações pela Internet nunca é totalmente segura. Embora nos esforcemos para proteger seus Dados Pessoais, não podemos garantir a segurança de seus dados enquanto eles estiverem sendo transmitidos para nosso site; portanto, qualquer transmissão será feita por sua própria conta e risco. Recomendamos que você tome medidas para manter suas informações pessoais seguras (incluindo a senha da sua conta) e faça logoff da sua conta após utilizá-la. Caso sua conta seja invadida, isso poderá levar a um acesso não autorizado à sua conta; portanto, mantenha as informações da sua conta protegidas.

### B. Armazenamento de seus Dados Pessoais.

Os Dados Pessoais coletados, compartilhados conosco ou processados ​​sob esta Política de Privacidade podem ser armazenados nos Estados Unidos ou em qualquer outro país onde nós, nossas subsidiárias/afiliadas ou terceiros prestadores de serviços operemos, inclusive por meio do uso de armazenamento na nuvem. Ao usar os Serviços, você concorda com a transferência de seus Dados Pessoais e dados não pessoais para os Estados Unidos e outros países que podem não oferecer o mesmo nível de proteção de privacidade que as leis do seu país de residência ou cidadania. Como resultado, suas informações podem ser acessadas por autoridades governamentais estrangeiras, ou de outra forma, de acordo com as leis locais aplicáveis.

VI. Seus controles de privacidade
---------------------------------

Você tem controle sobre a coleta e o uso de seus Dados Pessoais. Você pode, a qualquer momento, acessar ou corrigir seus Dados Pessoais, restringir a coleta ou o processamento de seus Dados Pessoais e, em alguns casos, solicitar a desativação ou exclusão permanente de seus Dados Pessoais. Para solicitar acesso, correção, restrição, desativação ou exclusão de seus Dados Pessoais, entre em contato conosco em [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Antes de processarmos qualquer solicitação, podemos solicitar que você verifique sua identidade para proteger sua privacidade. Isso pode incluir comunicação por meio de plataforma de serviços ou outros métodos de verificação de identidade.

Solicitações não verificadas, não razoáveis ​​ou impraticáveis ​​podem ser rejeitadas. Para proteger sua conta, solicitações de desativação ou exclusão de Dados Pessoais exigem verificação adicional, que pode incluir uma suspensão temporária de sua conta e dos Serviços. Após o processamento das solicitações de desativação ou exclusão, elas são permanentes e os Dados Pessoais e a conta não poderão ser restaurados.

VII. Crianças menores de 13 anos
--------------------------------

Nossos serviços não são direcionados, nem pretendem ser atraentes, para crianças menores de 13 anos. Não coletamos intencionalmente Dados Pessoais, informações pessoais, fotos, vídeos, arquivos de áudio ou dados de localização de crianças menores de 13 anos nem usamos conscientemente identificadores persistentes para reconhecer crianças menores de 13 anos ao longo do tempo e em diferentes sites ou serviços on-line. Se você tem menos de 13 anos, não use nossos Serviços e não envie nenhuma informação para nós. Incentivamos os pais e responsáveis ​​legais a monitorar o uso da Internet por seus filhos e a ajudar a aplicar esta Política de Privacidade, instruindo crianças menores de 13 anos a não usarem nossos Serviços. Se você tiver motivos para acreditar que uma criança com menos de 13 anos forneceu Dados Pessoais ou informações pessoais à KIXEYE por meio de nossos Serviços, entre em contato conosco em [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) e tomaremos as medidas necessárias para excluir essas informações de nossos bancos de dados o mais rápido possível.

VIII. Políticas e práticas de privacidade de terceiros/redes sociais
--------------------------------------------------------------------

Esta Política de Privacidade se aplica apenas a Dados Pessoais e informações coletadas pela KIXEYE por meio do uso de nossos Serviços. Sites de terceiros podem ser acessados ​​por meio de links ao usar nossos Serviços, ou você pode ter acessado, baixado ou chegado a nossos Serviços por meio de sites de terceiros. Esses sites de terceiros são regidos por suas próprias políticas de privacidade e não somos responsáveis ​​por qualquer conteúdo exibido nesses sites ou por quaisquer práticas de privacidade ou segurança desses sites. Para gerenciar as informações que a KIXEYE recebe sobre você das Redes Sociais em que você usa nossos Serviços, você precisará seguir as instruções naquele site para atualizar suas informações e alterar suas configurações de privacidade. As ferramentas de gerenciamento de privacidade para aplicativos da Apple podem ser encontradas em [http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/). As ferramentas de gerenciamento de privacidade do Google podem ser encontradas em [https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/). Você pode gerenciar certos aspectos da coleta e do uso de informações acessando as configurações do seu dispositivo (móvel) e analisando as permissões de cada aplicativo.

Quando a KIXEYE recebe suas informações de Redes Sociais, essas informações são armazenadas e usadas pela KIXEYE de acordo com esta Política de Privacidade, e você pode acessar e atualizar essas informações conforme descrito a seguir. As contas criadas na KIXEYE são consideradas ativas até que recebamos uma solicitação do usuário para excluí-las ou desativá-las.

IX. Retenção de dados/efeito de solicitações de exclusão
--------------------------------------------------------

Realizamos esforços para reter somente os Dados Pessoais necessários. Quando os Dados Pessoais não forem mais exigidos por esta Política de Privacidade, nós os excluiremos ou removeremos a identificação periodicamente. Quando não for comercialmente razoável excluir ou remover a identificação de seus Dados Pessoais, removeremos seus Dados Pessoais do processamento e os armazenaremos com segurança até que possamos excluí-los permanentemente. Observe que podemos reter informações necessárias para fins jurídicos e contábeis, para resolver disputas, aplicar nossos contratos de usuário, proteger nossos direitos legais e cumprir os requisitos e restrições técnicas e legais. Por exemplo, podemos reter registros relativos a pagamentos ou questões de atendimento ao cliente. Se você enviou ou publicou conteúdo no Serviço, talvez não possamos excluí-lo. A exclusão efetiva pode exigir ações de sua parte, como exclusão de aplicativos e/ou conteúdo relacionado ao Serviço de seu dispositivo e/ou desvinculação do Serviço em sua(s) conta(s) de Redes Sociais. Observe que se você nos solicitar a exclusão de sua conta, todo o seu progresso no jogo e quaisquer itens virtuais não utilizados serão perdidos permanentemente. Observe que os resultados e artefatos de seu jogo, por exemplo, bases, personagens, naves, suprimentos etc. podem permanecer ativos no jogo (e sujeitos ao jogo, ou seja, destruição ou exploração por jogadores ativos), mesmo após a exclusão ou desvinculação de sua conta e/ou de seus Dados Pessoais.

X. Bases legais para usuários de países europeus
------------------------------------------------

Se você estiver em um país da União Europeia, na Área Econômica Europeia ou na Suíça, a seguir estão as bases jurídicas que empregamos para processar suas informações.

* Necessidade contratual. Abrange os dados usados ​​por nós para fornecer a você os Serviços que você solicitou e que concordamos em fornecer a você, como nossos jogos, atendimento ao cliente e funcionalidade de chat;
* Obrigação legal. Abrange os dados usados ​​por nós para cumprir obrigações legais, como manter registros relacionados a impostos ou para responder a solicitações legais válidas para certos dados;
* Interesses legítimos. Abrange os dados usados ​​por nós para fins que podem ser razoavelmente esperados com o uso de nossos Serviços e que não acreditamos serem prejudiciais à sua privacidade, como análises para entender como nossos usuários navegam em nossos sites e aplicativos, para manter nossos sites e aplicativos seguros e protegidos, pesquisa e otimização do nosso Serviço para proporcionar experiência, marketing e publicidade mais personalizados, e

Consentimento. Nos casos em que processarmos dados com base em seu consentimento, solicitaremos seu consentimento explícito. Você pode revogar o consentimento a qualquer momento, mas isso não afetará a legalidade do processamento de seus dados pessoais antes de tal revogação.

Embora você possa revogar seu consentimento ou se opor a certos tipos de processamento a qualquer momento nas formas descritas nesta Política de Privacidade, observe que, se continuar a usar os Serviços após essas solicitações, retomaremos a coleta e o processamento de dados pessoais sobre você conforme descrito de outra forma nesta Política de Privacidade. Caso não queira que coletemos quaisquer dados pessoais sobre você, interrompa o uso do jogo e de nossos Serviços.

XI. Direitos de usuários de países europeus
-------------------------------------------

Se estiver localizado em um país da União Europeia, na Área Econômica Europeia ou na Suíça, você terá certos direitos em relação aos dados pessoais que mantemos sobre você, que detalhamos a seguir e que estão sujeitos a isenções de acordo com leis sobre privacidade de dados aplicáveis. Algumas só se aplicam em determinadas circunstâncias, conforme estabelecido mais detalhadamente a seguir. Definimos também como exercer esses direitos. Observe que podemos exigir que você verifique sua identidade antes de responder a qualquer solicitação para exercer seus direitos. Responderemos a uma solicitação sua para exercer esses direitos sem adiamentos indevidos e dentro de pelo menos um mês (embora esse prazo possa, em certas circunstâncias, ser prorrogado por mais dois meses). Para exercer qualquer um dos seus direitos, envie um e-mail para [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Podemos nos recusar a processar solicitações em determinadas circunstâncias, como quando as solicitações forem manifestamente infundadas ou excessivas ou colocarem em risco a privacidade de terceiros.

### A. Exclusão de seus dados pessoais

Em algumas circunstâncias, você poderá solicitar a exclusão de alguns dos seus dados pessoais mantidos por nós. Se quiser a exclusão de seus dados pessoais, entre em contato conosco em [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Observe que, para processar sua solicitação e garantir a exclusão, você deve excluir nossos aplicativos/jogos de seus dispositivos móveis e limpar os cookies de qualquer dispositivo em que tenha usado nossos jogos. Você também deve remover todos os links de funcionalidade do Serviço em suas contas de Redes Sociais. Quando excluirmos quaisquer informações, elas serão excluídas de nossos bancos de dados ativos, mas poderão permanecer em nossos arquivos. No entanto, observe que ainda poderemos manter algumas ou todas essas informações para outros fins, como manutenção de registros financeiros, proteção ou aplicação de direitos legais, manutenção de listas de supressão de marketing ou por razões técnicas, como manutenção de segurança técnica ou integridade de nosso banco de dados. Também podemos reter suas informações de maneira anônima. Consulte “Impacto da exclusão de retenção de dados“ acima para obter mais informações sobre solicitações de exclusão.

### B. Acesso e portabilidade

Você tem o direito de saber quais informações temos sobre você e, em alguns casos, de que as informações lhe sejam comunicadas. Se você quiser exercer esse direito, entre em contato conosco pelo e-mail [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) e informe-nos que deseja exercer seu direito de acesso e exatamente quais informações você está solicitando. Observe que podemos não ser capazes de fornecer todas as informações solicitadas, por exemplo, se as informações incluírem informações pessoais sobre outra pessoa.

Em algumas circunstâncias, você poderá solicitar os dados que processamos com base em consentimento ou para executar nosso contrato com você em um formato estruturado, comumente usado e legível por máquina ou para solicitar a transferência de tais dados pessoais para outra parte. Seus direitos estão sujeitos a isenções de acordo com as leis de privacidade de dados aplicáveis.

Se desejar que façamos a transferência dos dados pessoais para outra parte, certifique-se de detalhar essa parte e observe que só podemos fazer isso quando houver viabilidade técnica. Não somos responsáveis ​​pela segurança dos dados pessoais ou seu processamento quando recebidos por terceiros.

Também não podemos fornecer certos dados se isso interferir nos direitos de outra pessoa (por exemplo, quando o fornecimento de dados pessoais sobre você revelar informações sobre outra pessoa ou nossos segredos comerciais ou propriedade intelectual) conforme permitido pelos direitos de proteção de dados aplicáveis.

### C. Correção

Você tem o direito de corrigir quaisquer Dados Pessoais em nosso poder que não estejam corretos. Quando você solicitar a correção, explique detalhadamente por que acredita que os Dados Pessoais que mantemos sobre você estejam incorretos ou incompletos para que possamos avaliar a necessidade de uma correção.

### D. Restrição de processamento a somente armazenamento

Você tem o direito de exigir a interrupção do processamento dos Dados Pessoais que mantemos sobre você que não seja para fins de armazenamento em certas circunstâncias, por exemplo, quando considerarmos se devem ser corrigidos ou excluídos ou, com base na sua objeção, se devemos interromper o processamento permanentemente. Contudo, observe que, se interrompermos o processamento dos Dados Pessoais, poderemos voltar a usá-los se houver motivos válidos para fazê-lo (por exemplo, para a defesa de ações judiciais ou para a proteção de terceiros).

### E. Objeção

Você tem direito a se opor ao nosso processamento de dados sobre você, exceto quando exigido para o cumprimento de nossos Termos do Serviço.

Você também tem direito a se opor ao nosso processamento de dados sobre você, enviando um e-mail para [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) caso estejamos processando os dados que mantemos sobre você com base em nosso interesse legítimo e você se tiver objeções relacionadas a tal processamento. Forneça detalhes sobre seu raciocínio para que possamos avaliar se há um interesse primordial em continuarmos a processar esses dados ou se precisamos processá-los em relação a ações judiciais.

### F. Reclamações

Se quiser fazer uma reclamação sobre como processamos seus Dados Pessoais, entre em contato conosco em privacy@kixeye.co e faremos o possível para responder às suas dúvidas. Isso não prejudica o seu direito de apresentar uma reivindicação junto à autoridade supervisora de proteção de dados no país da UE em que você reside ou trabalha quando acreditar que infringimos as leis de proteção de dados.

XII. Seus direitos à privacidade da Califórnia.
-----------------------------------------------

Em vigor a partir de 1º de janeiro de 2020, se você for residente da Califórnia, e mediante solicitação verificável do consumidor, terá os direitos listados a seguir (no entanto, esses direitos estão sujeitos a determinadas exceções permitidas por lei):

* Informações. Você pode solicitar as seguintes informações sobre como coletamos e usamos suas Informações Pessoais durante os últimos 12 meses: as categorias de “Informações Pessoais“ (conforme contempladas pela CCPA) que coletamos; as categorias de fontes das quais coletamos Informações Pessoais; a finalidade comercial para coletar e/ou vender Informações Pessoais; as categorias de terceiros com os quais compartilhamos Informações Pessoais para que possamos fornecer nossos Serviços a você. Se nos solicitar a exclusão de algumas ou todas as suas informações, você não poderá voltar a acessar ou usar os Serviços.
* Não discriminação. Você está autorizado a exercer os direitos descritos acima, livre de práticas discriminatórias proibidas pela lei da Califórnia.

Exercendo seus direitos. Você pode exercer periodicamente seus direitos de privacidade na Califórnia descritos acima enviando um e-mail para [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) ou pelos métodos de contato dentro do jogo. Precisaremos confirmar sua identidade e residência na Califórnia para processar suas solicitações de exercer seus direitos a suas informações, de acesso ou de exclusão. Não poderemos processar sua solicitação se você não nos fornecer detalhes razoavelmente suficientes para que possamos entendê-la e respondê-la.

Tempo de resposta. Nosso objetivo é responder a uma solicitação de acesso ou exclusão do cliente em até 45 dias após o recebimento da solicitação. Se necessitarmos de mais tempo, você será informado sobre o motivo e a extensão por escrito.

Informações pessoais que coletamos, usamos e compartilhamos. Descrevemos as fontes das quais coletamos Informações Pessoais e os fins comerciais para os quais coletamos essas informações nesta Política de Privacidade acima.

Não vendemos suas Informações Pessoais a terceiros. Compartilhamos Informações Pessoais com terceiros para os fins comerciais descritos nesta Política de Privacidade, incluindo, sem limitação, publicidade e marketing de nossos Serviços.

XIII. Atualizações em nossa Política de Privacidade
---------------------------------------------------

Periodicamente, poderemos atualizar esta Política de Privacidade para manter nosso compromisso com a privacidade. As atualizações são aplicáveis ao futuro, nunca retroativamente. Quando fizermos alterações, atualizaremos a data na parte superior desta página e faremos os esforços necessários para notificá-lo caso as alterações sejam substanciais. Recomendamos que você acesse frequentemente esta página para manter-se atualizado sobre quaisquer alterações.

Forneceremos uma opção individual de exclusão ou inclusão antes de compartilharmos seus dados com terceiros que não sejam nossos agentes ou antes de usá-los para outros fins que não os originalmente coletados ou autorizados subsequentemente. Para solicitar a limitação do uso e da divulgação de seus Dados Pessoais, envie uma solicitação por escrito para [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

XIV. Entre em contato conosco
-----------------------------

Caso tenha dúvidas referentes a esta Política de Privacidade, envie um e-mail para [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Caso queira entrar em contato com o responsável pela proteção de dados, envie um e-mail para [dpo@kixeye.com](mailto:dpo@kixeye.com).

Политика конфиденциальности KIXEYE Inc.
=======================================

Обновлено: 23 июня 2023 г.

I. Введение к Политике конфиденциальности
-----------------------------------------

Компания KIXEYE Inc. (далее «мы» или «KIXEYE») серьезно относится к играм. А еще к Вашей конфиденциальности и защите данных. Мы хотим сохранять с Вами доверительные и прозрачные отношения. Эта политика конфиденциальности написана доступным языком, чтобы Вам было проще понять, как мы собираем, используем, храним и передаем информацию, которую можно связать с Вами («Личные данные» – в определенном контексте также обозначаются как “Личная информация”, как определено Законом штата Калифорния о защите конфиденциальности потребителей 2018 г. и/или Генеральным регламентом ЕС по защите персональных данных), когда Вы пользуетесь нашими веб-сайтами, мобильными приложениями, играми, форумами или другими услугами (вместе называемые «Услуги»). Используя Услуги, Вы соглашаетесь с любым сбором, использованием и раскрытием информации (включая запись и отслеживание), описанным в настоящей Политике конфиденциальности. Внимательно прочитайте ее. ЕСЛИ ВЫ НЕ СОГЛАСНЫ С НАСТОЯЩЕЙ ПОЛПИТИКОЙ, НЕ ИСПОЛЬЗУЙТЕ НИКАКИХ НАШИХ УСЛУГ.

II. Какую информацию/личные данные мы собираем?
-----------------------------------------------

### A. Информацию, которую Вы предоставляете нам напрямую.

Когда Вы заходите на веб-сайт компании KIXEYE или скачиваете Услугу из стороннего магазина приложений, мы собираем и сохраняем Вашу информацию, как описано ниже, в доступной для нас степени. Мы собираем информацию, которую Вы нам даете. Это могут быть:

* Ваше имя;
* адрес электронной почты;
* информация об учетной записи KIXEYE, такая как уникальное имя пользователя, идентификатор или аватар;
* Ваш идентификатор из различных “социальных сетей” (включая Facebook, Apple iTunes, Google Play, Steam и т. д).
* Также мы можем дать Вам возможность заполнить профиль пользователя, видимый другим пользователям Услуги. Он может включать в себя: изображение, одно или несколько имен пользователя Услуги; идентификационный номер пользователя KIXEYE, созданный KIXEYE для идентификации Вашего профиля;
* платежные данные или реквизиты;
* Ваши сообщения напрямую нам или в рамках Услуг (журналы чатов, запросы в службу поддержки);
* информация, помогающая нам определять, что это и правда Вы, предотвращать случаи мошенничества, разрабатывать и улучшать наши Услуги.

### B. Автоматически собираемую информацию.

Мы автоматически получаем информацию с Вашего устройства с помощью cookie-файлов и других средств (SDK, пиксели слежения и др.), когда Вы используете наши Услуги, включая следующую информацию (по мере ее доступности и, при необходимости, после получения Вашего согласия):

* IP-адрес;
* общие данные об устройстве (например, тип устройства, модель, операционная система, версия браузера, уникальные идентификаторы для проверки совместимости устройств, а также IDFA или GAID).
* IDFA – это рекламный идентификатор Apple, GAID – рекламный идентификатор Google. Эти уникальные идентификаторы непостоянны и обезличены, то есть не содержат конфиденциальной информации о Вас, но позволяют обеспечить единство данных по всем приложениям. Вы можете отключить передачу идентификатора устройства, изменив настройки на устройстве.
* сообщения в рамках Услуг (сообщения в играх, журналы чатов).
* Тип соединения

### C. Информацию от третьих сторон.

Мы можем получать доступ к информации о Вас, собранной третьими сторонами, включая социальные сети, во время использования Вами их услуг, веб-сайтов, приложений или других услуг.

### D. Информацию о Вашей учетной записи.

Мы создадим и назначим Вашему устройству идентификатор, который похож на номер учетной записи. Мы также будем собирать о Вас следующую информацию (по мере ее доступности и, при необходимости, после получения Вашего согласия):

* игровое имя пользователя;
* тип устройства, модель, операционная система, память, свободное место;
* номер телефона;
* страна, регион, город;
* имя пользователя, имя персонажа;
* язык;
* адрес электронной почты;
* Ваши контакты, чтобы Вы могли пригласить друзей пользоваться Услугой.

Когда Вы используете наши Услуги, мы будем собирать информацию о том, как Вы это делаете, например о том, когда и как долго Ваше устройство находилось в наших играх, какие игровые возможности используете, с какими игроками взаимодействуете, о Ваших покупках внутри игр, о набранных уровнях, прогрессе и других игровых активностях.

Также мы собираем псевдонимизированную статистику использования о Ваших взаимодействиях с Услугой. Обычно мы делаем это, используя журналы сервера или веб-журналы, наборы для разработки ПО для мобильных устройств и отслеживающие технологии, такие как cookie-файлы для браузера, чтобы собирать и анализировать определенные типы технической информации. Некоторые из cookie-файлов, которые Услуга размещает на Вашем компьютере, привязаны к Вашему номеру-идентификатору пользователя (или номерам). 

### E. Информацию, собираемую благодаря Вашему участию в сообществах

Используя Услугу, Вы получаете доступ к сетевому игровому сообществу в ее рамках, которое дает Вам возможность общаться и обмениваться информацией не только с нами, но и с другими пользователями услуги посредством:

* участия в форумах и на досках сообщений;
* публикации открытых комментариев в профилях других пользователей или на игровых площадках для общения;
* отправки личных сообщений или приглашений другим пользователям напрямую на наших веб-сайтах или на их адреса эл. почты;
* чатов с другими пользователями;
* публикации ссылок на сайты.

Когда Вы участвуете в жизни сетевых игровых сообществ, мы получаем доступ к Вашим личным данным и сохраняем их. То, какую информацию мы сохраняем, зависит от игры/приложения и настроек конфиденциальности, которые Вы и Ваши друзья выбираете для этой игры/приложения. Узнать больше о этих настройках и изменить их Вы можете в приложении. Мы собираем следующую&nbspинформацию:

* Ваше имя пользователя в Услуге;
* рекламный идентификатор Вашего устройства;
* в зависимости о того, как Вы входите в Услугу, идентификатор пользователя Facebook;
* IP-адрес устройств, с которых Вы осуществляете вход;
* Ваши чаты и сообщения внутри игр;
* Ваш адрес эл. почты и номер телефона, если Вы их указали.
* Отправленные аватары

### F. Информацию о платежах

Мы также собираем некоторую информацию о покупках (включая историю транзакций, список покупок, цену и дату). Обратите внимание, что Ваши покупки в играх и/или приложениях обрабатываются сторонними платежными операторами, такими как Apple (для покупок на устройствах на iOS), Google (для покупок на устройствах на Android). Эти операторы выступают “официальными получателями платежей” и не делятся с нами Вашими финансовыми данными, такими как номера кредитных карт.

### G. Историю переписки со службой поддержки

Когда Вы просите помощи у службы поддержки, мы собираем и сохраняем:

* Ваше имя и адрес электронной почты;
* информацию о Вашей активности в рамках Услуги;
* Ваше имя пользователя или идентификатор;
* любую переписку, связанную с оказанной Вам помощью.

### H. Что мы не собираем никогда

Мы не собираем о Вас «данных особой категории»: информацию о Вашей расе, этническом происхождении, сексуальных практиках или ориентации, политических, религиозных или философских взглядах, членстве в профсоюзах, данных о здоровье и т. д.

III. Как и зачем мы используем эту информацию/личные данные?
------------------------------------------------------------

Мы используем Ваши личные и прочие данные, чтобы:

### A. Предоставлять Вам наши Услуги.

* Общаться с Вами с учетом Ваших настроек и Условий предоставления услуг.
* Оказывать, разрабатывать, поддерживать и улучшать наши Услуги.
* Оказывать поддержку клиентам Услуг.
* Решать споры и обеспечивать выполнение Условий предоставления услуг.
* Готовить для вас особые/рекламные акции в игре.
* Взимать сборы, платежи и другие виды выплат, возникающие в связи с оказанием Услуг.
* Давать возможности для связи с другими игроками.
* Создавать учетные записи для использования наших Услуг.
* Предоставлять Вам подходящую версию Услуг, в том числе на выбранном Вами языке.
* Выявлять, исправлять и устранять ошибки и недостатки в Услугах.
* Разрабатывать новые продукты.

### B. Сделать наши Услуги безопасными.

* Выявлять и/или предотвращать мошенничество.
* Выявлять и/или предотвращать нарушения Условий предоставления услуг, незаконные или нечестные действия.
* Подтверждать личность пользователей для оказания поддержки.
* Отслеживать, поддерживать и повышать уровень безопасности наших сетевых и информационных систем.

### C. Предлагать Вам персонализированные Услуги и акции.

* Предоставлять Вам уведомления, персонализированные игровые возможности и другие материалы.
* Общаться с Вами на интересующие Вас темы и отвечать на Ваши запросы.
* Проводить и оптимизировать маркетинговые кампании, измерять их эффективность.
* Проводить анализ для внутренних маркетинговых и демографических исследований в целях развития, улучшения или персонализации Услуг.
* Сохранять и отслеживать параметры, прогресс и статистику по игре.

### D. Соблюдать нормы закона/прочее.

Мы также используем Ваши личные и прочие данные, чтобы:

* Соблюдать юридические обязательства.
* Претворять в жизнь Условия предоставления услуг и другие законные права и следить за их соблюдением.
* В случаях, когда мы можем добросовестно предполагать, что должны защитить безопасность, финансовый или существенный интерес (Вас, нас или любого другого лица).

IV.&nbspС кем мы делимся этой информацией/личными данными?
----------------------------------------------------------

За исключением описанных ниже случаев, мы не будем делиться Вашими личными данными со сторонними третьими лицами без Вашего согласия. Однако, в соответствии с настоящей Политикой, мы можем делиться данными других типов, включая обезличенные, агрегированные или псевдонимизированные. Мы можем делиться информацией о Вас, включая личные данные, со следующими третьими лицами:

### A. Сторонние поставщики услуг

Мы можем заключать с третьими лицами договоры на сбор или обработку информации о Вас или личных данных от нашего имени для оказания Услуг, например, с хостинг-провайдерами для хранения предоставленных Вами личных данных, экстренного восстановления данных или выполнения любых заключенных с Вами договоров; службами доставки электронной почты и аналитическими компаниями (для обработки данных по платежным картам, рассылки электронной почты клиентам). Наши соглашения с такими третьими лицами требуют от них защиты конфиденциальности и безопасности Ваших личных данных и прочей информации в соответствии с настоящей Политикой конфиденциальности. Без Вашего согласия мы не передаем Ваши личные данные никаким третьим лицам, которые могли бы их использовать.

### B. Аффилированные с KIXEYE компании

Мы входим в группу компаний StillFront AB. Мы можем делиться информацией о Вас с нашими дочерними, материнскими или аффилированными компаниями в целях оказания и улучшения Услуг и персонализированных возможностей и предложений.

### C. Сторона-преемник при покупке

Если компания KIXEYE объединится с третьей стороной, будет ей приобретена (полностью или частично) или пройдет отчуждение, реорганизацию, банкротство или другое похожие событие, то информация, собранная в соответствии с настоящей Политикой, может быть передана такой третьей стороне. Мы сообщим Вам, если это произойдет.

### D. Получатели по требованию закона.

Мы можем раскрывать личную информацию, если добросовестно предполагаем, что обязаны это сделать:

* для исполнения правового обязательства;
* для защиты прав или собственности KIXEYE, пользователей Услуг или других лиц;
* для защиты личной безопасности, финансовых или существенных интересов пользователей Услуг или других лиц;
* для защиты от юридической ответственности;
* для проверки соблюдения Условий использования, политик или правил форумов/сообщества;
* для ответа на законные запросы государственных органов, включая органы национальной безопасности и правоохранительные органы.

V. Как мы защищаем и храним Ваши личные данные?
-----------------------------------------------

### A. Защита Ваших личных данных

Мы применяем разумные меры безопасности для защиты Ваших данных как в сети, так и вне ее, и ответственно подходим к защите информации клиентов/пользователей. Мы принимаем меры предосторожности против возможных взломов наших Услуг, база данных и записей по клиентам, но не можем полностью исключить возможность несанкционированного доступа, взломов, потери данных и других нарушений безопасности данных. К сожалению, передача информации через Интернет не бывает абсолютно безопасной. Мы стремимся защитить Ваши личные данные, но не можем гарантировать их безопасность во время их передачи на наш сайт; любая передача происходит на Ваш страх и риск. Мы призываем Вас беречь Вашу личную информацию (включая пароль от учетной записи) и выходить из учетной записи после использования. Если Вашу учетную запись взломали, это может привести к несанкционированному доступу к ней, поэтому информацию по ней необходимо беречь.

### B. Хранение личных данных

Личные данные, которые мы собираем, получаем или обрабатываем в соответствии с настоящей Политикой, могут храниться в США или любой другой стране, в которой работаем мы, наши дочерние/аффилированные компании или сторонние поставщики услуг, в том числе с использованием облачных хранилищ. Используя Услуги, Вы даете согласие на передачу Ваших личных и прочих данных в США и другие страны, которые могут не обеспечивать необходимый уровень защиты конфиденциальности по законам Вашей страны проживания или гражданства. В результате к Вашей информации могут получить доступ зарубежные органы государственной власти в соответствии с действующим местным законодательством.

VI. Ваши настройки конфиденциальности
-------------------------------------

Вы можете настраивать сбор и использование Ваших личных данных. Вы можете в любой момент получить доступ к своим личным данным или исправить их, ограничить сбор или обработку личных данных, а в некоторых случаях потребовать деактивации или полного удаления своих личных данных. Чтобы оставить запрос на доступ, исправление, ограничение, деактивацию или удаление личных данных, свяжитесь с нами по адресу [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Перед обработкой запроса мы можем попросить Вас подтвердить Вашу личность для защиты Вашей конфиденциальности. Это может быть сделано через платформу Услуг или с помощью других методов проверки личности.

Неподтвержденные, необоснованные или невыполнимые запросы могут быть отклонены. В целях защиты Вашей учетной записи запросы на деактивацию или удаление персональных данных требуют дополнительной проверки, которая может включать в себя временную приостановку Вашей учетной записи и Услуг. После выполнения запроса на деактивацию и удаление личных данных и учетной записи их уже нельзя будет восстановить.

VII. Дети младше 13 лет
-----------------------

Наши услуги не адресованы детям в возрасте до 13 лет и не предназначены для них. Мы намеренно не собираем личные данные, личную информацию, фотографии, видео, аудиофайлы или данные о местоположении в отношении детей в возрасте до 13 лет или принадлежащие им и намеренно не используем идентификаторы для распознавания детей в возрасте до 13 лет на различных веб-сайтах и в онлайн-сервисах. Если Вам меньше 13 лет, не используйте наши Услуги и не передавайте нам никакой информации. Мы призываем родителей и законных представителей проверять то, как используют Интернет их дети, и помогать нам соблюдать настоящую Политику, предписывая детям в возрасте до 13 лет не пользоваться нашими Услугами. Если у Вас есть основания полагать, что ребенок в возрасте до 13 лет предоставил личные данные или личную информацию KIXEYE через наши Услуги, напишите нам на адрес [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com), и мы примем меры по скорейшему удалению этой информации из наших баз данных.

VIII. Политики и практики конфиденциальности третьих сторон/социальные сети
---------------------------------------------------------------------------

Настоящая Политика относится только к личным данным и информации, которые KIXEYE собирает, пока Вы используете наши Услуги. При использовании Услуг Вам могут быть доступны сторонние веб-сайты по ссылкам. Их работа регулируется их собственными политиками конфиденциальности, и мы не несем и не можем нести ответственность за любые материалы, размещенные на этих веб-сайтах, или практики этих веб-сайтов в отношении конфиденциальности или безопасности. Для настройки того, какую информацию KIXEYE получает о Вас из социальных сетей, в которых Вы используете наши Услуги, Вам нужно будет следовать инструкциям по обновлению информации и изменению настроек конфиденциальности на соответствующих веб-сайтах. Инструменты для настройки конфиденциальности в приложениях для Apple можно найти по адресу [http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/). Инструменты для настройки конфиденциальности для Google можно найти по адресу [https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/). Некоторые настройки сбора и использования информации можно изменить, перейдя в настройки своего (мобильного) устройства и изучив разрешения для каждого приложения.

Как только KIXEYE получает Вашу информацию из социальных сетей, она сохраняется и используется KIXEYE согласно положениям ее Политики конфиденциальности, и Вы можете получить к ней доступ и обновить ее, как описано ниже. Созданные в KIXEYE учетные записи считаются активными, пока мы не получаем запрос от пользователя на их удаление или деактивацию.

IX. Сохранение данных/Результат запросов на удаление
----------------------------------------------------

Мы стараемся сохранять не больше личных данных, чем это необходимо. Когда личные данные больше не требуются в соответствии с настоящей Политикой, мы удаляем их или деидентифицируем. Если это коммерчески нецелесообразно, мы удаляем личные данные из обработки и надежно храним их до тех пор, пока не сможем безвозвратно удалить. Обратите внимание, что мы можем сохранять информацию, необходимую в юридических и бухгалтерских целях, для разрешения споров, обеспечения выполнений пользовательских соглашений, защиты своих законных прав и выполнения технических и правовых требований и ограничений. Например, мы можем сохранять записи о платежах или работе службы поддержки. Если Вы отправляли или публиковали материалы в рамках Услуги, у нас может не быть возможности его удалить. Для удаления могут потребоваться действия с Вашей стороны, такие как удаление с Вашего устройства приложений и/или материалов, связанных с Услугой, или отвязка Услуги от учетных записей в социальных сетях. Учтите: если Вы попросите нас удалить учетную запись, весь прогресс и неиспользованные виртуальные предметы пропадут навсегда. Ваши результаты и артефакты, например, базы, персонажи, корабли, припасы и т. п. могут остаться в игре (и будут доступны, например, для уничтожения или использования активными игроками) даже после того, как Ваша учетная запись и/или личные данные были удалены или отключены от игры.

X. Правовая база для пользователей из европейских стран
-------------------------------------------------------

Если Вы находитесь в стране Европейского союза, Европейской экономической зоны или в Швейцарии, мы опираемся на следующую правовую базу при обработке Ваших данных.

* Обусловленная договором необходимость: мы используем данные, необходимые для оказания запрошенных Вами Услуг, которые мы согласились Вам оказать, таких как игры, поддержка и функции чатов.
* Законные требования:&nbspмы используем данные, необходимые для выполнения законных требований, например, сохраняем записи, имеющие отношения к налогам, и выполняем правомерные запросы на доступ к определенным данным;
* Законные интересы: мы используем данные, необходимые нам для оказания Вам Услуг, которые, по нашему мнению, не нарушают Вашу конфиденциальность, такие как аналитические данные, позволяющие понять, как именно наши пользователи перемещаются по нашим веб-сайтам и приложениям, что позволяет гарантировать их надежную и безопасную работу, развивать и улучшать наши Услуги и персонализировать материалы, маркетинг и рекламу.

Согласие: когда мы обрабатываем данные с Вашего согласия, мы запрашиваем Ваше явно выраженное согласие. Вы можете отозвать его в любой момент, но это не повлияет на законность обработки Ваших личных данных до такого отзыва.

Вы можете отозвать согласие или запретить обработку определенного типа в любой момент способом, описанным в настоящей Политике конфиденциальности, но если Вы продолжите пользоваться Услугами после такого запроса (или запросов), мы продолжим собирать и обрабатывать Ваши личные данные согласно настоящей Политике конфиденциальности. Если Вы не хотите, чтобы мы собирали Ваши личные данные, Вы должны прекратить игру и использование наших Услуг.

XI. Пользователи из европейских стран и их права
------------------------------------------------

Если Вы находитесь в стране Европейского союза, Европейской экономической зоны или в Швейцарии, у Вас есть определенные права в отношении личных данных, которые мы у Вас собираем. Эти права перечислены ниже; некоторые из них могут быть недействительны согласно применимым законам о защите конфиденциальности. Некоторые из них можно реализовать только в определенных обстоятельствах (подробнее ниже). Мы определяем, как реализовать эти права. Внимание: мы можем потребовать у Вас подтвердить Вашу личность перед реакцией на любой запрос о реализации Ваших прав. Мы отреагируем на такой запрос без неоправданных задержек и не позднее одного месяца с момента запроса (хотя этот срок может быть увеличен еще на два месяца при определенных обстоятельствах). Чтобы реализовать любое из Ваших прав, отправьте электронное письмо на адрес [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Мы можем отказать в обработке запроса при определенных обстоятельствах, например, если он явно необоснован, избыточен или ставит под угрозу конфиденциальность других лиц.

### A. Удаление Ваших персональных данных

В некоторых ситуациях Вы можете запросить удаление некоторых личных данных о Вас, которые у нас хранятся. Если Вы хотите, чтобы Ваши личные данные удалили, напишите нам на [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Обратите внимание: для обработки запроса и удаления данных Вы должны удалить наши игры/приложения с Ваших мобильных устройство и удалить наши cookie-файлы со всех устройств, на которых Вы запускали наши игры. Также Вы должны удалить все функциональные ссылки, относящиеся к нашим Услугам, из своих профилей в социальных сетях. Когда мы удаляем информацию, она стирается из наших активных баз данных, но может остаться в архивах. Обратите внимание, что мы можем сохранить всю информацию или ее часть в других целях, таких как поддержание финансовой отчетности, защита и реализация законных прав, поддержание стоп-списка для маркетинговых мер, или по техническим причинам, таким как поддержание безопасности или целостности баз данных. Также мы можем сохранять Вашу информацию в обезличенной форме. Подробнее о запросах на удаление см. раздел “Сохранение данных/Результат запросов на удаление” выше.

### B. Доступ и перенос

Вы имеете право знать, какие данные о Вас мы храним, а в некоторых случаях и получать эти данные. Если Вы хотите воспользоваться этим правом, напишите нам на [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com), и сообщите об этом, а также о том, какие именно данные Вы запрашиваете. Обратите внимание, что мы не сможем предоставить все требуемые данные, например, если они включают личные данные другого человека.

В некоторых случаях Вы имеете право запросить данные, которые мы обрабатываем с Вашего согласия, или потребовать выполнения договора с Вами в структурированной, общепринятой и машиночитаемой форме, или запросить перевод личных данных третьей стороне. Некоторые из Ваших прав могут быть недействительны согласно применимым законам о защите конфиденциальности.

Если Вы хотите, чтобы мы передали личные данные третьей стороне, обязательно укажите ее и учтите, что мы можем сделать это только при наличии технической возможности. Мы не несем ответственности за безопасность личных данных или их обработку с момента их получения третьей стороной.

Также мы не сможем переслать Вам определенные данные, если их предоставление затронет права других сторон (например, если передача личных данных о Вас раскроет информацию о другом человеке, нашу коммерческую тайну или интеллектуальную собственность), согласно применимому законодательству о защите данных.

### C. Исправление

Вы вправе исправить любые неточности в имеющихся у нас личных данных. Оставляя запрос на исправление, подробно опишите, почему Вы считаете Ваши личные данные у нас неточными или неполными, чтобы мы могли оценить, необходимо ли их исправление.

### D. Ограничение обработки только хранением

Вы вправе в потребовать от нас остановить обработку личных данных о Вас, за исключением хранения при определенных условиях, например, пока мы решаем, необходимо ли исправить или удалить данные или (на основе Вашего возражения) бессрочно остановить их обработку. Обратите внимание: если мы остановим обработку личных данных, мы можем возобновить ее, если для этого будут веские основания (например, защита законных требований или интересов других сторон).

### E. Воспрещение

Вы вправе запретить нам обрабатывать личные данные о Вас за исключением случаев, когда это необходимо для выполнения Условий предоставления услуг.

Вы также вправе запретить нам обрабатывать данные о Вас, отправив электронное письмо на адрес [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com), если мы обрабатываем данные о Вас на основе нашего законного интереса, и Вы возражаете против такой обработки. Укажите причины Вашего запрета, чтобы мы могли определить, нет ли у нас насущного преимущественного интереса в обработке таких данных или необходимости в ней по законному требованию.

### F. Жалобы

Если Вы хотите пожаловаться на то, как мы обрабатываем Ваши личные данные, напишите нам на [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com), и мы постараемся отреагировать на Вашу жалобу. Это не ограничивает Вашего права подать жалобу в надзорный орган той страны ЕС, в которой Вы проживаете или работаете, если Вы полагаете, что мы нарушили законы по защите данных.

XII. Права на конфиденциальность в Калифорнии.
----------------------------------------------

Начиная с 1 января 2020 г., если Вы житель штата Калифорния, США, то по Вашему поддающемуся проверке запросу Вы имеете следующие права (некоторые из них могут быть исключены из этого списка, если это позволяет закон):

* Информация. Вы вправе запросить следующую информацию о том, как мы собирали и использовали Ваши личные данные за последние 12 месяцев: категории “личных данных” (как указано в CCPA), которые мы собирали; категории источников, из которых мы собирали личные данные; деловые или коммерческие цели сбора и/или продажи личных данных; категории третьих сторон, с которыми мы делимся личными данными, чтобы оказывать Вам Услуги. Если Вы попросите нас удалить Вашу информацию или ее часть, Вы можете лишиться доступа или возможности использовать наши Услуги.
* Недискриминация. Вы имеете право на реализацию указанных выше прав без дискриминационных практик, запрещенных законами штата Калифорния.

Реализация прав. Вы можете реализовать свои описанные выше права на конфиденциальность в штате Калифорния, написав нам на адрес [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) или использовав средства для связи внутри игры. Для обработки Вашего запроса на раскрытие, доступ или удаление информации нам будет необходимо подтвердить Вашу личность и Ваше проживание в штате Калифорния. Мы не сможем обработать Ваш запрос, если Вы составите его достаточно подробно, чтобы мы могли его понять и отреагировать на него.

Время реакции. Мы стараемся отвечать на запросы на доступ или удаление в течение 45 дней с момента получения запроса. Если нам нужно больше времени, мы сообщаем Вам о причине и продлении срока в письменной форме.

Личные данные, которые мы собираем, используем и передаем. Мы описываем источники, из которых мы собираем личные данные, а также деловые и коммерческие цели, в которых мы это делаем, в настоящей Политике конфиденциальности.

Мы не продаем Ваши личные данные третьим сторонам. Мы передаем личную информацию третьим сторонам исключительно в деловых и коммерческих целях, описанных в настоящей Политике конфиденциальности, включая рекламу и маркетинг наших Услуг, но не ограничиваясь ими.

XIII. Обновления Политики конфиденциальности
--------------------------------------------

Время от времени мы можем обновлять настоящую Политику, чтобы сохранять нашу приверженность конфиденциальности. Все обновления вступают в силу после внесения и никогда задним числом. При внесении изменений мы обновим дату в верхней части этой страницы и приложим разумные усилия, чтобы уведомить Вас, если эти изменения существенны. Мы рекомендуем Вам чаще заходить на эту страницу, чтобы оставаться в курсе изменений.

Мы будем запрашивать Ваше согласие на передачу Ваших данных третьим лицам, за исключением наших агентов, или на их использование в целях, отличных от тех, в которых они собирались или для которых было получено разрешение. Письменный запрос на ограничение использования и раскрытия Ваших личных данных можно направить на адрес privacy@kixeye.com.

XIV. Контакты
-------------

Если у Вас есть вопросы по Политике конфиденциальности, пишите нам на адрес эл. почты [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Если Вы хотите связаться с нашим главным специалистом по защите данных, пишите на [dpo@kixeye.com](mailto:dpo@kixeye.com).

Política de privacidad de KIXEYE Inc.
=====================================

Última actualización: 23 de junio de 2023

I. Introducción a nuestra Política de privacidad
------------------------------------------------

KIXEYE Inc. («nosotros» o «KIXEYE») se toma en serio los juegos, así como su privacidad y sus derechos de datos. Estamos comprometidos a mantener una relación de confianza y transparencia con usted. Esta Política de privacidad está escrita en un lenguaje sencillo para facilitar la comprensión de cómo recopilamos, usamos, almacenamos y compartimos información que es identificable para usted («Datos personales»: cuando el contexto así lo indique, los «Datos personales» también pueden significar «Información personal», según lo establecido en la Ley de Protección de la Privacidad de los Consumidores de California de 2018 y/o el Reglamento General de Protección de Datos de la UE) cuando accede a nuestros sitios web, aplicaciones móviles, juegos, foros u otros servicios (colectivamente, los «Servicios»). Al usar un Servicio, usted acepta cada recopilación, uso y divulgación de la información (incluidos el registro y el seguimiento) que se describen en la presente Política de privacidad. Léala detenidamente. SI USTED NO ACEPTA ESTA POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD, NO UTILICE NINGÚN SERVICIO.

II. ¿Qué información/Datos personales recopilamos?
--------------------------------------------------

### A. La información que nos proporciona directamente.

Cuando interactúa con un sitio web que sea propiedad de KIXEYE o descarga el Servicio de una tienda de aplicaciones de terceros, recopilaremos y almacenaremos información de usted directamente como se describe a continuación, en la medida en que esté disponible para nosotros. Recopilamos la información que nos proporciona y la información puede incluir su:

* Nombre
* Dirección de correo electrónico
* Información de su cuenta de KIXEYE, como el nombre de usuario único, el ID o el avatar
* Su ID de varias «Redes sociales» (incluidas Facebook, Apple iTunes, Google Play, Steam, etc.)
* También podemos ofrecerle la opción de completar un perfil de usuario que sea visible para otros usuarios del Servicio. Su perfil de usuario puede incluir: una imagen de perfil; uno o más nombres de usuario del Servicio; y un número de identificación de usuario de KIXEYE que crea KIXEYE y utiliza para identificar su perfil.
* Información de pago o facturación
* Sus mensajes para nosotros o los Servicios (registros de chat, solicitudes de atención al cliente)
* Información que nos ayuda a verificar que realmente es usted, prevenir fraudes, así como desarrollar y mejorar nuestros Servicios

### B. La información recopilada automáticamente.

Recopilamos otra información automáticamente de su dispositivo a través de cookies y otros medios (SDK, píxeles de seguimiento, etc.) cuando utiliza nuestros Servicios, incluidos, en la medida en que esté disponible, y cuando sea necesario, sujetos a su consentimiento:

* Dirección IP
* Información del dispositivo de los datos de ubicación generales (como tipo, modelo, sistema operativo, versión del navegador o identificadores únicos del dispositivo para verificar la compatibilidad del dispositivo e IDFA o GAID)
* IDFA significa identificador para anunciantes en Apple y GAID significa identidad publicitaria de Google, por sus siglas en inglés. Estos identificadores únicos no son permanentes ni personales, lo que significa que no contienen información confidencial sobre usted, pero permiten la coherencia en todas las aplicaciones y el seguimiento entre aplicaciones. Puede optar por no compartir el identificador de su dispositivo actualizando la configuración en su dispositivo.
* Comunicaciones del Servicio (mensajes en el juego, registros de chat)
* Tipo de conexión

### C. La información que nos proporcionan terceros.

Podemos tener acceso a cierta información recopilada de usted por terceros, incluidas las Redes sociales, a través de su uso de los servicios, sitios web, aplicaciones u otros servicios de dichos terceros.

### D. La información que recopilamos sobre su cuenta.

Crearemos y asignaremos a su dispositivo un identificador que es similar a un número de cuenta. También recopilaremos la siguiente información sobre usted, en la medida en que esté disponible y, si es necesario, en función de su consentimiento:

* Nombre de usuario del juego;
* Tipo, modelo, sistema operativo, memoria, almacenamiento de dispositivo;
* Número de teléfono;
* País, región, ciudad;
* Nombre de usuario, nombre de personaje;
* Idioma;
* Dirección de correo electrónico; y
* Sus contactos para permitirle invitar amigos para unirse al Servicio.

Cuando utilice nuestros Servicios, recopilaremos información sobre las formas en que usted utiliza e interactúa con nuestros Servicios, como cuándo y durante cuánto tiempo está conectado su dispositivo a nuestros juegos, las funciones del juego a las que accede y los otros jugadores con los que interactúa, las compras en aplicaciones que realiza, el progreso o los niveles que alcanza, y otras actividades de juego.

También recopilamos estadísticas de uso seudónimas sobre sus interacciones con el Servicio. Normalmente, esta información se recopila mediante el uso de archivos de registro del servidor o archivos de registro web, kits de desarrollo de software para dispositivos móviles y tecnologías de seguimiento, como las cookies del navegador para recopilar y analizar ciertos tipos de información técnica. Algunas de las cookies que el Servicio coloca en su ordenador están vinculadas a su(s) número(s) de identificación de usuario. 

### E. La información obtenida mediante su participación en las comunidades

Cuando utilice el Servicio, obtendrá acceso a la comunidad de juegos en línea dentro del Servicio, lo que le brinda la oportunidad de comunicarse o compartir información no solo con nosotros, sino también con otros usuarios de nuestro Servicio mediante:

* La participación en foros de jugadores y tablones de mensajes;
* La publicación de comentarios públicos a otros perfiles de usuarios o tablones de juego;
* El envío de mensajes privados o invitaciones a otros usuarios, ya sea directamente a través de nuestras páginas web o a sus cuentas de correo electrónico;
* El chateo con otros usuarios; y
* La publicación de enlaces web.

Cuando participa en comunidades de juegos en línea, accedemos y almacenamos información y Datos personales sobre usted. La información que almacenamos varía según el juego y la aplicación y se ve afectada por la configuración de privacidad que usted y sus amigos establezcan en ese juego y aplicación. Puede controlar y obtener más información sobre esta configuración dentro de la aplicación. Recopilaremos la siguiente información:

* Su nombre de usuario en el Servicio;
* El ID de anunciante de su dispositivo;
* Dependiendo de cómo inicie sesión en los Servicios, el ID de usuario de Facebook;
* La dirección IP de sus dispositivos de acceso;
* Sus chats y mensajes en el juego; y
* Si los proporciona, su dirección de correo electrónico y número de teléfono.
* Avatares enviados

### F. Información de pago

También recopilaremos cierta información de compra (que consiste en el historial de transacciones, incluido lo que haya comprado, el precio y la fecha). Tenga en cuenta que sus transacciones de compra en el juego y/o en la aplicación son procesadas por procesadores de pago de terceros, como Apple (para compras en dispositivos iOS) y Google (para compras en dispositivos Android). Estos procesadores de pagos de terceros son el «comerciante registrado» para sus compras y no comparten su información financiera, como los números de las tarjetas de crédito, con nosotros.

### G. Correspondencia con atención al cliente

Cuando solicite ayuda a nuestro equipo de atención al cliente, recopilaremos y almacenaremos:

* Su nombre y dirección de correo electrónico;
* Información sobre su actividad en el Servicio;
* Su nombre de usuario o número de ID; y
* Cualquier correspondencia relacionada con la asistencia que se le proporcionó

### H. Información que nunca recopilamos

No recopilamos ninguna «categoría especial de información» de usted ni sobre usted. Es decir, datos o información racial sobre origen étnico, prácticas u orientación sexuales, opiniones políticas, creencias religiosas o filosóficas, afiliación sindical o datos de salud, etc.

III. ¿Cómo y por qué utilizamos esta información y estos Datos personales?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------

Utilizamos sus Datos personales y su información no personal para:

### A. Proporcionarle nuestros Servicios.

* Comunicarnos con usted de acuerdo con sus preferencias y nuestros Términos de servicio.
* Operar, desarrollar, mantener y mejorar nuestros Servicios.
* Proporcionar atención al cliente para los Servicios.
* Resolver disputas y hacer cumplir nuestros Términos de servicio.
* Poner a su disposición ofertas especiales/promocionales en el juego.
* Recaudar tarifas, pagos y otros montos adeudados en relación con los Servicios.
* Permitir que pueda conectar con otros jugadores.
* Crear una cuenta de usuario para usar los Servicios.
* Proporcionarle la versión adecuada de los Servicios, incluso en su idioma preferido.
* Identificar, reparar y solucionar errores y problemas de servicio.
* Desarrollar nuevos servicios.

### B. Proteger nuestros Servicios.

* Identificar y/o prevenir el fraude.
* Identificar y/o prevenir las infracciones de nuestros Términos de servicio, así como las actividades ilegales o trampas.
* Verificar las identidades de los usuarios para comunicaciones de atención al cliente.
* Monitorizar, garantizar y mejorar la seguridad de nuestros sistemas de redes e información.

### C. Personalizar nuestras promociones de Servicios u ofertas.

* Proporcionarle avisos, una experiencia de juego personalizada y otras ofertas.
* Comunicarnos con usted en relación con sus áreas de interés y responder a sus solicitudes.
* Desempeñar nuestras campañas de marketing, así como optimizar y medir la efectividad de las mismas.
* Realizar análisis para estudios demográficos y de marketing interno para desarrollar, mejorar o personalizar los Servicios.
* Guardar y realizar un seguimiento de los atributos, el progreso y las estadísticas de su partida.

### D. Información legal/Otro.

También utilizamos sus Datos personales y su información no personal para:

* Cumplir con las obligaciones jurídicas.
* Ejercer, establecer o defender nuestros Términos de servicio y otros derechos legales.
* Casos en los que creemos de buena fe la necesidad de proteger la seguridad, los intereses económicos o importantes de usted, nosotros o cualquier otra persona.

IV. ¿Con quién compartimos esta información y estos datos personales?
---------------------------------------------------------------------

A excepción de como se describe a continuación, no compartiremos sus Datos personales con terceros no afiliados sin su consentimiento. Sin embargo, podemos compartir datos no personales, incluidos datos anónimos, agregados o seudonimizados de acuerdo con esta Política de privacidad. Podemos compartir su información, incluidos los Datos personales con terceros en los siguientes casos:

### A. Proveedores de servicios de terceros.

Podemos contratar a terceros para recopilar o procesar su información o Datos personales en nuestro nombre para proporcionar los Servicios, como proveedores de alojamiento para almacenar los datos personales que usted proporciona y para los servicios de recuperación en caso de desastres, así como para el cumplimiento de cualquier contrato que celebremos con usted, servicios de entrega de correo electrónico y empresas de análisis (procesamiento de tarjetas de crédito, envío de correos electrónicos de servicio al cliente). Nuestros acuerdos con dichos terceros requieren que protejan la confidencialidad y seguridad de sus Datos personales e información de acuerdo con esta Política de privacidad. No compartimos Datos personales con terceros para que puedan comercializarlo sin su consentimiento.

### B. Empresas afiliadas de KIXEYE.

Somos parte del grupo de empresas StillFront AB. Podemos compartir su información entre nuestras empresas subsidiarias, matrices o afiliadas para brindar y/o mejorar nuestros Servicios y ofrecerle experiencias y ofertas personalizadas.

### C. Un tercero sucesor o adquiriente.

Si KIXEYE es fusionado con un tercero, adquirido, comprado (total o parcialmente), experimenta una desinversión, reorganización, quiebra o acontecimiento similar, la información recopilada bajo esta Política de privacidad puede compartirse con dicho tercero. Le notificaremos si esto sucede.

### D. Según lo requiera la ley.

Podemos divulgar Datos personales si creemos de buena fe que estamos obligados a hacerlo para:

* Cumplir con una obligación jurídica.
* Proteger y defender los derechos o la propiedad de KIXEYE, los usuarios del Servicio u otros.
* Proteger la seguridad personal, así como el interés financiero o importante de los usuarios de los Servicios o el público.
* Proteger contra la responsabilidad jurídica.
* Monitorizar el cumplimiento y hacer cumplir nuestros Términos de servicio, políticas o reglas de los foros/comunidades.
* Responder a las solicitudes legales de las autoridades públicas, incluidas las agencias de seguridad nacional o de los cuerpos de seguridad.

V. ¿Cómo almacenamos y protegemos sus Datos personales?
-------------------------------------------------------

### A. Protección de sus Datos personales.

Implementamos medidas de seguridad razonables para proteger la seguridad de su información, tanto en línea como fuera de línea, y estamos comprometidos con la protección de la información del cliente/usuario. Aunque tomamos precauciones razonables contra las posibles violaciones de seguridad de nuestros Servicios y las bases de datos y los registros de nuestros clientes, no podemos garantizar que nunca se produzcan accesos no autorizados, piratería, pérdidas de datos u otras violaciones. Por desgracia, la transmisión de información a través de internet nunca es completamente segura. Aunque nos esforzamos por proteger sus Datos personales, no podemos garantizar la seguridad de sus datos mientras se transmiten a nuestro sitio; por lo que cualquier transmisión que se realice es bajo su cuenta y riesgo. Le instamos a que tome medidas para mantener segura su información personal (incluida la contraseña de su cuenta) y que cierre sesión en su cuenta después de usarla. Si su cuenta es pirateada, este hecho puede derivar en un acceso no autorizado a su cuenta, así que mantenga segura la información de su cuenta.

### A. Almacenamiento de sus Datos personales.

Los Datos personales que recopilamos, se comparten con nosotros o se procesan de acuerdo con esta Política de privacidad pueden almacenarse en los Estados Unidos o en cualquier otro país en el que operemos nosotros, nuestras subsidiarias/afiliadas o proveedores de servicios externos, incluso mediante el uso de almacenamiento en la nube. Al usar los Servicios, usted acepta la transferencia de sus Datos personales y datos no personales a los Estados Unidos y otros países que pueden no ofrecer el mismo nivel de protección de privacidad que las leyes de su país de residencia o ciudadanía. Como resultado, las autoridades gubernamentales extranjeras podrían acceder a su información o, de lo contrario, de acuerdo con las leyes locales aplicables.

VI. Su control de la privacidad
-------------------------------

Usted tiene control sobre la recopilación y el uso de sus Datos personales. En cualquier momento puede acceder a sus Datos personales o corregirlos, restringir la recopilación o el procesamiento de sus Datos personales y, en algunos casos, solicitar la desactivación o eliminación permanente de sus Datos personales. Para solicitar acceso, corrección, restricción, desactivación o eliminación de sus Datos personales, contáctenos a través de [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Antes de procesar cualquier solicitud, podemos pedirle que verifique su identidad para proteger su privacidad. Esto puede incluir la comunicación a través de la plataforma de Servicios u otros métodos de verificación de identidad.

Las solicitudes que no se hayan verificado o que sean poco razonables o poco prácticas pueden ser rechazadas. Para proteger su cuenta, las solicitudes de desactivación o eliminación de Datos personales requieren una verificación adicional, que puede incluir una suspensión temporal de su Cuenta y los Servicios. Una vez que se procesan las solicitudes de desactivación o eliminación, son permanentes, y los Datos personales y la Cuenta no se pueden restaurar.

VII. Niños menores de 13 años
-----------------------------

Nuestros Servicios no están dirigidos, o tienen la intención de ser atractivos, para niños menores de 13 años. No recopilamos a sabiendas Datos personales, información personal, fotos, videos, archivos de audio o datos de ubicación de niños menores de 13 años, ni usamos a sabiendas identificadores persistentes para reconocer a los niños menores de 13 años a lo largo del tiempo y en diferentes sitios web o servicios en línea. Si es usted menor de 13 años, no use nuestros Servicios y no nos envíe ninguna información. Alentamos a los padres y tutores legales a que supervisen el uso de internet de sus hijos y ayuden a hacer cumplir esta Política de privacidad indicando a sus hijos menores de 13 años que nunca usen nuestros Servicios. Si tiene motivos para creer que un niño menor de 13 años ha proporcionado Datos personales o información personal a KIXEYE a través de nuestros Servicios, comuníquese con nosotros a través de [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) y tomaremos medidas para eliminar dicha información de nuestras bases de datos lo antes posible.

VIII. Políticas y prácticas de privacidad de terceros / Redes sociales
----------------------------------------------------------------------

Esta Política de privacidad solo se aplica a los Datos personales y a la información recopilada por KIXEYE a través del uso de nuestros Servicios. Es posible que se pueda acceder a sitios web de terceros a través de enlaces al utilizar nuestros Servicios, o es posible que usted haya obtenido, accedido o descargado nuestros Servicios a través de sitios web de terceros. Estos sitios web de terceros se rigen por sus propias políticas de privacidad y no somos responsables de ningún contenido que aparezca en dichos sitios web ni de las prácticas de privacidad o seguridad de los mismos. Para administrar la información que KIXEYE recibe sobre usted de las redes sociales donde usa nuestros Servicios, deberá seguir las instrucciones en dicho sitio para actualizar su información y cambiar su configuración de privacidad. Las herramientas de administración de privacidad para aplicaciones en Apple se pueden encontrar en [http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/). Las herramientas de administración de privacidad de Google se pueden encontrar en [https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/). Puede administrar ciertos aspectos de la recopilación y el uso de la información yendo a la configuración de su dispositivo (móvil) y revisando los permisos de cada aplicación.

Una vez que KIXEYE recibe su información de las Redes Sociales, KIXEYE almacena y utiliza dicha información de acuerdo con esta Política de Privacidad, y usted puede acceder y actualizar esa información como se describe a continuación. Las cuentas creadas con KIXEYE se consideran activas hasta que recibimos una solicitud del usuario para eliminarlas o desactivarlas.

IX. Retención de datos / Efecto de las solicitudes de eliminación
-----------------------------------------------------------------

Nos esforzamos por conservar solo la cantidad de Datos personales que sea necesaria. Cuando los Datos personales ya no sean necesarios en virtud de esta Política de privacidad, los eliminaremos o los desidentificaremos. Cuando no sea comercialmente razonable eliminar o desidentificar sus Datos personales, eliminaremos sus Datos personales del procesamiento y los almacenaremos de forma segura hasta que podamos eliminarlos permanentemente. Tenga en cuenta que podemos retener la información necesaria para fines legales y contables, para resolver disputas, hacer cumplir nuestros acuerdos de usuario, proteger nuestros derechos legales y cumplir con las restricciones y los requisitos técnicos y legales. Por ejemplo, podemos conservar los registros relacionados con los pagos o los asuntos de atención al cliente. Si ha enviado o publicado contenido en el Servicio, es posible que no podamos eliminarlo. La eliminación efectiva puede requerir acciones por su parte, como eliminar aplicaciones y/o contenido relacionado con el Servicio de su dispositivo y/o desvincular el Servicio de su(s) cuenta(s) de Red(es) Social(es). Tenga en cuenta que si nos pide que eliminemos su cuenta, perderá permanentemente todo su progreso en el juego y cualquier elemento virtual no utilizado. Tenga en cuenta que los resultados y artefactos de su partida en el juego, p. ej. las bases, los personajes, los barcos, los suministros, etc. pueden permanecer activos en el juego (y sujetos al juego, es decir, destrucción o explotación por parte de jugadores activos) incluso después de que su cuenta y/o Datos personales se hayan eliminado o disociado del juego.

X. Bases legales para usuarios de países europeos
-------------------------------------------------

Si se encuentra en un país de la Unión Europea, el Espacio Económico Europeo o Suiza, las siguientes son las bases legales en las que nos basamos para procesar su información.

* Necesidad contractual. Esto abarca los datos que utilizamos para brindarle los Servicios que ha solicitado y que hemos acordado brindarle, como nuestros juegos, servicios de atención al cliente y funcionalidad de chat;
* Obligación legal. Esto abarca los datos que utilizamos para cumplir con obligaciones legales, como mantener los registros relacionados con impuestos o responder a solicitudes legales válidas de ciertos datos;
* Intereses legítimos. Esto abarca los datos que utilizamos para fines que se pueden esperar razonablemente con su uso de nuestros Servicios y que no creemos que sean perjudiciales para su privacidad, como los análisis para comprender cómo nuestros usuarios navegan por nuestros sitios web y aplicaciones, para mantener seguros y protegidos nuestros sitios web y aplicaciones, investigar y optimizar nuestro Servicio, para proporcionar una experiencia, un marketing y una publicidad más personalizados; y

Consentimiento. En los casos en que procesemos datos en función de su consentimiento, le solicitaremos su consentimiento explícito. Puede retirar el consentimiento en cualquier momento, pero eso no afectará a la legalidad del procesamiento de sus Datos personales antes de dicha retirada.

Aunque puede retirar su consentimiento u objetar ante ciertos tipos de procesamiento en cualquier momento de las formas descritas en esta Política de privacidad, tenga en cuenta que si continúa utilizando los Servicios después de dicha(s) solicitud(es), reanudaremos la recopilación de datos personales sobre usted y los procesaremos como se describe en esta Política de privacidad. Si no desea que recopilemos ningún Dato personal sobre usted, debe dejar de jugar y usar nuestros Servicios.

XI. Derechos de los usuarios de países europeos
-----------------------------------------------

Si se encuentra en un país de la Unión Europea, el Espacio Económico Europeo o Suiza, tiene ciertos derechos en relación a los Datos personales que tenemos sobre usted, los cuales detallamos a continuación y están sujetos a exenciones según las leyes de privacidad de datos aplicables. Algunas de ellas solo se aplican en determinadas circunstancias, como se establece con más detalle a continuación. También establecemos cómo ejercer esos derechos. Tenga en cuenta que podemos solicitarle que verifique su identidad antes de responder a cualquier solicitud para ejercer sus derechos. Responderemos a su solicitud para ejercer dichos derechos sin demoras indebidas y al menos dentro de un mes (aunque este tiempo puede extenderse por otros dos meses en ciertas circunstancias). Para ejercer cualquiera de sus derechos, envíe un correo electrónico a [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Podemos negarnos a procesar solicitudes en determinadas circunstancias, como cuando las solicitudes son manifiestamente infundadas o excesivas o si ponen en peligro la privacidad de otros.

### A. Eliminación de sus datos personales

En algunas circunstancias, puede solicitar que borremos algunos de los Datos personales que tenemos sobre usted. Si desea que se eliminen sus Datos personales, comuníquese con nosotros a través de [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

Tenga en cuenta que para procesar su solicitud y garantizar la eliminación, debe eliminar nuestras aplicaciones/juegos de sus dispositivos móviles y borrar nuestras cookies de cualquier dispositivo donde haya jugado a nuestros juegos. También debe eliminar todos los enlaces de funcionalidad del Servicio dentro de sus cuentas de Redes sociales. Cuando borremos cualquier información, esta se eliminará de nuestras bases de datos activas, pero puede permanecer en nuestros archivos. Sin embargo, tenga en cuenta que aún podemos retener una parte o la totalidad de dicha información para otros fines, como mantener registros financieros, proteger o hacer cumplir los derechos legales, mantener listas de supresión de marketing o por razones técnicas, como mantener la seguridad técnica o la integridad de nuestra base de datos. También podemos retener su información de forma anónima. Consulte el apartado anterior, «Retención de datos / Efecto de las solicitudes de eliminación», para obtener más información sobre las solicitudes de eliminación.

### B. Acceso y portabilidad

Tiene derecho a saber qué información tenemos sobre usted y, en algunos casos, a que se le comunique dicha información. Si desea ejercer este derecho, comuníquese con nosotros a través de [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) y háganos saber que desea ejercer su derecho de acceso, así como exactamente qué información quiere solicitar. Tenga en cuenta que es posible que no podamos proporcionar toda la información que solicita; por ejemplo, si la información incluye información personal sobre otra persona.

En algunas circunstancias, puede solicitar los datos que procesamos de conformidad con el consentimiento o para ejecutar nuestro contrato con usted en un formato estructurado, comúnmente utilizado y legible por máquina o para solicitar que transfiramos dichos datos personales a otra parte. Sus derechos están sujetos a exenciones según las leyes de privacidad de datos aplicables.

Si desea que transfiramos los datos personales a otra parte, asegúrese de proporcionar información detallada sobre dicha parte y tenga en cuenta que solo podemos hacerlo cuando sea técnicamente posible. No somos responsables de la seguridad de los datos personales ni de su procesamiento una vez recibidos por el tercero.

Es posible que tampoco le proporcionemos ciertos datos si proporcionarlos fuera a interferir con los derechos de otra persona (p. ej., cuando proporcionar los datos personales que tenemos sobre usted fuera a revelar información sobre otra persona o nuestros secretos comerciales o propiedad intelectual) según lo permitido por los derechos de protección de datos aplicables.

### C. Corrección

Usted tiene derecho a corregir cualquier Dato personal que tengamos que sea inexacto. Cuando solicite una corrección, explique en detalle por qué cree que los Datos personales que tenemos sobre usted son inexactos o incompletos para que podamos evaluar si es necesaria una corrección.

### D. Restricción del procesamiento para solo almacenamiento

Usted tiene derecho a solicitarnos que dejemos de procesar los Datos personales que tenemos sobre usted para fines que no sean de almacenamiento en determinadas circunstancias, p. ej. mientras estamos considerando si debe corregirse o eliminarse o, según su objeción, si debemos detener el procesamiento de forma permanente. Sin embargo, tenga en cuenta que si dejamos de procesar los Datos personales, podemos volver a utilizarlos si existen motivos válidos para hacerlo (p. ej., para la defensa de reclamaciones legales o para la protección de otra persona).

### E. Objeción

Usted tiene derecho a oponerse a nuestro procesamiento de datos sobre usted, excepto cuando sea necesario para cumplir con nuestros Términos de servicio.

También tiene derecho a oponerse a nuestro procesamiento de datos sobre usted enviándonos un correo electrónico a [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) si estamos procesando los datos que tenemos sobre usted según nuestro interés legítimo y usted se opone a dicho procesamiento. Proporcione detalles sobre su razonamiento para que podamos evaluar si existe un interés imperioso para que continuemos procesando dichos datos o si necesitamos procesarlos en relación con reclamaciones legales.

### F. Quejas

Si desea presentar una queja sobre cómo procesamos sus Datos personales, comuníquese con nosotros a través de [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) y nos esforzaremos por responder a sus inquietudes. Esto sin detrimento de su derecho a presentar una reclamación ante la autoridad supervisora de protección de datos en el país de la UE en el que viva o trabaje, donde crea que hemos infringido las leyes de protección de datos.

XII. Sus derechos de privacidad en California.
----------------------------------------------

A partir del 1 de enero de 2020, si usted es residente de California y, según su solicitud de consumidor verificable, tiene los derechos que se enumeran a continuación (sin embargo, estos derechos están sujetos a ciertas excepciones permitidas por la ley):

* Información. Puede solicitar la siguiente información sobre cómo hemos recopilado y utilizado su Información personal durante los últimos 12 meses: las categorías de «Información personal» (según lo contempla la CCPA) que hemos recopilado; las categorías de fuentes de las que recopilamos Información personal; el propósito comercial o empresarial para recopilar y/o vender Información personal; las categorías de terceros con quienes compartimos Información personal para que podamos brindarle nuestros Servicios. Si nos solicita que eliminemos una parte o la totalidad de su información, es posible que ya no pueda acceder ni utilizar los Servicios.
* No discriminación. Usted tiene derecho a ejercer los derechos descritos anteriormente sin prácticas discriminatorias, prohibidas por la ley de California.

Ejercicio de sus derechos. Puede ejercer sus derechos de privacidad de California descritos anteriormente enviándonos un correo electrónico a [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) o a los métodos de contacto dentro del juego de vez en cuando. Necesitaremos confirmar su identidad y residencia en California con el fin de procesar sus solicitudes para ejercer sus derechos de información, acceso o eliminación. No podemos procesar su solicitud si no nos proporciona detalles razonablemente suficientes para permitirnos comprenderla y responder a ella.

Tiempo de respuesta. Nuestro objetivo es responder a una solicitud de acceso o eliminación de un consumidor dentro de los 45 días posteriores a la recepción de esa solicitud. Si requerimos más tiempo, le informaremos el motivo y la extensión por escrito.

Información personal que recopilamos, usamos y compartimos. Describimos las fuentes de las que recopilamos Información personal y los fines comerciales y empresariales para los que recopilamos esta información en esta Política de privacidad anterior.

No vendemos su Información personal a terceros. Compartimos Información personal con terceros para los fines comerciales y empresariales descritos en esta Política de privacidad, que incluyen, entre otros, la publicidad y el marketing de nuestros Servicios.

XIII. Actualizaciones a nuestra Política de privacidad
------------------------------------------------------

De vez en cuando, podemos actualizar esta Política de privacidad para mantener nuestro compromiso con la privacidad. Las actualizaciones se aplican en el futuro y nunca de forma retroactiva. Cuando hagamos cambios, actualizaremos la fecha en la parte superior de esta página y nos esforzaremos de forma razonable para notificárselo si los cambios son materiales. Le recomendamos que visite esta página con frecuencia para mantenerse al día de cualquier cambio.

Proporcionaremos una opción de exclusión o inclusión voluntaria antes de compartir sus datos con terceros que no sean nuestros agentes o antes de que los usemos para un propósito diferente para el que se recopiló originalmente o se autorizó posteriormente. Para solicitar limitar el uso y la divulgación de sus Datos personales, envíe una solicitud por escrito a [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com).

XIV. Contacte con nosotros
--------------------------

Si tiene alguna pregunta acerca de esta Política de privacidad, envíenos un correo electrónico a través de [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com). Si quiere contactar con nuestro agente de protección de datos, envíenos un correo electrónico a través de [dpo@kixeye.com](mailto:dpo@kixeye.com).

KIXEYE Inc. Gizlilik Politikası
===============================

Son Güncelleme: 23 Haziran 2023

I. Gizlilik Politikamıza Giriş
------------------------------

KIXEYE Inc. ("biz" ya da "KIXEYE") oyunlar konusunda ciddidir. Ayrıca gizliliğiniz ve veri haklarınız konusunda da ciddiyiz. Sizinle güven ve şeffaflık üzerine kurulu bir ilişki sürdürmeye kendimizi adadık. Bu Gizlilik Politikası web sitelerimize, mobil uygulamalarımıza, oyunlarımıza, forumlarımıza veya diğer hizmetlerimize (toplu olarak "Hizmetler") eriştiğinizde sizin için tanılabilir bilgileri ("Kişisel Veri" – “Kişisel Veri” bağlam bunu belirttiğinde aynı zamanda 2018 Kaliforniya Tüketici Gizliliği Koruma Yasası’nda ve / veya AB Genel Veri Koruma Yönetmeliği’nde belirtildiği şekilde “Kişisel Bilgi” anlamına da gelebilir) nasıl topladığımızı, kullandığımızı, depoladığımızı ve paylaştığımızı anlaşılması kolay hale getirmek için sade dille yazılmıştır. Bir hizmeti kullandığınızda, bu Gizlilik Politikası’nda tanımlandığı şekilde bilginin (kaydetme ve takip etme dahil olmak üzere) toplanması, kullanımı ve açığa çıkarılmasının her birine rıza göstermiş olursunuz. Lütfen bunu dikkatli okuyun. BU GİZLİLİK POLİTİKASI’NI KABUL ETMİYORSANIZ, LÜTFEN HERHANGİ BİR HİZMETİ KULLANMAYIN.

II. Hangi Bilgileri/Kişisel Verileri Topluyoruz?
------------------------------------------------

### A. Bize Doğrudan Sunduğunuz Bilgiler.

Sahibi KIXEYE olan bir web sitesi ile etkileşime geçtiğinizde veya hizmeti bir üçüncü parti uygulama mağazasından indirdiğinizde, sizden aşağıda tanımlanan şekilde bizim için mevcut olduğu ölçüde doğrudan bilgi toplayacağız ve depolayacağız. Bize verdiğiniz bilgileri topluyoruz ve bilgiler şunları içerebilir:

* Adınız
* E-posta adresiniz
* Eşsiz kullanıcı adı, kimlik veya avatar gibi KIXEYE hesabı bilgileriniz
* Muhtelif “sosyal ağlardan” kimliğiniz (Facebook, Apple iTunes, Google Play, Steam vb. dahil olmak üzere)
* Ayrıca size diğer hizmet kullanıcılarına görünür olan bir kullanıcı profili tamamlama seçeneği de sunabiliriz. Kullanıcı profiliniz şunları içerebilir: bir profil fotoğrafı; bir veya daha fazla hizmet kullanıcı adı ve KIXEYE tarafından oluşturulmuş olup profilinizi belirlemek için kullanılan bir kullanıcı kimliği numarası.
* Ödeme veya fatura bilgileriniz
* Bize veya hizmetlere mesajlarınız (sohbet günlükleri, müşteri hizmetleri talepleri)
* Gerçekten siz olduğunuzu doğrulamamıza, sahtekarlığı önlememize ve hizmetlerimizi geliştirmemize ve iyileştirmemize yardımcı olan bilgiler

### B. Otomatik Olarak Toplanan Bilgiler.

Siz hizmetlerimizi kullanırken cihazınızdan çerezler ve diğer araçlar (SDK, takip eden pikseller vb.) aracılığıyla otomatik olarak diğer bilgileri topluyoruz, bunlar bizim için mevcut olduğu ölçüde ve gerekli olduğunda, rızanıza bağlı olarak:

* IP adresi
* Genel Konum Verisi Cihaz bilgisi (cihaz türü, modeli, işletim sistemi, tarayıcı sürümü veya cihaz uyumluluğu ve IDFA veya GAID kontrolü yapmak için eşsiz cihaz tanımlayıcılar gibi)
* IDFA, Apple’daki Reklamcılar İçin Tanımlayıcı ve GAID, Google Reklamcılık Kimliği anlamına gelir. Bu eşsiz tanımlayıcılar kalıcı değildir ve kişisel değildir, bu da hassas bilgi içermediği ancak tüm uygulamalar arasında ve uygulamalar arası takipte kararlılığa olanak sağladığı anlamına gelir. Cihazınızdaki ayarları güncelleyerek cihaz tanımlayıcınızı paylaşmaktan vazgeçebilirsiniz.
* Hizmet iletişimleri (oyun içi mesajlar, sohbet günlükleri)
* Bağlantı türü

### C. Üçüncü Partiler Tarafından Bize Verilen Bilgiler.

Bize sosyal ağlar dahil olmak üzere üçüncü partiler tarafından bu partilerin hizmetlerini, web sitelerini, uygulamalarını ve diğer hizmetlerini kullanımınızla sizden toplanmış olan bazı bilgilere erişim verilmiş olabilir.

### D. Hesabınız İle İlgili Topladığımız Bilgiler.

Cihazınıza bir hesap numarasına benzer bir tanımlayıcıyı oluşturacağız ve atayacağız. Ayrıca bizim için mevcut olduğu ölçüde ve gerekli olduğunda, rızanıza bağlı olarak hakkınızda aşağıdaki bilgileri de toplayacağız:

* Oyun kullanıcı adı;
* Cihaz türü; modeli; işletim sistemi; hafızası; depolaması;
* Telefon numarası;
* Ülke, bölge, şehir;
* Kullanıcı adı, karakter adı;
* Dil;
* E-posta adresi ve
* Arkadaşlarınızı hizmette size katılmaya davet edebilmeniz için kişileriniz.

Hizmetimizi kullandığınızda, cihazınızın ne zaman ve ne kadar süre ile oyunlarımızda oturum açtığı, eriştiğiniz oyun özellikleri ve etkileşime geçtiğiniz diğer oyuncular, yaptığınız uygulama için satın alımlar, ilerleme veya ulaştığınız seviyeler ve diğer oynanış etkinlikleri gibi hizmetimizi kullanma ve etkileşime geçme yollarınız ile ilgili bilgiler toplayacağız.

Aynı zamanda hizmet ile etkileşimleriniz ile ilgili takma adlı kullanım istatistikleri topluyoruz. Bu bilgiler genellikle sunucu günlük dosyaları veya web günlük dosyaları, mobil cihaz yazılım geliştirme kitleri ve belirli türde teknik bilgileri toplamak ve analiz etmek için tarayıcı çerezleri gibi takip teknolojileri kullanımı aracılığıyla toplanır. Hizmetin bilgisayarınıza yerleştirdiği bazı çerezler kullanıcı kimlik numara(ları)nıza bağlıdır. 

### E. Topluluklara Katılımınız Aracılığıyla Toplanan Bilgiler

Hizmeti kullandığınızda, hizmet içerisindeki çevrimiçi oyun topluluğuna erişim elde edersiniz, bu da size aşağıdakiler aracılığıyla yalnızca bizimle değil, aynı zamanda hizmetin diğer kullanıcılarıyla da iletişime geçip bilgi paylaşma olanağı sağlar:

* Oyuncu forumları ve mesaj panolarına katılmak;
* Diğer kullanıcıların profillerinde veya oyun panolarında halka açık yorumlar yayınlamak;
* Doğrudan web sitemizden veya onlara ait e-posta hesaplarından diğer kullanıcılara özel mesajlar ve davetiyeler göndermek;
* Diğer kullanıcılar ile sohbet etmek ve
* Web bağlantıları yayınlamak.

Çevrimiçi oyun topluluklarımıza katılımda bulunduğunuzda, hakkınızda bilgiye / kişisel veriye erişir ve bunları depolarız. Depoladığımız bilgiler oyuna / uygulamaya göre değişiklik gösterir ve siz ve arkadaşlarınızın o oyun / uygulama içerisinde belirlediği gizlilik ayarlarından etkilenir. Uygulama içerisinde bu seçenekleri kontrol edebilir ve hakkında daha fazlasını öğrenebilirsiniz. Biz aşağıdaki bilgileri toplayacağız:

* Hizmet içi kullanıcı adınız;
* Cihaz reklamcı kimliğiniz;
* Hizmetlere nasıl giriş yaptığınıza bağlı olarak, Facebook Kullanıcı Kimliği;
* Erişim cihazlarınızın IP adresi;
* Oyun içi sohbetleriniz ve mesajlarınız ile
* Tarafınızca sağlanmış ise e-posta adresiniz ve telefon numaranız.
* Gönderilen Avatarlar

### F. Ödeme Bilgileri

Aynı zamanda bazı satın alım bilgilerini toplayacağız (bunlar ne satın aldığınız, ücreti ve tarihi dahil olmak üzere işlem geçmişinden oluşur). Oyun içi ve/veya uygulama için satın alım işlemlerinizin Apple (iOS cihazları üzerindeki satın alımlar için), Google (Android cihazları üzerindeki satın alımlar için) gibi üçüncü parti ödeme işlemcileri tarafından işlendiğini unutmayın. Bu üçüncü parti ödeme işlemcileri, satın alımlarınız için “kayıt satıcılarıdır” ve kredi kartı numarası gibi finansal bilgilerinizi bizimle paylaşmazlar.

### G. Müşteri Hizmetleri Yazışmaları

Müşteri Hizmetleri ekibimizden yardım istediğinizde şunları toplayacağız ve depolayacağız:

* Adınız ve e-posta adresiniz;
* Hizmet üzerindeki aktivitenize dair bilgiler;
* Kullanıcı adınız veya kimlik numaranız ve
* Size sağlanan yardım ile bağlantılı her türlü yazışma

### H. Asla Toplamadığımız Bilgiler.

Sizden veya hakkınızda hiçbir "özel sınıflandırma bilgisi" toplamayız. Bunlar ırka ait veriler veya etnik köken, cinsel uygulamalar veya yönelim, dini veya felsefi inançlar, sendika üyelikleri ya da sağlık verileri ve benzeri bilgilerdir.

III. Bu Bilgileri / Kişisel Verileri Nasıl Ve Neden Kullanıyoruz?
-----------------------------------------------------------------

Kişisel verilerinizi ve kişisel olmayan bilgilerinizi şunlar için kullanıyoruz:

### A. Size hizmetlerimizi sağlamak.

* Sizinle tercihleriniz ve Hizmet Kullanım Şartlarımız uyarınca iletişim kurmak.
* Hizmetlerimizi yönetmek, geliştirmek, sürdürmek ve iyileştirmek.
* Hizmetler için müşteri desteği sağlamak amacıyla.
* Uyuşmazlıkları çözmek ve Hizmet Kullanım Şartlarımız’ı uygulamak amacıyla.
* Size özel/tanıtıcı oyun içi teklifler sağlamak
* Hizmetlerle bağlantılı beklenen ücretleri, ödemeleri ve diğer meblağları toplamak amacıyla.
* Diğer oyuncularla bağlantı kurmanızı sağlamak amacıyla.
* Hizmetleri kullanmak için bir kullanıcı hesabı oluşturmak amacıyla.
* Tercih ettiğiniz dil de dahil olmak üzere, size hizmetlerin uygun sürümünü sağlamak amacıyla.
* Arızaları ve hizmet hatalarını belirlemek, düzeltmek ve sorun giderme yapmak amacıyla.
* Yeni hizmetler geliştirmek amacıyla.

### B. Hizmetlerimizi güvenceye almak.

* Sahtekarlığı belirlemek ve/veya önlemek amacıyla.
* Hizmet Kullanım Şartları ihlallerini, yasadışı aktiviteleri ve hileleri belirlemek ve/veya önlemek.
* Müşteri hizmetleri iletişimleri için kullanıcı kimliklerini doğrulamak amacıyla.
* Ağımızın ve bilgi sistemlerimizin güvenliğini denetlemek, emniyete almak ve artırmak.

### C. Hizmetlerimizi kişiselleştirmek veya promosyonlar sunmak.

* Size bildiriler, kişiselleştirilmiş oyun deneyimi ve diğer teklifleri sağlamak.
* İlgi alanlarınız hakkında sizinle iletişim kurmak ve taleplerinize karşılık vermek amacıyla.
* Pazarlama kampanyalarımızı sunmak, optimize etmek ve etkililiklerini ölçmek.
* Hizmetleri geliştirmek, iyileştirmek veya kişiselleştirmek için dahili pazarlama ve demografik çalışmalarımıza analizler yapmak.
* Oyun niteliklerinizi, ilerlemenizi ve istatistiklerinizi kaydetmek ve takip etmek.

### D. Yasal/Diğer.

Kişisel verilerinizi ve kişisel olmayan bilgilerinizi ayrıca şunlar için de kullanıyoruz:

* Yasal zorunluluklara uyum sağlamak amacıyla.
* Hizmet Kullanım Şartlarımızı ve diğer yasal haklarımızı kullanmak, tesis etmek veya savunmak amacıyla.
* Sizin, bizim veya başka herhangi bir kişinin güvenliğini, finansal veya önemli menfaatlerini koruma ihtiyacı konusunda iyi niyetli bir inancımız olduğu durumlarda.

IV. Bu Bilgileri / Kişisel Verileri Kimlerle Paylaşıyoruz?
----------------------------------------------------------

Aşağıda tanımlanan durum haricinde, Kişisel Verilerinizi rızanız olmadan bağlı olmayan üçüncü partilerle paylaşmayacağız. Ancak anonim, kümelenmiş veya takma ad koyulmuş veriler gibi kişisel olmayan verileri Gizlilik Politikamız’a uygun olarak paylaşabiliriz. Kişisel verileriniz dahil olmak üzere bilgilerinizi üçüncü partilerle aşağıdaki durumlarda paylaşabiliriz:

### A. Üçüncü Parti Hizmet Sağlayıcılar.

Sağladığınız kişisel verileri depolamak için yer sağlayıcılar ve yıkım onarımı hizmetlerinin yanı sıra sizinle yaptığımız her türlü anlaşmanın performansı için, e-posta dağıtım hizmetleri ve analiz şirketleri (kredi kartı işleme, müşteri hizmeti e-postaları gönderme) hizmetleri sağlamak amacıyla bilgilerinizi veya kişisel verilerinizi bizim adımıza toplaması veya işlemesi için üçüncü partilerle anlaşma yapabiliriz. Bu üçüncü partilerle olan anlaşmalarımız, kişisel verilerinizin ve bilgilerinizin gizliliğini ve güvenliğini bu Gizlilik Politikası doğrultusunda korumalarını gerektirir. Kişisel verilerinizi, rızanız olmadan size pazarlama yapabilmesi için hiçbir üçüncü parti ile paylaşmayız.

### B. KIXEYE Bağlı Ortaklıkları.

Biz StillFront AB şirketleri grubunun bir parçasıyız. Hizmetlerimizi sunmak ve/veya iyileştirmek ve kişiselleştirilmiş deneyiminizi ve tekliflerinizi genişletmek amacıyla iştiraklerimiz, ana şirketimiz veya bağlı ortaklıklarımız arasında bilgilerinizi paylaşabiliriz.

### C. Üçüncü Parti Satın Alımının Bir Halefi.

Eğer KIXEYE bir üçüncü partiyi edinirse, satın alırsa (tamamen veya kısmen); bir elden çıkarma, yeniden yapılandırma, iflas veya benzer bir durum yaşarsa, bu Gizlilik Politikası altında toplanan bilgiler bu üçüncü parti ile paylaşılabilir. Bu gerçekleşirse sizi bilgilendireceğiz.

### D. Yasa Gereği.

Aşağıdaki sebeplerden dolayı yükümlü olduğumuza dair iyi niyetli bir inancımız varsa kişisel verileri açığa çıkarabiliriz:

* Bir yasal zorunluluğa uyum sağlamak amacıyla.
* KIXEYE’a, hizmetlerin kullanıcılarına veya diğerlerine ait hakları veya mülkiyeti korumak ve savunmak amacıyla.
* Hizmet kullanıcılarının veya halkın kişisel güvenliğini ya da finansal veya önemli çıkarlarını korumak amacıyla.
* Yasal yükümlülüğe karşı korumak amacıyla.
* Hizmet Kullanım Şartlarımız’ı, politikalarımızı veya forum/topluluk kurallarımızı uygulamak & uygunluğunu denetlemek amacıyla.
* Ulusal güvenlik veya emniyet teşkilatları dahil olmak üzere kamu yetkililerinden gelen yasal taleplere karşılık vermek amacıyla.

V. Kişisel Verilerinizi Nasıl Depoluyoruz Ve Koruyoruz?
-------------------------------------------------------

### A. Kişisel Verilerinizi Koruma.

Hem çevrimiçi hem de çevrimdışı bilgilerinizin güvenliğini korumak için makul güvenlik önlemleri uygularız ve müşteri/kullanıcı bilgilerinin korunmasına kendimizi adadık. Hizmetimizin ve müşteri veri tabanımız ile kayıtlarımızın olası güvenlik ihlallerine karşı makul tedbirler alsak da, yetkisiz erişimin, kırılmanın, veri kaybının veya diğer ihlallerin asla gerçekleşmeyeceğini garanti edemeyiz. Ne yazık ki, internet üzerinden bilgi taşımak asla tamamen güvenli değildir. Kişisel verilerinizi korumak için çabalamamıza rağmen, sitemiz üzerinden iletilirken verilerinizin güvenliğini garanti edemeyiz; bu nedenle her iletimin riski size aittir. Kişisel bilgilerinizi güvende tutmak için sizi gerekli adımları atmaya (hesap şifreniz dahil olmak üzere) ve kullanımdan sonra hesabınızdan çıkış yapmaya teşvik ediyoruz. Hesabınız kırılırsa, bu hesabınıza yetkisiz erişime yol açabilir, bu yüzden lütfen hesap bilgilerinizi güvende tutun.

### B. Kişisel Verilerinizi Depolama.

Topladığımız, bizimle paylaşılan veya bu Gizlilik Politikası altında işlenen Kişisel Veriler; Amerika Birleşik Devletleri’nde ya da bulut depolama kullanımı aracılığıyla dahil olmak üzere biz, iştiraklerimiz/bağlı ortaklıklarımız veya üçüncü parti hizmet sağlayıcılarımız tarafından faaliyet gösterilen başka herhangi bir ülkede depolanabilir. Hizmetleri kullanarak, kişisel verilerinizin ve kişisel olmayan verilerinizin Amerika Birleşik Devletleri’ne ve ikamet ettiğiniz veya vatandaşı olduğunuz ülkenin yasaları ile aynı seviyede gizlilik koruması sunamayabileceğimiz diğer ülkelere transferine rıza göstermiş olursunuz. Bunun sonucu olarak bilgilerinize yabancı hükümet yetkilileri tarafından, veya bunun dışında geçerli yerel yasalara uygun olarak erişilebilir.

VI. Gizlilik Kontrolleriniz
---------------------------

Kişisel verilerinizin toplanması ve kullanımı üzerinde kontrole sahipsiniz. Dilediğiniz zaman kişisel verilerinize erişebilir veya bunları düzeltebilirsiniz, kişisel verilerinizin toplanmasını veya işlenmesini kısıtlayabilirsiniz ve bazı durumlarda kişisel verilerinizin devre dışı bırakılmasını veya kalıcı olarak silinmesini talep edebilirsiniz. Kişisel verilerinize erişim, düzeltme, kısıtlama, devre dışı bırakma veya silme talebinde bulunmak için bizimle [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) adresinden iletişime geçin. Herhangi bir talebi işlemeden önce, gizliliğinizi korumak amacıyla kimliğinizi doğrulamanızı isteyebiliriz. Buna hizmetler platformu ile iletişim veya diğer kimlik doğrulama yöntemleri dahil olabilir.

Doğrulanmamış, makul olmayan veya elverişsiz olan talepler reddedilecektir. Hesabınızı korumak amacıyla, kişisel verileri devre dışı bırakma veya silme ek doğrulama gerektirir, buna hesabınızın ve hizmetlerin geçici olarak askıya alınması dahil olabilir. Devre dışı bırakma veya silme için talepler işlendiğinde, kalıcı olurlar ve kişisel veriler ile hesap onarılamaz.

VII. 13 Yaşından Küçük Çocuklar
-------------------------------

Hizmetlerimiz 13 yaşından küçük çocuklar için ilgi çekici olmaya yönelik değildir ve bu kastı bulunmamaktadır. 13 yaşından küçük çocuklardan kasten kişisel veri, kişisel bilgi, fotoğraf, video, ses dosyası veya konum verisi toplamayız ya da farklı web siteleri üzerinde veya çevrimiçi hizmetlerde zamanla 13 yaşından küçük çocukları ayırt etmek amacıyla kalıcı tanımlayıcılar kullanmayız. Eğer 13 yaşından küçükseniz, hizmetlerimizi kullanmayın ve bize herhangi bir bilgi göndermeyin. Ebeveynleri ve yasal vasileri çocuklarının internet kullanımını denetlemesi ve 13 yaşından küçük çocuklarına hizmetlerimizi asla kullanmamaları talimatını vererek bu Gizlilik Politikası’nın uygulanmasına yardımcı olmaları için teşvik ediyoruz. 13 yaşından küçük bir çocuğun hizmetler aracılığıyla KIXEYE’a kişisel veri veya kişisel bilgi sağladığına inanıyorsanız lütfen [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) adresinden bizimle iletişime geçin ve bu bilgiyi veri tabanlarımızdan silmek için en kısa zamanda harekete geçelim.

VIII. Üçüncü Parti Gizlilik Politikaları & Uygulamaları / Sosyal Ağlar
----------------------------------------------------------------------

Bu Gizlilik Politikası, yalnızca hizmetlerimizi kullanımınız aracılığıyla KIXEYE tarafından toplanan kişisel veriler ve bilgiler için geçerlidir. Hizmetlerimizi kullanırken bağlantılar aracılığıyla üçüncü parti web siteleri erişilir olabilir veya hizmetimize üçüncü parti web siteleri aracılığıyla ulaşmış, erişmiş veya indirmiş olabilirsiniz. Bu üçüncü parti web siteleri kendi gizlilik politikaları ile idare edilir ve bu web sitelerinde bulunan herhangi bir içerik ya da bu web siteleri için herhangi bir gizlilik veya güvenlik uygulaması için yükümlü ya da sorumlu değiliz. Hizmetimizi kullandığınızda KIXEYE’ın sosyal ağlardan hakkınızda aldığı bilgileri yönetmek için, bilgilerinizi güncellemek ve gizlilik ayarlarınızı değiştirmek için o sitedeki talimatları izlemeniz gerekir. Apple üzerindeki uygulamalar için gizlilik yönetim araçları [http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/) adresinde bulunabilir. Google üzerindeki uygulamalar için gizlilik yönetim araçları [https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/) adresinde bulunabilir. (Mobil) Cihazınızın ayarlarına gidip her bir uygulamanın izinlerini gözden geçirerek bilgi toplanmasının ve kullanımının belirli yönlerini yönetebilirsiniz.

KIXEYE sosyal ağlardan bilgilerinizi aldığında, bu bilgiler KIXEYE tarafından bu Gizlilik Politikası uyarınca depolanır ve kullanılır, bu bilgilere aşağıda tanımlanan şekilde erişebilir ve güncelleme yapabilirsiniz. KIXEYE ile oluşturulan hesaplar, biz bunları silmek veya devre dışı bırakmak için bir kullanıcı talebi alana kadar aktif değerlendirilir.

IX. Veri Saklama / Silme Etkisi Talepleri
-----------------------------------------

Yalnızca gerekli miktarda kişisel veri muhafaza etmek için çaba gösteriyoruz. Kişisel veri bu Gizlilik Politikası altında artık gerekli değilse, bunu sileceğiz ya da kimliksizleştireceğiz. Kişisel verilerinizi silmek veya kimliksizleştirmek ticari olarak makul olmadığında, kişisel verilerinizi işlemden kaldıracağız ve kalıcı olarak silebileceğimiz zamana kadar güvenli şekilde depolayacağız. Lütfen yasal ve hesaplama nedenleriyle, uyuşmazlıkları çözmek, kullanıcı anlaşmalarımızı uygulamak, yasal haklarımızı korumak, teknik ve yasal gereksinimlere ve kısıtlamalara uyum sağlamak için gerekli bilgileri tutabileceğimizi unutmayın. Örneğin, ödemelere veya müşteri hizmeti konularına ilişkin kayıtları tutabiliriz. Hizmet üzerinden içerik gönderdiyseniz veya paylaştıysanız, bunları silemeyebiliriz. Etkili silme, cihazınızdan hizmet ile bağlantılı uygulamaları ve/veya içerikleri silmeniz ve/veya hizmet ile sosyal ağ hesaplarınızın bağlantısını kesmeniz gibi tarafınızdan eylemler gerektirebilir. Lütfen bizden hesabınızı silmemizi isterseniz oyundaki tüm ilerlemenizin ve her türlü kullanılmamış sanal eşyanın tarafınızca kalıcı olarak kaybedileceğini unutmayın. Örneğin üsler, karakterler, gemiler, malzemeler vb. oyun içi oynanışınızdan sonuçların ve kalıntıların, hesabınız ve/veya kişisel verileriniz oyundan silindikten ve ayrıştırıldıktan sonra da oyun içerisinde yayında kalabileceğini (ve oynanışa tabi kalabileceğini, yani etkin oyuncular tarafından yıkım veya kullanılma) unutmayın.

X. Avrupa Ülkeleri Kullanıcıları İçin Yasal Temeller
----------------------------------------------------

Avrupa Birliği’ndeki ülkelerden birinde, Avrupa Ekonomik Bölgesi’nde veya İsviçre’de iseniz, aşağıdakiler bilgilerinizi işlerken dayandığımız yasal temellerdir.

* Sözleşmeli Gereksinim. Bu oyunlarımız, müşteri hizmetlerimiz ve sohbet işlevselliği gibi size sunmamızı talep ettiğiniz (ve bizim kabul ettiğimiz) servisleri sunmak için tarafımızca kullanılan verileri kapsar;
* Yasal Zorunluluk. Bu, belirli bir veri için vergi ile ilgili kayıtları tutmak veya geçerli yasal taleplere karşılık vermek gibi yasal zorunluluklara uyum sağlamak için tarafımızca kullanılan verileri kapsar;
* Meşru Menfaatler. Bu, kullanıcılarımızın web sitelerimizde ve uygulamalarımızda nasıl ilerlediğini anlamak, web sitelerimizi ve uygulamalarımızı güvenli ve emniyetli tutmak, hizmetimizin araştırması ve optimizasyonu, daha kişiselleştirilmiş bir deneyim sunmak, pazarlama ve reklamcılık için analizler gibi servisimizi kullanımınızla makul surette beklenen ve gizliliğinize zararlı olmadığına inandığımız verileri kapsar ve

Rıza. Rızanıza dayalı olarak veri işleme yaptığımız durumlarda, kesin rızanızı isteriz. Rızanızı dilediğiniz zaman geri çekebilirsiniz ancak bu, geri çekilmeden önce kişisel verilerinizin işlenmesindeki yasaya uygunluğu etkilemeyecektir.

Bu Gizlilik Politikası’nda tanımlanan yollarla istediğiniz zaman belirli işleme türlerinden rızanızı çekebilir veya bunlara itiraz edebilirsiniz, ancak lütfen bu tür taleplerin sonrasında hizmetleri kullanmaya devam ederseniz hakkınızda kişisel veri toplamaya devam edeceğimizi ve bunları bu Gizlilik Politikası’nda tanımlanan diğer şekillerde işleyeceğimizi unutmayın. Hakkınızda hiçbir kişisel veri toplamamızı istemiyorsanız, tüm oynanışı ve hizmetlerimizi kullanımınızı sonlandırmanız gerekir.

XI. Avrupa Ülkeleri Kullanıcılarının Hakları
--------------------------------------------

Avrupa Birliği’ndeki ülkelerden birinde, Avrupa Ekonomik Bölgesi’nde veya İsviçre’de iseniz, hakkınızda tuttuğumuz kişisel verilere ilişkin olarak aşağıda detaylandırdığımız belirli haklarınız bulunur ve bunlar geçerli veri gizliliği yasaları altında muafiyete tabi tutulur. Bunlardan bazıları yalnızca aşağıda daha ayrıntılı şekilde gösterilen belirli şartlar altında geçerlidir. Ayrıca bu hakların nasıl kullanılacağını da gösterdik. Lütfen haklarınızı kullanma taleplerinizden herhangi birine karşılık vermeden önce kimliğinizi doğrulamamız gerekebileceğini unutmayın. Bu hakları kullanmak için gönderilen bir talebinize usulsüz gecikme olmaksızın ve en az bir ay içerisinde (bununla birlikte belirli şartlarda bu iki ay daha uzatılabilir) karşılık vereceğiz. Lütfen herhangi bir hakkınızı kullanmak için [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) adresine bir e-posta gönderin.

Taleplerin açıkça esassız veya aşırı olduğu durumlarda ya da başkalarının gizliliğini tehlikeye atan talepler gibi belirli şartlarda talepleri işlemeyi reddedebiliriz.

### A. Kişisel Verilerinizin Silinmesi

Bazı şartlarda hakkınızda tuttuğumuz kişisel verilerden bazılarını silmemizi talep edebilirsiniz. Kişisel verilerinizin silinmesini istiyorsanız lütfen [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) adresinden bizimle iletişime geçin.

Lütfen talebinizi işlememiz ve silinmeyi garantilemek için mobil cihazlarınızdan uygulamalarımızı/oyunlarımızı silmeniz ve oyunlarımızı oynadığınız her cihazdan çerezlerimizi temizlemeniz gerektiğini unutmayın. Ayrıca sosyal ağ hesaplarınızdan tüm hizmet işlevsellik bağlantılarını da kaldırmanız gerekir. Herhangi bir bilgiyi sildiğimizde bu etkin veri tabanlarımızdan silinecektir, ancak arşivlerimizde kalabilir. Bununla birlikte finansal kayıtları sürdürmek, yasal hakları korumak veya uygulamak, pazarlama önleme listelerini sürdürmek gibi amaçlar için ya da teknik güvenliği veya veri tabanı bütünlüğünü sürdürmek gibi teknik nedenlerden, bilgilerin bazılarını veya tamamını yine de muhafaza edebileceğimizi lütfen unutmayın. Ayrıca bilgilerinizi anonim hale getirilmiş bir formda da muhafaza edebiliriz. Silme talepleri hakkında daha fazla bilgi için yukarıdaki “Veri Saklama Silme Etkisi” bölümüne bakın.

### B. Erişim ve Taşınabilirlik

Hakkınızda hangi bilgileri tuttuğumuzu ve bazı durumlarda size iletilen bilgileri bilme hakkınız bulunur. Bu hakkı kullanmak istiyorsanız, lütfen [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) adresinden bizimle iletişime geçerek erişim hakkınızı kullanmak istediğinizi ve tam olarak hangi bilgiyi talep ettiğinizi bize belirtin. Örneğin bilginin başka bir kişi hakkında kişisel bilgi içerdiği gibi durumlarda talep ettiğiniz tüm bilgileri size veremeyebileceğimizi lütfen unutmayın.

Bazı şartlarda, rızanıza dayalı olarak veya sizinle sözleşme yapmak için işlediğimiz verileri yapılandırılmış, kullanımı yaygın ve makinede okunur bir formatta talep edebilir veya bu kişisel verileri başka bir partiye transfer etmemizi talep edebilirsiniz. Haklarınız geçerli veri gizliliği yasaları altında muafiyete tabi tutulur.

Kişisel verileri başka bir partiye transfer etmemizi isterseniz, lütfen bu partiyi ayrıntılı şekilde belirttiğinizden emin olun ve bunu yalnızca teknik olarak uygulanabilir olduğu sürece yapabileceğimizi unutmayın. Kişisel veriler üçüncü parti tarafından teslim alındığında bunların veya işlenmesinin güvenliğinden biz sorumlu tutulamayız.

Ayrıca bazı verileri sunmamız başka bir kişinin haklarına müdahale edecek ise (örn. hakkınızda tuttuğumuz kişisel veriler başka bir kişi hakkında bilgileri veya bize ait ticaret sırlarını ya da fikri mülkiyeti ortaya çıkaracak ise), geçerli veri koruma hakları tarafından izin verildiği şekilde bu verileri size sunmayabiliriz.

### C. Düzeltme

Hakkınızda sahip olduğumuz yanlış olan herhangi bir kişisel veriyi düzeltme hakkına sahipsiniz. Lütfen bir düzeltme talep ettiğinizde, bir düzeltmenin gerekli olup olmadığını belirleyebilmemiz için hakkınızda tuttuğumuz kişisel verinin neden yanlış veya eksik olduğunu ayrıntılı şekilde açıklayın.

### D. İşlemeyi Yalnızca Depolamaya Kısıtlama

Bazı şartlarda hakkınızda tuttuğumuz kişisel verileri depolama amaçları dışında işlemeyi durdurmamızı talep etme hakkınız bulunur, örn. biz düzeltilmesi veya silinmesi gerekip gerekmediğini veya itirazınıza dayalı olarak işlemeyi kalıcı şekilde durdurmamız gerekip gerekmediğini değerlendirirken. Bununla birlikte, kişisel verileri işlemeyi durdurursak, bunları bizim için haklı gerekçeler olduğunda (örn. yasal hak taleplerinin savunulması veya başka birinin korunması için) tekrar kullanabiliriz.

### E. İtiraz

Hizmet Kullanım Şartlarımız altında uygulanması gerekmesi haricinde hakkınızdaki verileri işlememize itiraz etme hakkına sahipsiniz.

Aynı zamanda verileri meşru menfaatlerimize dayalı olarak işliyorsak ve sizin bu işlemeye itirazınız varsa [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) adresinden bize e-posta göndererek hakkınızda tuttuğumuz verileri işlememize itiraz etme hakkına sahipsiniz. Bu verileri işlemeye devam etmemizde mecburi hak çiğneyen bir menfaat olup olmadığını veya yasal hak taleplerine ilişkin olarak işlememiz gerekip gerekmediğini belirleyebilmemiz için lütfen gerekçenize istinaden ayrıntıları sunun.

### F. Şikayetler

Kişisel verilerinizi nasıl işlediğimize dair bir şikayette bulunmak istiyorsanız, lütfen [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) adresinden bizimle iletişime geçin ve endişelerinize karşılık vermek için gayret edelim. Bu, AB içerisinde yaşadığınız veya çalıştığınız, veri koruma yasalarını ihlal ettiğimizi düşündüğünüz ülkenin veri koruma düzenleyici otoritesi ile dava açma hakkınızı çiğnemez.

XII. Kaliforniya Gizlilik Haklarınız.
-------------------------------------

1 Ocak 2020’den itibaren geçerli olarak, bir Kaliforniya sakini olmanız durumunda ve doğrulanabilir tüketici talebiniz üzerine, aşağıda listelenen haklara sahipsiniz (ancak bu haklar yasa tarafından izin verilen bazı istisnalara tabidir):

* Bilgi. Son 12 ay içerisinde kişisel bilgilerinizi nasıl topladığımız ve kullandığımız hakkında aşağıdaki bilgileri talep edebilirsiniz: topladığımız “kişisel bilgilerin” kategorileri (CCPA tarafından tasarlandığı gibi); kişisel bilgileri topladığımız kaynakların kategorileri; kişisel bilgileri toplamanın ve/veya satmanın iş veya ticari amacı; size hizmetlerimizi sunabilmemiz için kişisel bilgileri paylaştığımız üçüncü partilerin kategorileri. Eğer bilgilerinizden bazılarını veya tamamını silmemizi isterseniz, hizmetlere daha fazla erişim sağlayamayabilir ve bunları kullanamayabilirsiniz.
* Ayrımcılık yapmama. Yukarıda tanımlanan hakları Kaliforniya yasaları tarafından yasaklanmış ayrımcı uygulamalardan muaf olarak kullanma yetkisine sahipsiniz.

Haklarınızı kullanmak. Bize [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) adresinden e-posta göndererek veya oyun içi iletişim yöntemleriyle, zaman zaman yukarıda tanımlanan Kaliforniya gizlilik haklarınızı kullanabilirsiniz. Bilgilerinizi, erişim veya silme haklarınızı uygulamak için talebinizi işlemek amacıyla kimliğinizi ve Kaliforniya ikametinizi doğrulamamız gerekir. Anlamamız ve karşılık verebilmemiz için makul şekilde yeterli ayrıntıyı bize sağlamazsanız talebinizi işleyemeyiz.

Karşılık Verme Zamanlaması. Erişim veya silme için bir tüketici talebine, o talebi aldıktan sonraki 45 gün içerisinde karşılık vermeyi hedefleriz. Eğer daha fazla süreye ihtiyaç duyarsak, sizi nedeni ve uzatılma konusunda yazı ile bilgilendireceğiz.

Topladığımız, kullandığımız ve paylaştığımız kişisel bilgiler. Kişisel bilgileri topladığımız kaynakları ve bu bilgileri toplamamızın iş ve ticari amaçlarını yukarıda bu Gizlilik Politikası’nda tanımlıyoruz.

Kişisel bilgilerinizi üçüncü partilere satmayız. Kişisel bilgileri hizmetlerimizin reklamcılığı ve pazarlaması dahil olmak ve bunlarla sınırlı olmamak kaydıyla üçüncü partilerle bu Gizlilik Politikası’nda tanımlandığı şekilde iş ve ticari amaçlarla paylaşırız.

XIII. Gizlilik Politikamıza Güncellemeler
-----------------------------------------

Zaman zaman gizliliğe olan bağlılığımızı sürdürmek amacıyla bu Gizlilik Politikası’nı güncelleyebiliriz. Güncellemeler ileriye dönük olarak geçerlidir ve asla geçmişe dönük olmaz. Değişiklik yaptığımızda bu sayfanın üst kısmındaki tarihi güncelleyeceğiz ve değişiklikler esaslı ise sizi bilgilendirmek için makul çabayı göstereceğiz. Her türlü değişiklikle ilgili güncel kalmanız için bu sayfayı sık sık ziyaret etmenizi teşvik ediyoruz.

Verilerinizi temsilcilerimiz dışındaki üçüncü partilerle paylaşmadan veya aslen toplanma ya da akabinde yetkilendirilme amacından farklı bir amaçla kullanmadan önce size bireysel bir çekilme veya dahil olma seçimi sağlayacağız. Kişisel verilerinizin kullanımını ve açığa çıkarılmasını sınırlama talebinde bulunmak için, lütfen [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) adresine yazılı bir talepte bulunun.

XIV. Bizimle İletişime Geçin
----------------------------

Bu Gizlilik Politikası hakkında herhangi bir sorunuz varsa, [privacy@kixeye.com](mailto:privacy@kixeye.com) adresinden bize e-posta gönderebilirsiniz.
